<reviews>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009O5MWI:horrible_dvd_player:m._martinez
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
13132
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009O5MWI
</asin>
<product_name>
Philips HTS3400D/37 Home Theater System with DVD Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Horrible DVD player
</title>
<date>
June 23, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
M. Martinez
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have bought and returned three of these units now. Each one has been defective, and finally I just gave up on returning the system. The DVD player constantly gives "Bad Disc" errors and skips if there is even the slightest smudge on a disc. The sound quality is very nice for the price, but since the player doesn't work, it's essentially useless. This is a complete rip-off at any price point
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000093IRC:these_dvd-rs_suck:suzette_truesdell
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
29607
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000093IRC
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 4.7GB 4x DVD+R Media (25-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
These DVD-Rs suck
</title>
<date>
February 11, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Suzette Truesdell
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Key Largo, FL
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I used a 25 pack of these doing DVD backups, and the last 5 or so failed. I thought it was my software, so I got new software. Guess what? My first disc out of the new package of 25 that I bought failed, too.  It's not my burner (as another reviewer suggested, implying that people should learn to read), as it's brand new and doesn't require the firmware upgrade they mention. They just suck and have a high failure rate.  So the consensus seems to be that TDK or Sony are best. I'm buying some now and save myself the frustration
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000093IRC:waste_of_money:c._ambrow_"renegade"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
29608
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000093IRC
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 4.7GB 4x DVD+R Media (25-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Waste Of Money
</title>
<date>
January 21, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
C. Ambrow "Renegade"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Tennessee
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought these discs at CompUSA because I needed a few before I got the ones I ordered online. Well, I just wated a good 25 bucks because out of 5 discs, I got one that burned good. Not much bang for the buck. I have burned many discs but never Memorex, usually Verbatim or Ridata or MAM. Very disgruntled with these discs making coasters. Maybe my burners don't like them but whatever the case, I won't buy them ever again. I thought Memorex made good products
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000093IRC:good_when_it_works:stefanie_clay_"stef1223"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
29609
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000093IRC
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 4.7GB 4x DVD+R Media (25-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
good when it works
</title>
<date>
November 3, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Stefanie Clay "stef1223"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Morristown, NJ
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The DVDs I burned successfully showed the movies in excellent quality. The only problem is that for every 3 good burns I get one bad one. I'm using the Plextor DVD burner (love it!!), but I'm going to try my luck with a different DVD brand. The failure rate for Memorex is unacceptable. It's less the cost that bothers me, but more the time wasted on burning coasters
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007P4G76:no_cash_back_here!:mr._b_"1st_gradeteacher"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
38971
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007P4G76
</asin>
<product_name>
Xtreme TB264DKO 264-Disc CD/DVD Case: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
No Cash Back Here!
</title>
<date>
May 15, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Mr. B "1st GradeTeacher"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Washington, D.C.
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Please don't expect to get the cash back from this purchase as promised!  To date, I've been denied twice.  The second time they said the U P C number was invalid. Only, it's the original U P C barcode!  I was meticulous filing the paperwork, yet they state, "All required products were not submitted."  Meanwhile, I have phoned AMAZ0N to lodge a formal complaint.

The product itself is average.  I've used better and worse.  That said, it's definitely not worth the full asking price
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007P4G76:tinstaafl:j._davis_"jimidee"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
38972
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007P4G76
</asin>
<product_name>
Xtreme TB264DKO 264-Disc CD/DVD Case: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
TINSTAAFL
</title>
<date>
March 23, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Davis "jimidee"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Columbia, SC USA/Tokyo, Japan
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
No free lunch and you get what you pay for...is that the verdict on this product?

Well, the poor rating given by those who have purchased this product has discouraged me from buying it.  I need disc binders and the Case Logic brand, while being the original, is pricey.  Low cost alternatives are needed, but not at the expense of quality and TCO (total cost of ownership).  But the flap about poor customer service (rebates) and poor quality (zippers and sleeve binding) is enough to give me pause.....  So, if someone from Xtreme's management is paying attention....fix it or be content to lose business.  Price isn't everything to everyone in the markt for your product..
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00026KJ26:slooooooooow:matt_jones_"matomizer"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
41144
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00026KJ26
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar Media 32X 1 GB Secure Digital Card (SD1GB-32-231): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
slooooooooow
</title>
<date>
February 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Matt Jones "matomizer"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Orlando, FL
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This card is such a disappointment.  It is soooo sloooooow.  I use it for my digital camera, mp3 player, and ipaq.  It takes forever to copy anything to and from it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00026KJ26:worst_choice_of_my_life:yeppy_fan_"alan"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
41146
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00026KJ26
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar Media 32X 1 GB Secure Digital Card (SD1GB-32-231): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 21
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
worst choice of my life
</title>
<date>
March 6, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
yeppy Fan "alan"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
NY
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Bought this a month ago for use with my DX4330 kodak 3MP digital camera. It worked for 2 days.After that, everytime I on the camera, it wanted me to reformat the card,WTH is that?
Now I can't use it at all....
I'm always so confidence with my previous purchases from Amazon.One mistake I made,I threw away the shipping and product packages once I tested out the card, thought It worked and It would be OK.I can no longer return it now.
Needless to say,I'm too over confident with LEXAR's products.
Buyers beware...
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00026KJ26:doesn't_work_with_sd_audio:astrid
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
41147
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00026KJ26
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar Media 32X 1 GB Secure Digital Card (SD1GB-32-231): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
16 of 23
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Doesn't work with SD Audio
</title>
<date>
January 9, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Astrid
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
As the other reviewer found out, these cards can't be formatted to work with SD Audio.  Total waste of money
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009YUPS:freezes_and_tech_help_not_good:jud
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
47542
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009YUPS
</asin>
<product_name>
ADS Tech DVD Express 2.0 (USBAV-701): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Freezes and tech help not good
</title>
<date>
June 21, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
JUD
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Indiana, Richmond
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I purchased dvd express and it never worked. I spent endless time with tech support. The old story about, "It must be your computer." did not fly either, my machine is a media type and it far exceeds the system requirements advertised by ADS. I exchanged the item and it was supposedly checked out before I got it. Same problems. Tech support told me I was the only person having trouble with this product. They need to check out a few websites that review products there are hundreds of bad reviews very few good ones. My only mistake was not reading them before I wasted my time and money. ADS also told me it would not work with Ulead's Movie Factory 3, some of the software it came bundled with, but that was Uleads problem. I should use Cap Wiz ( Their program ) DUH!!! Guess what, it did not work with their program either. Ulead said they had several complaints with ADS's product. Their final solution hold on to the product and maybe they will have a new version of cap wiz and that might work. Save yourself time money and aggravation buy another product! P.S. Since ADS doesn't consider the product defective they will not refund your money or allow you trade it in for an upgrade. I don't think they want a product like that either. The only reason I gave one star is.....it was packed well.
JU
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000092WZ1:worked_great_at_first......:scott_a._urbaniak
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
78002
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000092WZ1
</asin>
<product_name>
Monster Cable Ultra-High Capacity 2100mAh AA Rechargeable Powercells (4 pack): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
worked great at first......
</title>
<date>
March 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Scott A. Urbaniak
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
milwaukee, WI
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
When I purchased these batteries, I was very pleased, but that wore off after a couple of months. I don't use my camera all that often, but when I do, I expect ther batteries to have some charge. I recharge them per instructions, and they do not hold a charge any longer.I know Monster makes good products, but I am a little disappointed in this one
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000092WZ1:nah:tbones73
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
78004
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000092WZ1
</asin>
<product_name>
Monster Cable Ultra-High Capacity 2100mAh AA Rechargeable Powercells (4 pack): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Nah
</title>
<date>
March 8, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Tbones73
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
You can get a 4 pack of Emerging Power 2100 mAH batteries for 9.95 on this very site.   I did.  They work great.  Why would anyone pay almost 30 bucks just for the batteries.  Ridiculous
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006B8MU:not_for_textbooks:e._c._hart
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
78577
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006B8MU
</asin>
<product_name>
Insight Adjustable Book and Copy Holder: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
NOT FOR TEXTBOOKS
</title>
<date>
September 4, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
E. C. Hart
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Ohio USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I wish I never bought this because it was not sturdy enough for textbooks.  If you put a textbook on it and turn the page, it collapses and or tears the page.  I wouldn't even use this for a notebook.  
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001NBHQ2:no_battery_back_up!!__:needbackup_"needbackup"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
86581
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001NBHQ2
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony ICF-CD855VSIL TV/Weather/FM/AM 4 Band CD Clock Radio: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
NO BATTERY BACK UP!!  
</title>
<date>
January 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
needbackup "needbackup"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
nc
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
We bought this clock radio, got it home, set it up, realized that it didn't have battery back up, called Sony only to find out that they do not find it necessary to put that feature on their alarm clocks....how bizarre!!  They do not carry battery back up on any of their new models according to their representative at the customer service center!  Boxed it up and it's going right back where it came from.  If it's okay not to have battery back up, it might deserve a chance, however, what's the use in having an alarm clock if you can't trust that it will indeed wake you up
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001NBHQ2:sucks!:orangeyellowdog_"sosky"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
86582
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001NBHQ2
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony ICF-CD855VSIL TV/Weather/FM/AM 4 Band CD Clock Radio: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
sucks!
</title>
<date>
January 6, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
orangeyellowdog "Sosky"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
California
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Bought new around $80.  CD player and LCD CLOCK stopped working within 6 months--now nap function and radio are all that works--if only I could find the damn receipt!!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00004Z5QI:total_rip-off:m._warren
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
86740
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00004Z5QI
</asin>
<product_name>
Fellowes Book Lift Copyholder - For Use with Textbooks and Large Manuals: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
32 of 33
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Total rip-off
</title>
<date>
August 8, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
M. Warren
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
In the ten minutes since I've had it out of the box two pieces have fallen off.  More importantly, It can't handle large manuals as advertised.  (The reason I purchased this particular book holder)  My 1000 page manual only fits if you happen to only want to read the middle chapter.  Based on that I estimate that this is a totally worthless product to anyone needing to go through a manual or training book more than five or six hundred pages.  If you don't anticipate needing it for a book that big then just glue the rubber feet on, keep an eye on the page retainers (these are the parts that fell off) and you should be ok.  As for me, I'm off to read Amazon's return policy and see if I can get rid of this useless hunk of plastic
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007XH72E:is_there_a_zero_stars?:lauren
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
91851
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007XH72E
</asin>
<product_name>
JVC FSG5 180-Watt Micro Audio System with 5-Disc CD Changer and Digital AM/FM Tuner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Is there a zero stars?
</title>
<date>
May 2, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Lauren
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
said there were no cd's inside
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is the worst thing I have ever owned!!!! It broke (said there were no cd's inside) after about a week! Do yourself a favor don't get this product, don't buy this brand and don't buy from sears they sucked about the whole thing too
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00032Q3WY:it_was_surprise_for_me:y._golod
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
99992
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00032Q3WY
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar Media MULTI CARD READER ( RW022-001 ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
It was surprise for me
</title>
<date>
September 25, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Y. Golod
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Before I bought this reader I considered 2 models 12-in-1: Lexar and SanDisk. I decided to buy Lexar.
I bought this reader to use mostly with Memory stick. I have 2 cards: 128 MB and 1 GB. I had no problem with 128 MB card. 
But I could not insert My GIG card into this reader. It just did not go. I tried hard trying not to break the card - no success. It was a surprise for me. May be because my card was made not by Lexar - by SanDIsk...? I contacted Lexar but did not get any explanation of this problem.
Any way I had to send it back and buy 12-in-1 SanDisk Reader. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000AYKP6U:do_not_buy_this_card_if_you_have_nvidia_chipset:v._ivanov
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
106919
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000AYKP6U
</asin>
<product_name>
Creative Sound Blaster X-Fi Platinum: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
25 of 30
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Do not buy this card if you have NVidia chipset
</title>
<date>
May 30, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
V. Ivanov
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Rockville, MD
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Pros: Perfect sound, solved resampling issues

Cons: famous popping/crackling noises makes it useless for gaming, especially in BF2 (which use OpenAL by Creative). Crystallizer is useless.

This card has the most advanced sound processor which does not work on at least 20% of high end systems, not only NVidia NForce 4 chipset, but also with other AMD and Intel CPU motherboards: see Google for "X-Fi popping/crackling".  Even if you do not have in game crackling immediately, you have a good chance to get it after any memory or HD upgrade or driver configuration change. For long time  Creative denied existence of this problem. Eventually it was recognized (see official CL forums) and a new driver (since November 2005!) was promised at the end of May 2006, but beta version published 05/30/06 did not solve my problem. In the case of old audigy 2 zs the problem was solved with unofficial "hacked" drivers. I suspect that X-Fi crackling is an architecture design flow, which cannot be completely solved at software level, because PCI bus cannot provide sufficient memory access for the "the fastest sound processor" simultaneously with high end graphic card, HD controller, and other devices. 

Bottom end: I have to stop playing games, or go back to low quality integrated sound. Do not take risk, wait for working drivers, or buy a working card from different manufacturer. With fixed drivers I would give this card 4 or 5 stars.

UPDATE 06/12/2006
I found that many desktop motherboards (MB) have really slow south bridge (south bridge is connecting PCI, USB, Firewire, and HD to CPU directly or through north bridge), especially MBs with NVidia chipsets (and even with some Intel MBs). New beta X-Fi driver and MB BIOS updates solved the problem in many cases (but not for my MB Asrock K8NF4G-SATA2, nVidia 6100 / 410 MCP chipset), but situation is still marginal and X-Fi might go unstable again. I contact CL customer service, they did not solved the problem, but pointed out that ATI chipsets (Athlon 64, ATI 200 or 3200) have no problems with X-Fi. I decided not to return SB to seller, but save it for a new computer with ATI based MB. I guess that majority of workstation class MBs with upscale south bridge and PCI-X (even NVidia based) also should be fine with X-Fi. The trouble is that majority of X-Fi buyers have generic NVidia based MBs like me. So I can give X-Fi two stars instead of 1 (but I cannot change the rating), and even more stars if it will work well in my new computer of after new driver release (if it will work)
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002MSTW2:had_pix_loss_w/lexar_cards:frederick_carr_"flrhcarr"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
117022
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002MSTW2
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar Media 1 GB 80x Pro Series Compact Flash Card (CF1GB-80-380): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 25
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Had pix loss w/Lexar cards
</title>
<date>
March 24, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Frederick Carr "flrhcarr"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Kent, WA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
About three years ago, maybe four, I bought two Lexar CFII cards. One never worked, the other worked, but lost all data. I wrote to Lexar, that I had two bad cards, they sent me one new card of the same size. I gave that to my girlfriend and told her to only use it on pix she didn't care about losing. I still have my card, in a ziplock. None of the file removal programs will get the images off, and I've used all of them, and had their (file removal) tech help give up.

In this day and age of "just make the item" I am upset. But you take your chances. Do you want the only picture of your great grand-mother lost because you used a Lexar? I wouldn't, I use an actual sandisk card, myself.

If they ever (Lexar) made it right, I may have written a better review, but they haven't. So that tells me that they don't care.

How important are your pictures to you?


Frederic
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00001XE07:don't_buy_it:frank_wood
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
118260
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00001XE07
</asin>
<product_name>
DeLorme Earthmate GPS Receiver: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Don't Buy It
</title>
<date>
September 3, 2001
</date>
<reviewer>
Frank Wood
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Evanston, Il USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Consider another receiver before buying Delorme's. Delorme's receiver works only with their software (the receiver does not conform to any standard, unlike most other receivers.) The Delorme software itself is not very accurate. Just in looking at the area of a few blocks surronding my home, I found 3 instances where a facility was shown as being located several blocks from where it actually is - but Microsoft had no problem locating the facilities properly. Finally, with the receiver I have, even after the device as been initialized, Delorme's software sometimes is unable to find it. (I suspect that is because the cable on the GPS side sometimes pulls slightly out, but fiddling with it doesn't seem to accomplish much). Real irritating out on the road, as it is when you find one of their printed atlas has been misbound and lacks several pages
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00016L0VQ:very_sad_about_this...:sleepless_in_seattle
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
120341
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00016L0VQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Sandisk 512 MB Secure Digital Ultra II (SDSDH-512-901, Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Very sad about this...
</title>
<date>
July 4, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Sleepless in Seattle
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The card worked fine for my son's graduation and a family holiday but became corrupted during my brother's wedding and I lost all the photos from that event.  I still can't believe it happened.  If you have an iPod, or other, remember to back-up your photos as soon as you can to try and avoid this
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008EM7V:dont_buy_not_worth_a_cent:a._cunningham
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
128291
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008EM7V
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex Optifix Motorized CD/DVD Cleaner and Scratch Repair Kit: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
dont buy not worth a cent
</title>
<date>
August 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
A. Cunningham
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
got it at walmart can't even remove a scuff. i give it -100 good thing i could return it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008EM7V:destroyed_my_cd--i_wanna_give_this_product__minus_5_stars:redgecko
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
128294
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008EM7V
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex Optifix Motorized CD/DVD Cleaner and Scratch Repair Kit: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Destroyed my CD--I wanna give this product  minus 5 stars
</title>
<date>
June 6, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Redgecko
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Park City, UT USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Before the repair process there was one bad track on my CD.  After the "repair" process the entire disk was unplayable.  Took it back for a refund. With billions of CDs in the world, is this the best that the 21st century has to offer?

</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00070QI1S:kingston_2_gb_sd_memory_card:bernard_kliks_"printmaker"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
135752
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00070QI1S
</asin>
<product_name>
Kingston 512MB Elite Pro Secure Digital Memory Card ( SD/512-S ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Kingston 2 GB SD Memory Card
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Bernard Kliks "printmaker"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Portland, OR USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This SD would not work in my  Nikon  Coolpix S6 camera (but the Fuji and Sandisk product did
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001ZIYQ6:what_a_ripoff!:d._jones
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
137987
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001ZIYQ6
</asin>
<product_name>
Hagiwara Sys-Com HNT-MSW1 802.11b Memory Stick Wireless Lan Card for Sony's CLIE Handheld: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
What a ripoff!
</title>
<date>
October 4, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
D. Jones
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Philadelphia
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this card for my TJ25, supposedly a supported device. But the problems with this card make it nearly useless:

- It comes with a web browser that doesn't work.
- Even if the browser DID work, it would only work for 30 days before you had to buy the full version.
- The only downloadable browser that works with the card is Eudora, which doesn't do anything except display text (you can't even fill in web forms with it, so webmail, searches, etc. are impossible).
- The card is designed to work with NetFront and CLIE Mail, software that comes with Internet-enabled CLIE devices... obviously not what you would have if you were buying the card. These programs are not available separately.
- The card wouldn't connect to either my wireless network or the neighbors', even though my PowerBook has no trouble connecting to either, no additional configuration required.
- While attempting to connect, the card would often stop responding, and then lock up the handheld.

Bottom line: if you want a web-enabled PDA, buy a web-enabled PDA. Don't buy this
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008EM7U:sorry_-_didn't_do_the_job_for_me:caris_"caris"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
141452
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008EM7U
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex CD/DVD-Player Laser-Lens Cleaner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
sorry - didn't do the job for me
</title>
<date>
July 8, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
caris "caris"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Los Angeles, CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
i've given it 2 stars instead of 0 because after i used this CD, the sound from my system did seem to be a little better (the CD's were not skipping as much).  but the bottom line is it didn't fix the problem as the CDs are still skipping noticeably, although not as bad as before.  ... not sure if this has anything to do with the fact that my set has a 6-disk CD changer
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000AKVHF:good_except_the_compact_flash_card_gets_stuck:tim_sf
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
144478
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000AKVHF
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDDR-88-A15 8-in-1 USB 2.0 Hi-speed Reader (Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Good except the compact flash card gets stuck
</title>
<date>
October 22, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
tim_sf
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I use this in conjunction with the SanDisk Ultra II 2.0 GB compact flash card.

I like it, but the flash card doesn't slide in easily. Sometimes it get stuck halfway, as if the unit has not been designed properly and the sliders for the card offer enough give to slide the card to the left or right of the pins.

To add insult to injury, both the reader and flash card are manufactured by SanDisk. Therefore, they SHOULD work seamlessly together, but pathetically, they don't.

I'd much rather pay more for a reader that worked great, rather than save a few dollars for a reader that makes you work every time you use the thing.

For comparison, my camera accepts the card perfectly. There is no give at all, but instead is an effortless process.

Not a quality reader.

Other than that, it works as expected. Surprisingly, the reader doesn't topple over as easily as I thought it would. It stands vertically and looks like it might fall over when trying to slide the card in. Sliding the card in a 2 handed process, so one hand holds the unit while the other slides it in.

Removing the card is extremely easy. That's a one-handed process. "Eject" the card from the PC's drive and then remove it.

Data transfer from the card to PC is very quick.

Overall, I'm glad to have it, but it's an annoyance to use it. I hate the card getting stuck halfway in the reader
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002KQRBY:bad_quality,_stay_away_from_them:blackhole
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
144720
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002KQRBY
</asin>
<product_name>
Velocity DVD-R 4X 4.7GB, 10-Spindle: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
bad quality, stay away from them
</title>
<date>
March 7, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
blackhole
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
it was pretty cheap
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Some of the worst DVDs that I have purchased. I wouldn't waste my money on any more of these POS discs. I wish I could return them to amazon, but for what I paid (it was pretty cheap), its not worth the effort.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002KQRBY:2_of_10_coasters:itedin
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
144722
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002KQRBY
</asin>
<product_name>
Velocity DVD-R 4X 4.7GB, 10-Spindle: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
2 of 10 coasters
</title>
<date>
February 16, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
itedin
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Cali
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
If they weren't free, I'd give them 1 star.  Media code: MCC 01RG20.  2 of 10 were coasters at 4X with my DVDRW IDE1008
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000A2K3XW:sony_lcd_rea_projection_televisions:chuck_abdul_"hairman"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
148806
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000A2K3XW
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony KDFE42A10 42" LCD Rear Projection Television: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 12
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
SONY LCD REA PROJECTION TELEVISIONS
</title>
<date>
July 19, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
CHUCK ABDUL "Hairman"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
BALTIMORE,MD.
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I purchased my tv in Dec 2004. I did not purchase the extended warranty. These sets are have all kinds of video problems. Myself and other LCD owners have called for in home service. The service company is QUALXSERV in home service. They want $350.00 to come to your home if you do not have the extended warranty, and can not guarantee a fix. Take it from me buy some other Bran
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000B622CW:not_good:chris_hann
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
149657
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000B622CW
</asin>
<product_name>
Griffin Technology 4026-LCDT iTrip LCD FM Transmitter for iPod: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Not good
</title>
<date>
October 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Chris Hann
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Alameda, CA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The LCD is easier to use than the earlier version that relied on audio clips to switch frequency. You may have to experiment a good deal to find a position where the signal reaches the car radio adequately, like the 1960s rabbit ears tv antennas. Even then, if you are in an are with good FM radio coverage it's going to be hard to find a frequency where this will work. Mostly you can't use this with a cover on and you'll need a car charger if you want to use it for long. The all-in-one modulator and charger that clips to the docking connector is a better solution
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BNMDC4:broke_very_easily:teresa_e._glodek_"tglodek"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
156804
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BNMDC4
</asin>
<product_name>
DLO 009-3032 Transpod All-in-One Car Solution for iPod (Silver): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Broke very easily
</title>
<date>
November 3, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Teresa E. Glodek "tglodek"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Ann Arbor, MI
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The extendable arm breaks very easily.  I had two of them and they both broke within the first month.  The company does have a 3 month warranty but you have to pay for shipping to send it back to them and I have been waiting over a month for my replacement.  Very poor product.  Do not buy
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009FTMK0:slow,_slow_and_slow!:c._meyers
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
161611
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009FTMK0
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk 2 GB Cruzer Micro USB Flash Drive (SDCZ4-2048-A10, Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Slow, slow and SLOW!
</title>
<date>
April 18, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
C. Meyers
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Rockville, MD USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Do NOT buy this product.  It is incredibly slow, by far the slowest USB drive out of the dozen or so that I've used.  It handles small numbers of large files rather well but it immediately chokes whenever faced with a large quantity of small files.  I attempted to copy ~50MB (1500 files, 800 directories) to the disk and it took almost 30 minutes to complete the copy!  That's roughly 27K/second.  Deleting the files was painful as well, taking at least 15 minutes to delete everything.  For kicks, I popped in an old 128 MB Kingston drive and was able to copy the same set of files to it in under 30 seconds and the delete took under 15 seconds.  Bottom line is don't be fooled by the drive's small physical size, large capacity and price point: it simply doesn't perform
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009FTMK0:great_form_factor,_but_dead_slow.:another_tech_guy
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
161613
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009FTMK0
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk 2 GB Cruzer Micro USB Flash Drive (SDCZ4-2048-A10, Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Great form factor, but dead slow.
</title>
<date>
April 8, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Another Tech Guy
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
West of Chicago
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I wanted to replace a Lexar 1GB with this, but I'll keep looking. I used it to transfer a 700MB, 2300 file My Documents folder to a new PC. The transfer seemed pretty slow, but deleting those files from the Sandisk took *61* minutes! Back it goes
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BP50AY:player_failed_after_3_weeks_of_use,_manufacturer_received_unit_back_10_days_ago_and_has_still_not_given_a_date_for_replacement:j._f._shanley_"jim_from_nj"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
169036
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BP50AY
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk Sansa M240 1 GB MP3 Player (Silver): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Player failed after 3 weeks of use, manufacturer received unit back 10 days ago and has still not given a date for replacement
</title>
<date>
November 13, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. F. Shanley "Jim from NJ"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York, NY USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Product :  	MP3 Players Sansa M200 Series Sansa m240
We Received Your Item :  	11/03/2006
Customer Comments : 
11/13/2006 07:51 am   	When will I get my repaired or replaced item. You have had this for 1 week without notifying me of the status. Please respond (by the way, Apple turns around iPod repairs in 1 DAY!).

11/13 Still waiting for an update on the M240 you received on 11/3
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0008KL7B8:mediocre_sound_quality,_questionable_reliability,_weak_radio_reception:robodan
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
183797
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0008KL7B8
</asin>
<product_name>
Philips MCM240/37 Micro Hi-fi System: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
22 of 23
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Mediocre sound quality, questionable reliability, weak radio reception
</title>
<date>
March 23, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
RoboDan
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Pittsburgh, PA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this stereo because of its relatively small size and stylish appearance and because it had aux inputs for me to hook up my mp3 player to it.  

The first unit I received would not turn on at all.  I contacted Philips' tech support, and their solution was for me to send the brand new defective stereo back to them at my expense.  Fortunately, Amazon has a very nice return policy, and I sent it back to them instead.  Amazon was also very nice in sending a replacement right away without waiting until they received the defective unit.

The replacement stereo arrived in short order, and I was immediately disappointed in the sound quality, which didn't seem as good as the 15 year old cassette player boombox that I was replacing.  After listening to the stereo for a few days and comparing it to a Sony CMT-NE3 bookshelf stereo that I own, here are my thoughts.

1. The FM reception is not as good as the CMT-NE3.  Both units have a thin wire type of antenna, and both wires are about the same length.  The Philips stereo, however, would hiss and crackle as I moved around the room - my body interfered with the reception.  This did not happen with the Sony stereo.

2. The sound quality is not as good as the CMT-NE3.  Playing the same song side-by-side on the two stereos, I found that the Philips stereo had a flat, tinny sound when compared to the CMT-NE3.  The Sony system had a much fuller and richer sound quality.  Also, there seemed to be significant distortion in the high-frequencies on the Philips stereo, making "S" sounds sound more like "H" sounds.  I also noticed an occasional crackle of distortion in the overall sound, possibly due to a bad connector on the aux input.

3. The ergonomics of the Philips stereo are not so good.  For one thing, the stereo will easily tip over forwards if accidentally bumped.  If that happens, the CD can get wedged in the CD tray and it becomes almost impossible to remove.  The electronically actuated CD door is much more likely to break than a passive mechanical door like the top-loading CMT-NE3.  The volume goes up to 31 or so, but 5 is about as loud as you would need it for regular listening.  This means that there are only 4 quieter volume levels, which is rather limiting.  Finally, the stereo is a bit bigger than I was expecting (though I could have looked more closely at the specs when buying it).

I am in the process of returning this stereo, and I will try to find a Sony system instead.  Unfortunately, Amazon no longer sells the CMT-NE3, which I bought just about a year ago.  I don't understand why electronics manufacturers feel the need to churn their product lines so rapidly.  Is there really that much innovation in bookshelf stereos?  The only difference between the Sony I bought last year and one I bought in 1989 is the ability to play MP3 CDs. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00020SEYM:don't_buy_infocus!!!!!!____1_star_minus!!:kenneth_mayo
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
184544
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00020SEYM
</asin>
<product_name>
InFocus X2 Multimedia DLP Projector: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
DON'T BUY INFOCUS!!!!!!    1 STAR MINUS!!
</title>
<date>
June 25, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Kenneth Mayo
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
 I have to rate this product and this company as horrible!!

I purchased the X2 in 12/2004. Everything was fine. In 6/2005, the lamp blew. Less than 300 hours on it!!! I called the company. They said sometimes it happens. I questioned the projector. They said I just needed a new lamp. $300.00 later.....oh, you can only get the lamps from them. You can only get service on the X2 from them.

I get the new lamp. It just blew again-about 700 hours-half of what the life should be. Additionally, the fan died-which may be why the lamp blew. Maybe there was a problem with the fan a year ago (when it was STILL under warranty but they wouldn't look at it!!!) No. They say no.

The projector was ceiling mounted and never moved since it was first put in place. The projector was blown clean on a regular basis. This projector was not mistreated or misused.

Infocus says "sometimes this happens".

They, for $250, plus $30.00 shipping, will fix the fan. I also need to buy a new lamp-another $300. The company keeps saying-"It is out of warranty", "sometimes this happens", "1400 hours is just what some lamps get", etc., etc,. etc.. They will not accept that perhaps this was a defective product.

I will get a new projector-I can buy a new one for what they want to charge to maybe fix my current one. My new projector WILL NOT/WILL NEVER be an Infocus product.

They have failed to stand behind their product. Their service is overpriced and their technical support and customer service is nothing more than drones citing manuals and warranties.

Don't buy Infocus!!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00020SEYM:good_product,_forget_about_service:cayman
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
184547
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00020SEYM
</asin>
<product_name>
InFocus X2 Multimedia DLP Projector: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
18 of 18
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Good product, forget about service
</title>
<date>
January 13, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
cayman
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
heart of darkness, central africa
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Good product, forget about service. I e-mailed InFocus about my faulty projector 8th January 2005
it is now 7th January 2006 and I still do not have my projector. That's right, it's been ONE YEAR since
my projector stopped working, I have given up on it being repaired (it was under warranty) and am now
struggling to get it back so that I can repair it out of my own pocket. Check this company's record at 
the Better Business Bureau, it is deemed to be unsatisfactory due to unanswered complaints
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00063RT5K:old_adage_is_true_"you_get_what_you_pay_for":sonic
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
187573
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00063RT5K
</asin>
<product_name>
Tech B BTAA4801 AA Alkaline Batteries 48-Pack: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Old Adage is True "You Get What You Pay For"
</title>
<date>
October 25, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Sonic
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Los Angeles, CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I was hoping for a great deal on these batteries, but like other reviewers I've found that they run out of juice incredibly fast.  I'm amazed that other reviewers have had such good luck because things like my wireless keyboard which uses two AA's ran out of juice in a couple days of normal use while my automatic sprinkler time that uses two AA's lasted only a week.

Be warned that these aren't quite the bargain they may initially seem
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0006IH8AQ:don't_buy._very_bad_customer_service.:zhou
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
189887
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0006IH8AQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Viking CF2GB CompactFlash 2 GB Memory Card: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 16
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Don't buy. Very bad customer service.
</title>
<date>
May 17, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Zhou
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New Jersey, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The worst customer service I have ever experienced. The lady who alledged to be the customer service supervisor said:"You got it cheaper than other brands, what else do you expect?" "Viking cheats. So what?
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002CPBWS:great_for_a_while,_and_then_not_so_good:weary_road_warrior
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
191238
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002CPBWS
</asin>
<product_name>
Microsoft Wireless Notebook Optical Mouse 3000- Winter Blue: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Great for a while, and then not so good
</title>
<date>
October 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Weary Road Warrior
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Chicago, IL
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This was a great mouse for about the first year I owned. After one year is when all of the problems started.  The mouse now loses connection sproadically and sometimes it doesn't want to connect at all.  I have changed the battery quite a few times and that doesn't seem to help.  It is very tempremental, and I have now given up and am shopping for a replacement.

So, a word to the wise - in my experience the mouse will work great for a while, just be prepared to replace it in a year or so
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00083Y4HO:pathetic,_doesn't_work,_waste_of_money:steven_n._gehrman_"code_monkey"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
191370
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00083Y4HO
</asin>
<product_name>
IOGEAR Universal Memory Drive Hi-Speed USB 2.0 Memory Card Reader/Writer: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Pathetic, doesn't work, waste of money
</title>
<date>
November 4, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Steven N. Gehrman "Code monkey"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Los Angeles, CA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Beware of this product.  It always freezes up half way though the download when transfering photos to my computer.  I have another USB 1.0 card reader that works perfectly.  I upgrade to get the speed boost with USB 2.0, but this product is fundamentally flawed and buggy
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000B6KXM8:don't_waste_your_money:c._gunti
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
198915
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000B6KXM8
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony RM-AX4000 Home Theater Remote Control: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Don't waste your money
</title>
<date>
November 4, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
C. Gunti
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Atlanta, GA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This remote is so hard to use and setup. The Xpress functions don't work properly and when used switches to different inputs each time. Most of the interaction with the remote is done on the touch screen so you have to look for the buttons, instead of being able to memorize their locations with your fingers. Get something else
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000AMRTM:a_warning_-_do_not_use:marina_"marina"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
208136
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000AMRTM
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 4.7GB 4x DVD-R (25-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
A WARNING - DO NOT USE
</title>
<date>
April 7, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Marina "Marina"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
OH
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I had no problems burning to these discs, its when I went back a few months later to these discs and found out that none of them work anymore. After further research I found out that Memorex uses the cheapest dye available and thus the DVDs have absolutelly no life to them, my discs started dying after a few months.
In addition, in you physically hold the disc in your hands you can feel how warped physically it has become. This is true for all the discs (about 150 of them). I CAN NOT NOT RECOMMEND THIS PRODUCT STRONLY ENOUGH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000C54E96:great_product_if_i_could_use_it:nancy_mooney
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
216744
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000C54E96
</asin>
<product_name>
NEC ND3550A / 16x8x16x DVD+RW / 16x6x16x DVD-RW / 8x DVD+R DL / 6x DVD-R DL / 48x32x48x CD-RW / Black / Dual Layer / Retail Box DVD Burner with Software: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
great product if I could use it
</title>
<date>
February 22, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Nancy Mooney
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I did the research on this product and it was one of the best. I don't know that to be true due to the fact that the software that they sent me was a demo version that was outdated for use. I have to buy another software package to opperate the product that had stated in the description that the software was included. One if not the only reason I had purchased it. I e-mailed tiger.com and received no reply. If your going to sell something false advertisement is not the way
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EH4Y56:muddy_sound:b._roy_"roytech"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
217843
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EH4Y56
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony MHCEC70 Mini Shelf System with 3-Disc CD Changer, Cassette Deck, and AM/FM Tuner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Muddy Sound
</title>
<date>
October 23, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
B. Roy "RoyTech"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Sunnyvale, CA, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
You will be surprised how crummy this sounds compared to the Panasonics that cost about the same. This is my main problem - the sound quality sucks compared to the competition out there.

1 - The speakers are lightweight and shoddily built. They sound muddy and the deep bass from them is nothing to write home about. They are fairly light weight - meaning very small magnets in them. These are 3 way speakers - for really good sound on the cheap - speakers need to be 2 way!

2 - The sound input consists of a headphone type jack in FRONT. Not even standard phono inputs at the back.

3 - Its advertised as 320 watts - which is meaningless - since the speakers suck. What good is a high power amp with crappy speakers. And in case you know some audio - 320 watts is only twice as loud as 32 watts (log relationship). For some reason, this is not even half as loud as my 100 W receiver!

4 - No user adjustable equalizer, only presets possible

5 - Cannot connect a different pair of speakers to upgrade because of the "biamping" type of connections.

6 - The receiver sucks - even my Sandisk flash player seems to have a better receiver.

I concur with the other reviewer - Death to Sony! Shame on them for taking consumers for a ride. This company nowadays makes it stuff for ultra cheap and prices it "Competively" with the others - meaning - fat profit margins.


</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00000J4CX:what_happened_to_the_hard_case?:doppelganger_"dvd-archive"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
219139
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00000J4CX
</asin>
<product_name>
Case Logic DVA20 Koskin DVD Album (20-Disc Capacity): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
what happened to the hard case?
</title>
<date>
October 9, 2001
</date>
<reviewer>
doppelganger "dvd-archive"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Chicago
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
...I'm so dissappointed in CaseLogic for discontinuing the hard cases. They were great, a HARD cover with rubberized coating and actual cd case style holders inside (that you pop out with your finger by pressing the center). Somebody could have sat on it and it would've been fine..
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00083JQY0:the_easier_way_to_do_it:nicholas_coleman_moore
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
231130
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00083JQY0
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony 1 GB Memory Stick PRO Duo Media (MSXM1GST): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 15
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
The easier way to do it
</title>
<date>
September 2, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Nicholas Coleman Moore
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
RICH,VA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I mean seriously guys, is it really worth forking over to those greedy peeps at Sony over 40 dollars just for a silly memory card. There is an easier way to do it ya know. For your psp, if the game is really important to you and you can't save it. Just press up on the power switch real quick the screen will go off..it will go on hold and next time you wanna play it again.. just push it back up..and hopefully if you did it right you'll have the game right back in the place you left it..hey it saved me 50 dollars..and it can do the same thing for yo
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00007KDVJ:bugs_in_firmware:g._hovden
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
236057
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00007KDVJ
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys WAP54G Wireless-G Access Point: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Bugs in firmware
</title>
<date>
October 14, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
G. Hovden
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
California
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The minor problem is that the user manual claims the user ID is "admin". Well, it is not. Frustration and wasted time will occur until you somehow find out that the user ID should be left blank to log in.

The major problem is that the unit only works for twelve to 36 hours before it has be rebooted. After twelve to 36 hours it looses the connection to the wireless network. Once you unplug and plug back the power cord, it will work fine for another twelve to 36 hours. I am used to rebooting Windows every time it hangs, but I don't accept having a Wireless Access Point that hangs (I am not sure how Microsoft was able to convince me it is OK for an OS to hang). This box is going back. I already bought a Buffalo that works fine
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00007KDVJ:yet_another_wireless_piece_of_junk!!!:joe
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
236064
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00007KDVJ
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys WAP54G Wireless-G Access Point: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 24
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Yet Another Wireless Piece of JUNK!!!
</title>
<date>
May 22, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Joe
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This thing is JUNK!!!  Don't waste your money.  I am a computer professional and I had it working for about 5 minutes, then after powering it down and back up it never did work again!  If you buy one, go through the setup and if it doesn't work immediately SEND IT RIGHT BACK TO AMAZON!  Don't waste your precious time trying to get a $70 brick to do wireless because the odds are that you will just be wasting your time.

Finally, Amazon likes to keep the good reviews toward the top of the list to keep the potential customer from being discouraged. However, YOU SHOULD PAY MORE ATTENTION TO THE BAD REVIEWS THAN THE GOOD ONES. If the product is in fact good it won't have many bad reviews, or even possibly none at all if it is exceptional. However, look up all the bad reviews for this product. They should tell you that something is seriously wrong with this product
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006F2WD:print_heads_are_duds:jack__taylor
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
245085
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006F2WD
</asin>
<product_name>
Canon S530D Photo Printer: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
print heads are duds
</title>
<date>
August 19, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Jack  Taylor
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
which is why I bought the thing
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have had this printer for more than a year.  At first, it was a great printer. Not anymore!!  It uses up ink like no other, yes, it is great to have the individual tanks(which is why I bought the thing) but now the print head isn't working right.  Do several deep cleanings and use up nearly all the full tanks up, and the problem is still there.  The pages have splotchy black marks and the texts are only partially printed.  Went to the canon website, they don't even acknowledge this printer ever existed.
My recommendation is don't buy this model!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006F2WD:canon__s530d_review:"wpaul48"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
245086
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006F2WD
</asin>
<product_name>
Canon S530D Photo Printer: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Canon  S530D Review
</title>
<date>
April 1, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
"wpaul48"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Ranson, WV United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This printer prints fast but the quality is poor. Consumer reports rates it a best buy but I disagree. Pictures come out very graney and its almost worthless to have a 2 megapixel or higher camera because the quality will not be seen with this printer. I do not recommend this printer to anyone. I bought the Cannon to replace a Hewlett Packard deskjet 932C and it was slow but the picture quality was superior to the Cannon. This purchase was a real dissapointment
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000AZ0582:bad_design.....flimsy_toggles.......junk:j._vanburen_"mom_to_3_boys"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
251140
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000AZ0582
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony NW-E307 Walkman Bean 1 GB MP3 Player Black: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Bad design.....flimsy toggles.......JUNK
</title>
<date>
August 25, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. VanBuren "mom to 3 boys"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
VT United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Notice, all the happy....five star ratings, are from people that JUST bought this MP3. I have had mine for 9 months. 

I have had this MP3 since Christmas 2005. I bought the white 512 for my son at the same time. Whith in 3 weeks, my son's was no longer working at all, he had it in his back pack, and some how it got crunched enough to never work again!! I was not happy. Also in a few months, mine started to have issues. The very "tiny" menu button is rediculous. And the main toggle was a complete failure for Sony. I accually removed the cover to the toggle, and just moved the joy stick under it, to change songs, or volume. How stupid. I am so mad about this MP3 player. I am going to buy a Creative V. I have done a lot of research this time, and I will not buy another Sony. The hold button, that is part of this sliding door never works, I find the player dead in my gym bag, all the time!!! Apparently, the door slides over a bit, and the player will turn on, FOR HOURS, and than you have a dead player. Maybe Sony should have given us a on/off button, than this would not happen! Dont do it folks, look into other options, even my mom's iPod Nano is better designed than this joke of an MP3 player.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000AZ00EQ:please_read_this_before_you_invest__your_cash_in_this_product!!!!:sherri_taylor
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
251523
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000AZ00EQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony NW-E305 Walkman Bean 512 MB MP3 Player White: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Please Read this before you invest  your cash in this product!!!!
</title>
<date>
September 29, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Sherri Taylor
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
First off let me state for the record that I only buy Sony , but I have to
advise you against the purchase of the bean walkman. I purchased one in March 2006 and returned it September 2006, as I had purchased replacement
insurance and was able to return it because it broke. It is hard to turn off and the usb port cover always pops open, not to mention the headphones
always pull out. The FM receiver is hard tune in the daylight as the screen is invisiable. Save your self the hassel!!!!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000DD7PE:sandisk_2gb:carlos_carbonell_"ccg922"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
263902
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000DD7PE
</asin>
<product_name>
Sandisk 2GB Compactflash Card Type I (SDCFB-2048-A10, Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 28
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Sandisk 2GB
</title>
<date>
September 6, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Carlos Carbonell "ccg922"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Miami, FL USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I just cam from Las Vegas and the sandisk has a disk error that doesn't allow for more photos after only using 40mb. I have tried to format the disk using the camera and through Windows XP. It doesn't allow it to be formatted. Bad investment!!! Would not recommend the product unless there is a way I can get a refund or an exchange
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000A98AC:very_unreliable:jbat_"jbat"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
264296
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000A98AC
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 4x DVD+RW 25-Pack Spindle: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Very unreliable
</title>
<date>
July 31, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
jbat "jbat"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Fla
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Very unreliable .......... I have used DVD RW and CD RW Memorex disks on multiple computers and DVD recorders.  I find that they.....1) don't last....get about 50 re-recordings NOT 1500  2) may crap out on any occasion.......multiple CD RW's with critical material would NOT read on multiple computers.

AVOID MEMOREX DVD RW and  CD RW DISKS!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009ZY33:dwt108_double_wide_108_disc_dvd_tower:marjoire_j-b_simpson
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
264640
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009ZY33
</asin>
<product_name>
Case Logic DWT108 Double-Wide 108-Disc DVD Tower: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
11 of 15
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
dwt108 double wide 108 disc dvd tower
</title>
<date>
February 25, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Marjoire J-b Simpson
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Was a little hard putting it together.  You have to be very careful taking the cds out or it would fall apart.  I am not happy with this product
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005MIS8:defect_cf_card_i_purchased._how_can_i_get_replacement?:sherwood_zhang
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
268486
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005MIS8
</asin>
<product_name>
Viking CF512M 512 MB CompactFlash Card: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Defect CF card I purchased. How can I get replacement?
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Sherwood Zhang
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have had a Canon G2 since 2002. I used to use Viking 128 MB CF cards and had no problem. In October 2004, I bought one Viking CF512M 512MB CF card from Amazon. I did not use it until this summer. After I had taken 20 more photos and reviewed, I immediately found a few images corrupted. No matter how I tried, e.g. format the CF before use, there were alway corrupted images.

I wonder if I can return the defect CF card and get a replacement from Amazon or from manufacturer?

Sherwood

L.A. count
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006IW1X:has_anyone_else_had_this_problem??:perry_brubaker_"confused!"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
269636
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006IW1X
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 700MB/80-Minute 52x CD-R Media (100-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
HAs anyone else had this problem??
</title>
<date>
October 30, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Perry Brubaker "confused!"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Heres a new one....I have recently bought two spindles of these discs, and my computer (Imac w/ Intel chip-hardly outdated) simply doesnt recognize them-like I never put in a disc at all.  The kicker is that this spring, I also ordered two spindles of these discs (exactly the same as far as I can tell), from which I burned one hundred discs (not a single faulty one!) for a freind overseas.  I have no idea what the deal is, but have a feeling that the issue is not the quality of the discs.  Anyone got ideas?
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0006TI9WG:beware_of_mail-in_rebate_hoax:sanjeevp_"bottom_line"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
270227
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0006TI9WG
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk 1 GB Memory Stick Pro Duo (SDMSPD-1024-A10): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Beware of Mail-in Rebate Hoax
</title>
<date>
November 21, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
SanjeevP "Bottom Line"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The card works as advertised but SanDisk does not send in Mail-in-Rebate. Even though I mailed it in with the UPC Barcode, SanDisk sent me a post card stating that I needed to resubmit it with the barcode. How can I resubmit when they already have the barcode?

In my experience with SanDisk, I got rebate back on one of two cards that I submitted - so you get mail-in rebate 50% of the time with SanDisk. I think mail-in-rebate is a big hoax perpetrated by these companies. Don't trust it!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002CPBWI:great_while_it_lasted...:k._hossein
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
271498
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002CPBWI
</asin>
<product_name>
Microsoft Wireless Notebook Optical Mouse 3000 -Slate: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Great while it lasted...
</title>
<date>
November 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
K. Hossein
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York, NY
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this mouse eight months ago and was quite satisfied - until last week when it stopped functioning altogether.  I really expected a better product and durability from Microsoft.  I've since bought a Logitech VX Revolution Cordless Laser Mouse for Notebooks and love it.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002CPBWI:cheap_hunk_of_junk:d._j._mayard
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
271499
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002CPBWI
</asin>
<product_name>
Microsoft Wireless Notebook Optical Mouse 3000 -Slate: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Cheap Hunk of Junk
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
D. J. Mayard
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Baton Rouge, LA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This was the worst purchase of any type of computer hardware that I have ever made. It felt very light and flimsy, the definition of cheap plastic. Not just the construction but the performance was terrible. It would work perfectly for about a half hour and then go on a break and do NOTHING for about 10 minutes. This was very very frustrating. Maybe I was just unlucky and received a defective one, but I wouldn't take that chance again.

I wish I could give this device a worse rating, somewhere around -4 would be much more appropriate.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007SL4IW:bad_item:bradley_owens_"die_hard_cubs_fan"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
277933
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007SL4IW
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex DVD+R 16x 4.7GB 100 Pack Spindle: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Bad item
</title>
<date>
November 3, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Bradley Owens "Die hard Cubs fan"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Chicago, IL
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I do not like this item because it says it is a 16x DVD but when I put it in my burner it only reads it as 4x.  Something is wrong with the DVDs because my burner is one of the newest out there and it is a 16x burner.  So if you are looking for 16x, do not buy this one
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000B59JJ2:emartbuy_=_incompetence:j._lau
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
279931
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000B59JJ2
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk 512MB TransFlash microSD Card (SDSDQ-512-A10M, Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
EMARTBUY = INCOMPETENCE
</title>
<date>
September 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Lau
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
NYC , New York
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
It's been over 19 days since my SanDisk 512MB Transflash card was "shipped" from EMARTBUY and I still have not received my order. When I contacted EMARTCRAP, all they could tell me was that it had been shipped. I am sure that flash card works great. I just hope that I will receive it before it becomes obsolete. AVOID EMARTBUY AT ALL COST. Don't settle for incompetency. Your are better off paying a higher price for better service...correction any service
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000050AVT:compatibility_issues:joel_greenberg
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
284711
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000050AVT
</asin>
<product_name>
KB Gear Jam Studio: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Compatibility Issues
</title>
<date>
January 7, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Joel Greenberg
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Orange County, CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Cosmetically pleasing is about the only good thing you can say about this unit.  The included software does contain viruses.  The included software is a reminate of the late 80's to early 90's.  The tablet itself does not work under Win2000 nor WinXP.  Under 98 second edition it stops responding quite frequetly and you have to unplug and plug the unit back in to get it to respond again.  This unit would be great, if it came out 7 years ago.  You get what you pay for
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000093IRD:warning:marina_"marina"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
285980
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000093IRD
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 4.7GB 4x DVD+R 4.7GB (50-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
WARNING
</title>
<date>
April 7, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Marina "Marina"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
OH
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I had no problems burning to these discs, its when I went back a few months later to these discs and found out that none of them work anymore. After further research I found out that Memorex uses the cheapest dye available and thus the DVDs have absolutelly no life to them, my discs started dying after a few months.
In addition, in you physically hold the disc in your hands you can feel how warped physically it has become. This is true for all the discs (about 150 of them). I CAN NOT NOT RECOMMEND THIS PRODUCT STRONLY ENOUGH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002A9SJ2:cleaning_machine..._didn't_repair.:jean_m._gallant
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
287379
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002A9SJ2
</asin>
<product_name>
Aleratec DVD/CD Disc Repair Plus: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Cleaning machine... didn't repair.
</title>
<date>
November 5, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Jean M. Gallant
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The machine does fine for quick cleaning of your cd's/dvd's.  I can't give a complete review of the product because I only tried to repair 1 dvd... and it did not repair it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002A9SJ2:mine_was_doa_too:cara_thrace
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
287385
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002A9SJ2
</asin>
<product_name>
Aleratec DVD/CD Disc Repair Plus: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
9 of 14
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Mine was DOA too
</title>
<date>
May 26, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Cara Thrace
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
How do I assign a rating? As several other people have experienced, my unit is also DOA. I received it, plugged it in, pressed 'clean', and the motor started up. I popped open the cover, put in the disc I wanted cleaned, and pressed 'clean' again. Nothing. Terrible quality control.

What's worse is the unit case is glued together -- no way to open it up to try to fix the electronics inside without mutilating it and voiding warranty
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002A9SJ2:not_impressed...at_all._will_just_have_to_keep_buying_new_copies_until_something_better_comes_along!:ajax
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
287386
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002A9SJ2
</asin>
<product_name>
Aleratec DVD/CD Disc Repair Plus: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Not impressed...at all. Will just have to keep buying new copies until something better comes along!
</title>
<date>
May 19, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Ajax
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Kansas City, MO
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I ordered this on the recommendation of another Amazon customer. I wasnt impressed. I though this would save me money because until then I had been just buying new copies of my favorite CDs that were scrathced up. I cleaned a few discs and ran them through all three "processes" without successful results. It didnt seem to make much difference with any of my discs. I dont think this is a good "repairer" of any disc thats more than mildly scratched. My suggestion would be to just replace your damaged discs by buying another copy of your CD or DVD on AMAZON!! Many of my CDs I have replaced for $7-10 bucks on here. I wish I wouldve kept my $25
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000CD0B7:disappointed:d._lees
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
287609
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000CD0B7
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDCFH-1024-901 1 GB Ultra II CompactFlash Card (Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Disappointed
</title>
<date>
September 29, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
D. Lees
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
VA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I purchased this flash card in June for my GPS memory. Loaded fine, but only lasted 3 months. Card lost all it's memory and was unable to take a new load. Very disappointed in the life of the card.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00004XRDM:dead_after_a_few_months:brian_morris
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
289749
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00004XRDM
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys L03040 Power 2GO Inverter - Car Cigarette Lighter Power Supply: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 12
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Dead after a few months
</title>
<date>
September 4, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Brian Morris
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Pittsburgh, PA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
As with some of the other reviewers, mine stopped working and blew the fuse in my car for the cigarette lighter.  I bought a Vector brand inverter at Wal-Mart and it is much better
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00004XRDM:not_a_quality_item:hugo_calendar
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
289752
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00004XRDM
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys L03040 Power 2GO Inverter - Car Cigarette Lighter Power Supply: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Not a quality item
</title>
<date>
July 8, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Hugo Calendar
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Monument, CO
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This item worked for a while, but required fiddling (unplugging and replugging repeatedly) with the lighter socket each time I restarted my car.  Eventually, however, it blew out the fuses in both my lighter sockets.  Don't waste your money on this piece of crap
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00004XRDM:the_linksys_converter_was_pure_junk!:gene_r._barnes_"randy"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
289753
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00004XRDM
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys L03040 Power 2GO Inverter - Car Cigarette Lighter Power Supply: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
The Linksys converter was pure junk!
</title>
<date>
July 6, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Gene R. Barnes "Randy"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Perryton, Tx
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The product not only did not work but blew out fuses in my car.  The mechanic who checked my car out said the device had a dead short in it.  I have written to your customer service department and asked for money back but to no avail.  I will not purchase another thing from Amazon until my money is refunded
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00004XRDM:never_worked:d._ross_"just_an_average_guy"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
289754
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00004XRDM
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys L03040 Power 2GO Inverter - Car Cigarette Lighter Power Supply: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Never worked
</title>
<date>
June 16, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
D. Ross "Just an average guy"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
About a year ago I got one of these to allow me to play DVDs for my kids on my laptop while travelling.  It has an alarm that sounds when your battery is getting too low -- well it sounded immediately .  I figured that my car battery was not fully charged or on its last legs.  I hadn't tried to use it since.  Now that I'm taking another trip, I thought I'd try it out in other cars.  No luck.  The thing is dead -- doesn't do a thing when I plug it in
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00004WHFL:data_clears_with_battery_change:frank_schipani
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
294162
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00004WHFL
</asin>
<product_name>
Franklin EBM-901 eBookman (Metallic Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Data clears with battery change
</title>
<date>
November 8, 2003
</date>
<reviewer>
Frank Schipani
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Waterford, MI USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Each time you replace the battery you have to reload all of your data.  Don't waste your money on this one
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006JPFU:great_product!_for_two_days!:grant_d._green_"contrabass.com"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
298312
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006JPFU
</asin>
<product_name>
Coby CA-747 Dual Position CD/MD/MP3 Cassette Adapter: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Great product! For two days!
</title>
<date>
October 26, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Grant D. Green "Contrabass.com"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Los Altos, CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
When this adapter first arrived, I thought it was great. The sound quality was excellent, and free of all the distortion and interference I get from using an FM transmitter-style adapter (there are few open frequencies in the SF Bay Area). The first day, I used it for about 20 minutes total (didn't have far to drive), and it worked great. The second day I had a bit farther to drive. After about 30 minutes, it quit. Hasn't worked again since.

I didn't expect it to last forever, but less than an hour?

Yes, it has a 1 year warranty: just send the unit back with a money order ($6) to cover the return postage. Of course, then you're spending more in postage than you originally spent for the unit..
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006JPFU:worked_great_for_a_couple_of_days....:gil_adamowski_"love_science_now_guy"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
298313
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006JPFU
</asin>
<product_name>
Coby CA-747 Dual Position CD/MD/MP3 Cassette Adapter: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Worked great for a couple of days....
</title>
<date>
October 4, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Gil Adamowski "Love Science Now Guy"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Denver, Co
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I was so excited about how great this product worked when I got it.  I had purchased the FM transmitter for my wife and they do not work so great so I thought since my car had a tape deck I would give this a try.  I was excited that I had all my ipod music with me, BUT after less than a week it the sound  started going down hill to a point where I couldn't listen anymore with it.  It is now in a landfill somewhere.  My guess is I will need a radio in the car that is ipod compatiable cable.  For now just have the radio and CDs I burn
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00003IE4J:these_cost_$10.00_with_shipping!:s_marc80_"s_marc80"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
298997
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00003IE4J
</asin>
<product_name>
Energizer E91BP-4 AA Batteries (4-Pack): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
These cost $10.00 with shipping!
</title>
<date>
February 2, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
s_marc80 "s_marc80"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
No kidding!!  The shipping charge on these batteries was over $6.00.  Amazon doesn't itemize the shipping charges on your order, so if you order multiple items, you won't know that you're being raped by Crutchfield until it is too late!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00001XE07:don't_buy_it:frank_wood
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
326609
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00001XE07
</asin>
<product_name>
DeLorme Earthmate GPS Receiver: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Don't Buy It
</title>
<date>
September 3, 2001
</date>
<reviewer>
Frank Wood
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Evanston, Il USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Consider another receiver before buying Delorme's. Delorme's receiver works only with their software (the receiver does not conform to any standard, unlike most other receivers.) The Delorme software itself is not very accurate. Just in looking at the area of a few blocks surronding my home, I found 3 instances where a facility was shown as being located several blocks from where it actually is - but Microsoft had no problem locating the facilities properly. Finally, with the receiver I have, even after the device as been initialized, Delorme's software sometimes is unable to find it. (I suspect that is because the cable on the GPS side sometimes pulls slightly out, but fiddling with it doesn't seem to accomplish much). Real irritating out on the road, as it is when you find one of their printed atlas has been misbound and lacks several pages
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007P4G76:be_warned!:jane_hush_"rain_taster"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
334097
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007P4G76
</asin>
<product_name>
Xtreme TB264DKO 264-Disc CD/DVD Case: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Be Warned!
</title>
<date>
November 23, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Jane Hush "rain taster"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
These Xtreme cd cases STINKs,literally! I don't know what kind of plastic material they are using and if they are toxic, but the smell is absolutely nauseous. I kept it for two weeks hoping the smell would go away. Nope. Finally I threw it away. 
Other than the smell, quality-wise it is ok. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007P4G76:coming_apart_at_the_seams:c._saxton_"catsax"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
334104
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007P4G76
</asin>
<product_name>
Xtreme TB264DKO 264-Disc CD/DVD Case: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Coming Apart at the Seams
</title>
<date>
March 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
C. Saxton "catsax"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New Jersey
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
In theory an excellent product -- room for lots of disks, relatively compact and attractive HOWEVER I purchased three of these (2 for me 1 for a friend) I can't say how his is doing but both of mine have faulty zippers, making  it impossible to close the binders and therefore losing much of their attractiveness and compactness. (...). All in all, a disappointment
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009YUPS:i_would_never_recommend_this_product_to_anyone:rono_wubker
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
340466
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009YUPS
</asin>
<product_name>
ADS Tech DVD Express 2.0 (USBAV-701): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
I Would Never Recommend this Product to Anyone
</title>
<date>
August 19, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Rono Wubker
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
California
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I've only got this thing to work for about 3 hours and that is not in a row.  I've spent hours with this product on several machines and I can now say the hardware sucks. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009YUPS:don't_buy_this!:robert_campbell
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
340469
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009YUPS
</asin>
<product_name>
ADS Tech DVD Express 2.0 (USBAV-701): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Don't buy this!
</title>
<date>
July 14, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Robert Campbell
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
ID United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This isn't a consistent product. 99% of the time, I can't get it to work. After MONTHS of emails and phone calls, customer service responded. What a joke! They told me the plug in the unit and then unplug, wait 30 seconds, and then plug in. Gimme a break! I shouldn't have to do the Hokie Pokie just to get it to work. By the way, their process didn't work. Poor product, Poor customer service, Poor price
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001YM07G:worked_great_at_first,_till_it_only_started_taking_left_turns...:maxethan_"ethan"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
347420
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001YM07G
</asin>
<product_name>
Xbox Cordless Precision Controller: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Worked great at first, till it only started taking left turns...
</title>
<date>
April 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
maxethan "ethan"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Boston, Ma, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I was impressed with this controller at first, and found it to feel comfortable, and work well. It was played with once and a while for about a month (total 10 hours max). Some time after that, the next time I went to use it, it would only go left in a game that used the left joystick. I could not get it to center (or even stay still), it would just keep either steering the car (like Burnout3) or whatever the left joystick would do for the game no matter what. I tried it several times, and it has never worked since. I fire it up once and a while to see if it's still doing it, and it does. I am very dissapointed in this, and I was pretty careful about getting this newer version of the Logitech controller. I think I paid about $45 locally for it, and I just bought a Pelican Extreme edge from Radio shack on clearance for $19.99 that works and feels as good, but is less than half the cost. I don't really feel like going thru a warranty claim, if it's even covered, but it still annoys me every time I look at it in my Xbox 'drawer' of extra stuff.

I was going to go totally wireless (4 units) and luckily didn't run out and buy 3 more of these Logitech controllers. I instead bought some extra Microsoft S controllers, as they are still one of the best feeling controllers out there. If the Pelican holds up, (model PL-2050 version 2.0) I might go get some more if I can find them locally.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001YM07G:just_horrible:frank_saldivar_"im_too_cool_for_a_signature"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
347421
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001YM07G
</asin>
<product_name>
Xbox Cordless Precision Controller: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Just horrible
</title>
<date>
April 1, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Frank Saldivar "im too cool for a signature"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
edinburg, texas
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I am a gamer and i know a good controller when i feel it. This is a horrible controller. I mean it works well for maybe like a week or two, in that time you love it...but after a month its breaks down and turns into a heap of crap thats a dread to play with. The triggers just become extremely sensitive past the point of enjoyment. I swear the triggers are sensitive to gravity. I'm just playing halo 2 and out of nowhere my finger isn't on the grenade trigger and i just threw a grenade. It can spoil a good game of halo in an instant. Occasionally it disconnects from its receiver which makes it useless until you push the connect button on the receiver. Which takes about 10 dear seconds. After the contoller started breaking down, i had just bought a normal green microsoft xbox controller and it was a breath of fresh air. This controller is [...] and don't bother picking it up.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000AKA8Y:good_when_it_works:j._crupper_"jkc777"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
350586
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000AKA8Y
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus PA248U Tornado Notebook Chill Pad: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Good when it works
</title>
<date>
November 11, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Crupper "jkc777"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Lake Zurich, IL USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this item not to cool my laptop, but to provide some insulation from the heat when it's on my lap sitting in a chair. I'm very satisfied with it's being able to accomplish that. HOWEVER, the cord ended up breaking after a few months. Targus replaced it at no charge which is good, but still a hassle. Now one of the two fans has started making a racket when I first turn it on. After a bit it settles down but very noisy at first.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000AKVHF:this_junk_died_and_erased_100_images:poet/naturalist
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
366208
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000AKVHF
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDDR-88-A15 8-in-1 USB 2.0 Hi-speed Reader (Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
This junk died and erased 100 images
</title>
<date>
August 5, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Poet/Naturalist
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
MN USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The is perhaps the lease durable item I have purchased in 40 years. It lights up just fine, and it is a reassuring led gold, but it refuses to do anything with my xd card. It worked just fine for 3-4 days, then erased about 100 photos, all of them irreplaceable. Cheap yes, but Cheap Junk.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002KQRBY:i_wish_there_were_negative_stars....:clayton_dean_"cmd"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
366524
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002KQRBY
</asin>
<product_name>
Velocity DVD-R 4X 4.7GB, 10-Spindle: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
I wish there were negative stars....
</title>
<date>
August 2, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Clayton Dean "CMD"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Arlington, VA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The DVDs are a rip-off, although I'm counting on the REBATE to at least break even (not counting my time).

The DVD player completely fails to recognize them.  Even after extensive troubleshooting with Disk Management and ensuring my regionalization was not an issue....  

Just a poor product -- Velocity ought to be ashamed.  More Taiwanese junk.  (I'd recommend Verbatim's DVD+R DL product - made in Singapore)

As a note I can get other DVD-Rs to work just fine...

I haven't submitted the rebate yet, so no comment on the veracity of other negative rebate comments
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002KQRBY:does_not_work:tech_novice_"hex_johnson"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
366527
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002KQRBY
</asin>
<product_name>
Velocity DVD-R 4X 4.7GB, 10-Spindle: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Does not work
</title>
<date>
April 18, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Tech novice "Hex Johnson"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Raleigh, NC
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I tried 4 DVDs with different DVD writers and still doesn't work.  This stuff is junk.  In addition, the manufacturer
never sent the rebate.  Don't buy anything from Velocity
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00032Q3WY:it_was_surprise_for_me:y._golod
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
378823
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00032Q3WY
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar Media MULTI CARD READER ( RW022-001 ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
It was surprise for me
</title>
<date>
September 25, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Y. Golod
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Before I bought this reader I considered 2 models 12-in-1: Lexar and SanDisk. I decided to buy Lexar.
I bought this reader to use mostly with Memory stick. I have 2 cards: 128 MB and 1 GB. I had no problem with 128 MB card. 
But I could not insert My GIG card into this reader. It just did not go. I tried hard trying not to break the card - no success. It was a surprise for me. May be because my card was made not by Lexar - by SanDIsk...? I contacted Lexar but did not get any explanation of this problem.
Any way I had to send it back and buy 12-in-1 SanDisk Reader. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002ZAIM8:pos!__broke_w/in_6_months_and_apple_bailed_on_it.:mark_a._webster_"dunedain"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
382805
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002ZAIM8
</asin>
<product_name>
Apple 1 GB iPod Shuffle: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
POS!  Broke w/in 6 months and Apple bailed on it.
</title>
<date>
November 24, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Mark A. Webster "Dunedain"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Oklahoma
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
What a crock as it looks like everyone else got good product and good service!  I got a shuffle and something happened the second time I tried to load music to make it not even play.  I took it to the Apple Store in Mall of America (Minneapolis, MN) and they claimed to know there was an issue and claimed to have fixxed it.  I go back home (OK) and it still does not work.  Apple said for $113 they'll fix.  Gee thanks!  I'll be looking at another brand!  Apple stinks
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006L7XC:$2+__for_a_aaa_cell?:blake_mason_"doppler"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
387871
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006L7XC
</asin>
<product_name>
Monster High Capacity Alkaline Monster PowerCells AAA 1150 mAh Power Capacity AAA 4 Pack 1150 mAh MB AAA ALKA-4: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
$2+  for a AAA cell?
</title>
<date>
December 31, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Blake Mason "Doppler"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Livermore, CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Maybe if these were high end rechargable NiMH this would be a reasonable price. But for Alkaline? This is even more ridiculus than the cables they sell. You can find AAA battieries on Amazon for a third of this price
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009FTMK0:terrible..._want_to_throw_it_in_the_trash:b._kirk
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
391917
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009FTMK0
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk 2 GB Cruzer Micro USB Flash Drive (SDCZ4-2048-A10, Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Terrible... want to throw it in the trash
</title>
<date>
June 24, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
B. Kirk
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Monterey CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
But I won't because I paid good money for it.  As you can see from the other reviews, the speed on this thing is pathetic, almost to the point of non-functional when it comes to many small files.  I had a small game on the drive, but it has tons of small files in the folder. It took over 10 minutes to delete a 10 mb folder... makes you wonder if SanDisk spent 10 minutes to test this thing. Stay away.. or if you really want one, buy mine please
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009FTMK0:better_not_to_buy:rajagopal_alagarsamy_"-_raj"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
391919
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009FTMK0
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk 2 GB Cruzer Micro USB Flash Drive (SDCZ4-2048-A10, Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
11 of 13
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Better Not to Buy
</title>
<date>
May 17, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Rajagopal Alagarsamy "- Raj"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Concord, CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I'm the consumer of SanDisk USB flash drives. I have used couple of sandisk flash drives (i.e. 512MB Mini, 256MB Mini) before I bought this product. 

Performance wise this particular product is not doing good. It's taking long time to copy files from my computers. Even it's taking long time to delete files from this disk. So I returned to Amazon and looking for Mini products from SanDisk.

I doubt all the Micro products which is having capacity more than 512MB. Now I'm planning to buy 512MB or 1GB SanDisk Mini USB flash drive.  

Better buy some good one than wasting your time on this product
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007WKB14:broke_after_1+_year:pedro_marmol
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
400339
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007WKB14
</asin>
<product_name>
Panasonic DMR-ES10S DIGA Series DVD Recorder (Silver): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
broke after 1+ year
</title>
<date>
July 19, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Pedro Marmol
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Austin, Texas United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Overall the recorder worked OK. A moderate inconvenience was that once in a while the recorded DVDs could not be finalized for unexplained reasons.
However, that is irrelevant now. A few weeks ago, the unit stop working. I does not turn on at all. What a waist! It is out of warranty now
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BP50AY:player_failed_after_3_weeks_of_use,_manufacturer_received_unit_back_10_days_ago_and_has_still_not_given_a_date_for_replacement:j._f._shanley_"jim_from_nj"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
403084
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BP50AY
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk Sansa M240 1 GB MP3 Player (Silver): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Player failed after 3 weeks of use, manufacturer received unit back 10 days ago and has still not given a date for replacement
</title>
<date>
November 13, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. F. Shanley "Jim from NJ"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York, NY USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Product :  	MP3 Players Sansa M200 Series Sansa m240
We Received Your Item :  	11/03/2006
Customer Comments : 
11/13/2006 07:51 am   	When will I get my repaired or replaced item. You have had this for 1 week without notifying me of the status. Please respond (by the way, Apple turns around iPod repairs in 1 DAY!).

11/13 Still waiting for an update on the M240 you received on 11/3
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00001MXVP:only_bought_because_imation_sonix_stopped_making_their_label:cjm_"777"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
404029
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00001MXVP
</asin>
<product_name>
Fellowes NEATO 2000 CD/DVD Labeler Kit: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 15
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Only bought because Imation Sonix stopped making their label
</title>
<date>
January 9, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
cjm "777"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
No where near as easy to use as my old system ,But with trial and error can have a decent amount of control over your Projects.But one interesting thing someone mentioned earlier
is that regardless of with system you use these labels can alter
the way DVDs play making them stick and freeze and wondering if its the disks,burner or what..after some experimenting I did
confirm that it was actually the labels I was having so much fun making...It might be the weight but i think its possibly the way the beam shines through the disc and reflects off the white label backing..Dunno but if you all of a sudden start having problems try a labeling tape or a sharpie
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000DZDMB6:it_doesn't_work_at_all.:tmc_"nivisionbat"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
416498
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000DZDMB6
</asin>
<product_name>
Transfer Video Directly To DVD Capture Video for Psp Or Apple Ipod: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
It doesn't work at all.
</title>
<date>
October 13, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
TMC "nivisionbat"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Gabriel, CA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I connected all the cables as instructed, but it doesn't work, the light is not on.
So I return it to Amazon
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002MSTWC:*buyers_beware*!_check_your_camera_model_before_you_buy_this:shkshk
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
419778
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002MSTWC
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar Media 512 MB 80x Pro Series Compact Flash Card (CF512-80-380): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
*Buyers Beware*! Check your camera model before you buy this
</title>
<date>
February 11, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Shkshk
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Pflugerville, Texas United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
These cards only work with Camera that supports the Write Acceleration !! otherwise the speed is no different from a 12X card. There is nothing wrong with the card in terms of capacity or quality.

I have given a single star rating coz it should clearly state that the 80x speed is only possible with cameras supporting Write Acceleration !!

Very Few camera support this technology and one can easily get the same capacity ( 12x ) at 1/4 the mentioned price. SO why pay more if your camera does not support this technology !
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005BC0H:no_support:j._kim
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
421583
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005BC0H
</asin>
<product_name>
C Pen 800C Handheld Scanner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
NO SUPPORT
</title>
<date>
June 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Kim
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Let's be honest.
This product ain't cheap. It's not something you can just throw away if it decides to stop working. 
I bought mine at cpenusa.com. Delivery was great, only took them a couple of days. However, my c-pen cable was damaged. The connector to the c-pen was, for some reason, cut in half. Without it, you can't recharge or connect the c-pen to the pc.
I called their main office all the way in Sweden during the office hours. NO RESPONSE. I sent three e-mails to cpenusa. NO RESPONSE.
I don't care if the product itself is great(I'll never know now, will I..). If you're unable to receive support when you need 'em, you're screwed. 
If you're just interested in electronic equipments, just want to try things out and don't really care if you're on your own, go ahead and try it. Let me know how this thing really is. Otherwise, buy a product that you can trust on with respect to after-sales support
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00020SEYM:don't_buy_infocus!!!!!!____1_star_minus!!:kenneth_mayo
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
426280
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00020SEYM
</asin>
<product_name>
InFocus X2 Multimedia DLP Projector: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
DON'T BUY INFOCUS!!!!!!    1 STAR MINUS!!
</title>
<date>
June 25, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Kenneth Mayo
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
 I have to rate this product and this company as horrible!!

I purchased the X2 in 12/2004. Everything was fine. In 6/2005, the lamp blew. Less than 300 hours on it!!! I called the company. They said sometimes it happens. I questioned the projector. They said I just needed a new lamp. $300.00 later.....oh, you can only get the lamps from them. You can only get service on the X2 from them.

I get the new lamp. It just blew again-about 700 hours-half of what the life should be. Additionally, the fan died-which may be why the lamp blew. Maybe there was a problem with the fan a year ago (when it was STILL under warranty but they wouldn't look at it!!!) No. They say no.

The projector was ceiling mounted and never moved since it was first put in place. The projector was blown clean on a regular basis. This projector was not mistreated or misused.

Infocus says "sometimes this happens".

They, for $250, plus $30.00 shipping, will fix the fan. I also need to buy a new lamp-another $300. The company keeps saying-"It is out of warranty", "sometimes this happens", "1400 hours is just what some lamps get", etc., etc,. etc.. They will not accept that perhaps this was a defective product.

I will get a new projector-I can buy a new one for what they want to charge to maybe fix my current one. My new projector WILL NOT/WILL NEVER be an Infocus product.

They have failed to stand behind their product. Their service is overpriced and their technical support and customer service is nothing more than drones citing manuals and warranties.

Don't buy Infocus!!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0006IH8AQ:don't_buy._very_bad_customer_service.:zhou
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
434664
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0006IH8AQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Viking CF2GB CompactFlash 2 GB Memory Card: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 16
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Don't buy. Very bad customer service.
</title>
<date>
May 17, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Zhou
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New Jersey, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The worst customer service I have ever experienced. The lady who alledged to be the customer service supervisor said:"You got it cheaper than other brands, what else do you expect?" "Viking cheats. So what?
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00007IFMJ:never_received_it!:vladas_mazelis_"reviewer07"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
437023
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00007IFMJ
</asin>
<product_name>
Viking 256 MB Secure Digital Flash Card (SD256M): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Never received it!
</title>
<date>
March 21, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Vladas Mazelis "reviewer07"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Port Richey, FL USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This item was promised to me as a free bonus for my purchase of Casio Exilim camera, but was never delivered. Now Amazon wants me to review it, so here your are..
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00017IX10:good_system_-_one_huge_flaw:kevin
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
442256
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00017IX10
</asin>
<product_name>
Altec Lansing inMotion Portable Audio System for iPod: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Good system - one huge flaw
</title>
<date>
November 8, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Kevin
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
SLC, UT
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is a good product - sounds great, gets good battery life, everything you'd hope for in an iPod dock.  But it has one major flaw.  The iPod docking port is really flimsy, and has no structural support aside from the actual electronics themselves.  After a little bit of use, the connection between the iPod and the dock deteriorated to the point that the volume fluctuated up and down, and sometimes the sound cuts out all together.

If they added some kind of simple support so that bumping the iPod wouldn't stress the electronics, I'd give this thing 5 stars.  But without that, it simply breaks quickly, and no longer performs its only job - to sound good.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00080YK9Y:hunk_of_junk,_go_for_the_manual_version:j._zell_"mediocre_perfectionist"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
445946
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00080YK9Y
</asin>
<product_name>
Skip Dr. Motorized Automax Scratch Repair System: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Hunk of junk, go for the manual version
</title>
<date>
August 14, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Zell "Mediocre perfectionist"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Virginia Beach USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Luckily, I didn't pay a penny for the motorized SkipDr. as it was given to us as a "prize." I have the original (manual) SkipDr. which worked every time, and I always end up using it instead. It has more than paid for itself in repaired CD's--$20 for an entire kit at a wholesale club that came with spare sanding discs and the whole shebang.

The motorized version didn't come with any deep scratch sanding pads, which I need about 25% of the time for a badly scratched disc. Most of the time the automatic sensor fails to detect that a disc is even in the machine, and won't start turning, so I have to squeeze it together to make it work
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000B6KXM8:channel_+_did_not_work:ian_anderson
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
447997
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000B6KXM8
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony RM-AX4000 Home Theater Remote Control: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Channel + did not work
</title>
<date>
November 22, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Ian Anderson
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
MPLS, MN
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
One of the most essential buttons on any remote is the Channel + button and it did not work straight out of the box.  I returned it.

Beyond that, setting it up takes time but is not difficult.  I am just going to wait and see about the next model that comes out
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000B6KXM8:sony_rm-ax4000:joey
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
448001
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000B6KXM8
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony RM-AX4000 Home Theater Remote Control: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Sony RM-AX4000
</title>
<date>
November 3, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Joey
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
North  Wales, PA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is a poorly designed remote. I have six devices connected to my HD television set. The software depends on the user assigning positions to the various inputs to the TV and, in my case, routinely activated the wrong device when I used the remote. I purchased a Logistics Harmony remote and it works perfectly. At this point the only thing that I use the remote for is to remotely turn on my satellite receiver at a certain time during the day to record to Replay TV (which cannot turn the TV on and off).
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002IWCAQ:batteries_are_supposed_to_be_standardized:mr_t_"mrt"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
451447
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002IWCAQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony NH-AACE AA Rechargeable Batteries In Slide Case: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Batteries are supposed to be standardized
</title>
<date>
October 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Mr T "mrt"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Diego, CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have two Ni-MH chargers and sony batteries won't charge in them. They probably use some proprietary technology to prevent using other brand chargers. They force you to buy their own non-standard charger that probably won't again charge other brand batteries. And of course this is not mentioned anywhere. No wonder these batteries are the cheapest. Don't waste your money or support Sony's attempt to bring non-standard products into a standardized market. Soon we have to carry bunch of chargers instead of the good old times when just one was enough
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000092YQW:fooled_again:jake_sanders
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
459361
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000092YQW
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony MDR-EX71SL Fontopia In-The-Ear Headphones (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Fooled again
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Jake Sanders
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Boulder, CO United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Once again I'm amazed at how the reviews were so highly in favor of this product.  These are terribly uncomfortable (for my ears) and don't really provide that great of listening experience. The frequency response seems muted until you use the largest possible "surrounds", and then they become distractingly uncomfortable.  But of course, this is just my experience, your mileage may vary, as they say.  Personally, I found my Apple iPod 'phones to be better
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002WPSBC:disappointed:epiphane_flavius
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
459517
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002WPSBC
</asin>
<product_name>
Logitech Z-5500 Digital 5.1 5-Piece Speaker System with Subwoofer: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Disappointed
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Epiphane Flavius
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Wichita Falls, TX  USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I am disappointed in this product.
I was suppose to write to you from the weekend.
My two rear speakers just stop working, and also my
remote control. I have replace the batteries, but still
does not work.
I don't have any other rear speakers to try on the system.
Pleasy me what to do.

Thank you
Epiphane Flaviu
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002IQ1I0:poor_compatibility:david_c._sellers
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
460295
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002IQ1I0
</asin>
<product_name>
Verbatim 8x 4.7 GB DVD+R (100-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 12
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
poor compatibility
</title>
<date>
March 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
David C. Sellers
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Hattiesburg, MS United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
while the verbatim has burned well in 100% of my recordings they fail to operate in at least 24 different dvd players
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000AMRTM:a_warning_-_do_not_use:marina_"marina"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
461868
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000AMRTM
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 4.7GB 4x DVD-R (25-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
A WARNING - DO NOT USE
</title>
<date>
April 7, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Marina "Marina"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
OH
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I had no problems burning to these discs, its when I went back a few months later to these discs and found out that none of them work anymore. After further research I found out that Memorex uses the cheapest dye available and thus the DVDs have absolutelly no life to them, my discs started dying after a few months.
In addition, in you physically hold the disc in your hands you can feel how warped physically it has become. This is true for all the discs (about 150 of them). I CAN NOT NOT RECOMMEND THIS PRODUCT STRONLY ENOUGH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000AMRTM:incompatible_with_my_burner:j._cummings_"artgeekseattle"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
461869
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000AMRTM
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 4.7GB 4x DVD-R (25-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Incompatible with my burner
</title>
<date>
January 21, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Cummings "artgeekseattle"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Seattle, WA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This media did not work on my brand new asus burner, even after updating the firmware
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009UDABW:ads_tech_video_xpress_usbav-191-ef:gerald_v._bolton
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
464187
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009UDABW
</asin>
<product_name>
ADS Tech Video Xpress USBAV-191-EF: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
ADS Tech Video Xpress USBAV-191-EF
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Gerald V. Bolton
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Can capture analog video and produce cd-rom's but I expected the ability to produce DVD
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009UDABW:spend_a_little_more...:amy_kirsch
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
464192
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009UDABW
</asin>
<product_name>
ADS Tech Video Xpress USBAV-191-EF: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Spend a little more...
</title>
<date>
November 3, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Amy Kirsch
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Allyn, WA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this to record Tivo DVR stuff to DVD.  Worst frame rate capture and audio capture of .avi's of the four different devices I have tried.  Completely unusable.  The software is a trial version.  Instead, buy the ADS DVDXpress DX2 for a bit more.  Ulead's software is stable, and it's not a trial version.  It is also the only analog capture device I have tried that gives a good picture using mpeg capture.  Pinnacle's Dazzle only is tolerable using avi capture which is great if you have the drive space, but the software is way too buggy
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000CFY7I:leaked_in_my_grundig_radio,_what_a_mess>:lumi
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
467627
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000CFY7I
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex High Performance AA Alkaline Batteries, 50 Pack: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
leaked in my Grundig radio, what a MESS>
</title>
<date>
May 30, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Lumi
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I got sucked into this deal about a year ago and can say long term, risky cells.
It could be because the clock draws even when the radio part is off but I'm
not willing to chance it again
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009MZ9UA:bad:canito_"canito_40"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
468483
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009MZ9UA
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 4.7Gb/16x DVD-R (50-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Bad
</title>
<date>
October 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Canito "canito_40"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Lima, Peru
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
If these were free, i'd still would not recommend them, due to all the time that you will waste with faulty recordings.

It is the discs, I must assume, since my burner works fine with other brands.

Anyway, (now) I think it's best to invest a bit more and get good media..
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00000J506:not_very_durable._will_need_battery_changes.:d._amini_"zbestdoc"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
488248
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00000J506
</asin>
<product_name>
APC BP500UC Back-UPS Pro 500: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Not Very Durable. Will need battery changes.
</title>
<date>
February 5, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
D. Amini "zbestdoc"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Washington DC
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have owned five of these UPS units over the past four years. I purchased three for my Mac and PC at home. Then I had to purchase two replacements for units that simply quit. Currently only ONE still works! I have very infrequent power outages, perhaps three in the past four years. These units work well to allow you to save your work and shut down. My G5 mac was so power hungry that I had to use one for the computer and another for the 23 inch LCD.  I can't comment on other UPS brands such as Belkin,  but I have seen many competing brands on the web and at the computer stores. There seen to be quite a few dealers selling refurbished APC products but this may be a reflection of APC's popularity rather than the poor reliability of their brand. My experience over the past four years has been mixed. These are not inexpensive units and you have to decide how precious your data becomes. If you really fear the loss of data during a blackout then the answer is clear. I chose to switch to high quality surge suppressors and never work during potential storms. Many users do not have that flexibility so a UPS is essential insurance. The units I puchased were identical and only one unit is still operational after four years. I can accept the need to replace the battery every one to two years; three of the batteries failed and alarms beeped until I bought new batteries. Prices vary from $15 to $50 depending on the vendor. Battery life depends on many factors so I don't begrudge APC for wear and tear on the battery but to have 4 out of 5 units simply stop working is unacceptable. I bought APC branded batteries and can't explain why the recurrent failures. I'm frustated with my APC products but it may be a problem with this model. Just beware of the hidden costs of battery replacement when purchasing an UPS
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000093BD4:started_good_but_ended_bad:john_doe_"go_mavericks=p"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
488971
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000093BD4
</asin>
<product_name>
PNY 256 MB SD Secure Digital Flash Memory Card: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Started good but ended bad
</title>
<date>
June 7, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
John Doe "Go Mavericks=p"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Dallas ,Texas
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I had this card for more than 6 months, and It worked super in my Canon Powershot A510. Transfers went well too. Then all of a sudden for no reason I kept getting "card error" on my computer and digital camera a week ago. My SD/USB converter couldn't find the card either. I had really good photos I wanted to transfer to my computer and now they are probably lost for good. What a joke
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001IXUEY:also_disappointed:baby_sister
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
490919
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001IXUEY
</asin>
<product_name>
Panasonic RX-D29 CD / Radio / Cassette Boombox with MP3 CD Playback: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Also Disappointed
</title>
<date>
August 7, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Baby Sister
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Chi-town
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I purchased this Boombox over a year and a half ago.  What I do like about is that it was hard to find a boombox with a remote and Mp3 playback.  I agree that it could have been better.  It would be nice to be able to rewind from the first to the last.  You cannot rewind/fast forward in the song in Mp3 format but you can do it with a regular audio cd. sometimes I like to hear a certain portion of a song again, but I will have to play the entire song again. I no longer have the remote and there are some things that I cannot do anymore. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000DLB91A:not_exactly_match_fit_for_the_gen_2_nano:ethan_fatwoman_"beast_man"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
495754
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000DLB91A
</asin>
<product_name>
Belkin F8Z060 iPod Nano Silicon Sleeve (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
not exactly match fit for the gen 2 nano
</title>
<date>
November 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Ethan Fatwoman "beast man"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Francisco, CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This thing was slipping and sliding all over the place and I constantly had to readjust in so the functions were in place.  The slot on the top that is supposed to allow you to use the "hold" feature is completely off so you end up having to stretch the thing over to turn it on and off.  The little plastic protector that covers the screen would not stay in place over the screen and I was constantly losing it between the silicon cover and the ipod.  I finally just gave up on it and returned it.  I bought it because it is one of the only ipod accessories that has a fair price tag.  I think I'll just get it over with and buy one of the more expensive options.  Was this thing even meant for the Gen 2 nano
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00007KDVJ:bugs_in_firmware:g._hovden
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
504184
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00007KDVJ
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys WAP54G Wireless-G Access Point: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Bugs in firmware
</title>
<date>
October 14, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
G. Hovden
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
California
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The minor problem is that the user manual claims the user ID is "admin". Well, it is not. Frustration and wasted time will occur until you somehow find out that the user ID should be left blank to log in.

The major problem is that the unit only works for twelve to 36 hours before it has be rebooted. After twelve to 36 hours it looses the connection to the wireless network. Once you unplug and plug back the power cord, it will work fine for another twelve to 36 hours. I am used to rebooting Windows every time it hangs, but I don't accept having a Wireless Access Point that hangs (I am not sure how Microsoft was able to convince me it is OK for an OS to hang). This box is going back. I already bought a Buffalo that works fine
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000CO90OQ:worthless:d._davis
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
512416
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000CO90OQ
</asin>
<product_name>
2-Year Service Plan for Digital and Film Cameras $600 to $999.99: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Worthless
</title>
<date>
July 31, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
D. Davis
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I ordered the 2-year service plan on May 1st, this day (July 31st), I still have not recievied it. I have contacted them a number of times, and still nothing.  Do not buy from this company
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000CO90OQ:roll_the_dice,_this_one_is_a_gamble:r._goodrum
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
512417
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000CO90OQ
</asin>
<product_name>
2-Year Service Plan for Digital and Film Cameras $600 to $999.99: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Roll the dice, this one is a gamble
</title>
<date>
July 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
R. Goodrum
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Texas
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I purchased this item and one month later I still have not received any paperwork. I emailed and have not received a reply
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000658CH:waste_of_money:m._laad
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
512531
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000658CH
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys USBHUB4C ProConnect Compact USB 4-Port Hub: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Waste of money
</title>
<date>
September 29, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
M. Laad
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is a complete waste of money for a number of reasons.

1. This hub will not work with any USB powered devices. So forget being able to charge your phone or running an unpowered external disk through this hub.

2. Extremely slow USB 1.1. This device is NOT USB 2.0 compliant

3. It is clunky

4. Does not comke with a power adapte
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000658CH:not_usb_2.0:y._shuangchun
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
512534
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000658CH
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys USBHUB4C ProConnect Compact USB 4-Port Hub: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 11
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Not USB 2.0
</title>
<date>
May 21, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Y. Shuangchun
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
VA, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Wasted my money for this SLOW hub...
Be aware that if you want to connect your printer, scanner, ipod etc. to this device, think again
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000BZ40B:won't_fit_your_ipod_-__don't_bother_with_this_product:p._s.
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
513232
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000BZ40B
</asin>
<product_name>
DLO Action Jacket for 3G iPod Graphite: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
won't fit your ipod -  don't bother with this product
</title>
<date>
February 19, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
P. S.
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Connecticut USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
i purchased the DLO action jacket (neoprene for 20 and 40GB ipods) for my wife for use on walks, etc around town.  However, the ipod doesn't fit in properly.  The circle that is supposed to line up with the ipod's doesn't.  The plasic part covering the ipod is awkward and doesn't align either so you can't press the play button.  So, since the ipod doesn't fit in the case overall, this product is useless.  pls save your time and money and consider another ipod case
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006F2WD:print_heads_are_duds:jack__taylor
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
518066
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006F2WD
</asin>
<product_name>
Canon S530D Photo Printer: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
print heads are duds
</title>
<date>
August 19, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Jack  Taylor
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
which is why I bought the thing
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have had this printer for more than a year.  At first, it was a great printer. Not anymore!!  It uses up ink like no other, yes, it is great to have the individual tanks(which is why I bought the thing) but now the print head isn't working right.  Do several deep cleanings and use up nearly all the full tanks up, and the problem is still there.  The pages have splotchy black marks and the texts are only partially printed.  Went to the canon website, they don't even acknowledge this printer ever existed.
My recommendation is don't buy this model!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001NBHQ2:garbage:t._vanotterloo
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
520161
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001NBHQ2
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony ICF-CD855VSIL TV/Weather/FM/AM 4 Band CD Clock Radio: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
14 of 14
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Garbage
</title>
<date>
February 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
T. VanOtterloo
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I suffered with this clock for a year because it was a gift and expensive.  Even on the lowest setting the blue glow is so bright my finace says it looks like an alien spaceship is landing in the room.  The sound is so-so and it has no battery backup, lose power for a second and you have to reset everthing.  It is also very big, taking up 1/2 my nightstand.  The final straw was that it has trouble tuning in even the strongest radio stations where I live.  This morning I finally gave in, accepted reality and tossed it in the trash.  I won't miss it at all
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001NBHQ2:no_battery_back_up!!__:needbackup_"needbackup"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
520164
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001NBHQ2
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony ICF-CD855VSIL TV/Weather/FM/AM 4 Band CD Clock Radio: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
NO BATTERY BACK UP!!  
</title>
<date>
January 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
needbackup "needbackup"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
nc
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
We bought this clock radio, got it home, set it up, realized that it didn't have battery back up, called Sony only to find out that they do not find it necessary to put that feature on their alarm clocks....how bizarre!!  They do not carry battery back up on any of their new models according to their representative at the customer service center!  Boxed it up and it's going right back where it came from.  If it's okay not to have battery back up, it might deserve a chance, however, what's the use in having an alarm clock if you can't trust that it will indeed wake you up
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00007LTAU:rip-off:_doesn't_advertise_that_you_need_an_ac_adaptor:teacher_"teacher"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
520407
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00007LTAU
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus PA050U USB 2.0 High-Speed Hub (4-port): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 15
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
RIP-OFF: Doesn't advertise that you need an AC adaptor
</title>
<date>
February 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
teacher "teacher"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York, New York USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I would like to believe that this hub works well- but I wouldn't know.  I bought it to reduce clutter on my desk from all my devices hooking into my powermac.  I hooked up my printer, ipod and digital camera and nothing happened.  I called Targus and they said I needed an a/c adaptor.  It doesn't come with one and doesn't say anything about one in the manual or instructions, or their website.  They said I could get it at radio shack and gave me the info (5 volt, 2.1 amp, center positive).  I've been to two radio shacks and online- they don't carry it.  I'm upset.  Any advice
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007XH72E:sent_it_back:s._anderson
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
524365
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007XH72E
</asin>
<product_name>
JVC FSG5 180-Watt Micro Audio System with 5-Disc CD Changer and Digital AM/FM Tuner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
16 of 20
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Sent it back
</title>
<date>
October 2, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
S. Anderson
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New Hampshire USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I had to send this item back because it stopped playing cds. The sound quality was good, but the dependability of this item is questionable.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000AZ0582:sony_software_is_the_culprit:v._ananthanarayanan_"vj"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
527004
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000AZ0582
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony NW-E307 Walkman Bean 1 GB MP3 Player Black: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Sony Software is the Culprit
</title>
<date>
August 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
V. Ananthanarayanan "VJ"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
NJ USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Good thing first, efficient on battery,convenient and compact..doubles up as flash drive and no cables except headphone to carry around to charge. Thats it.

As most of the other reviewers have said this product is absolutely useless because of low IQ software people working in SONY. utterly non user friendly.
I develop software for a living and I am not afraid to use new software...even though I was able to use the software the main drawbacks are the over smartness of software where it tries to control the music piracy..
I had 1gb of Atrac songs on this player from my computer. Then one day my computer HDD crashed. I was kind of thankful that I had saved atleast 1 GB of music on this bean walkman. Atleast all the hours I spent in transfering did not go waste.
As soon as I fixed the new HDD and tried to transfer the songs back to my computer..the useless sony softwre will not take the music files back...I tried every trick and even the sony customer support could not help me( a very indifferent group of people). It is a rotten piece of software and that makes this efficient device a waste of money.

Of course transfering the files to this player is an entirely diff story and I dont want to go abt that..

It is absolutely infuriating
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00024VTKE:iriver_products_lack_plug_and_play_with_macs:donald_e._sandusky_"desco"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
527987
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00024VTKE
</asin>
<product_name>
iRiver iFP 799T 1 GB Flash MP3 Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Iriver products lack Plug and Play with Macs
</title>
<date>
August 13, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Donald E. Sandusky "Desco"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Charleston, SC United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have an Iriver T10 and there is virtually no software to support the USB plug and play interface that Mac owners have always expected.
Pay a little more and buy an IPOD.  It interfaces with PCs and Macs equally well.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00000JPPI:does_not_work_on_all_dvd_players:charles_truitt_parker
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
535606
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00000JPPI
</asin>
<product_name>
Maxell DVD-LC DVD Lens Cleaner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Does Not Work on ALL DVD Players
</title>
<date>
May 4, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Charles Truitt Parker
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Denver, Colorado
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
First of all, the shipping on this item costs more than the item itself.  I did get it quickly (2 or 3 days), but I had several problems with it:

(1) I repeatedly tried it on my DVD player and the player hung.  Each time I had to unplug it and plug it back in to get it to respond.  I tried over 10 times and got the same result each time.

(2) I tried it on DVD drive 1 on my computer and it hung as well.  Had to Ctrl-Alt-Del to get my DVD player software to close.  On the 3rd attempt it actually did work.

(3) I repeatedly tried it on DVD drive 2 on my computer. Each time I got a message saying "no disk".

I consider it item a waste of money
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000067VBM:joe_barone_big_buyer:joseph_barone
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
545136
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000067VBM
</asin>
<product_name>
50-pack Slim CD/DVD Jewel Cases (5mm) Clear: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Joe Barone Big Buyer
</title>
<date>
August 25, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Joseph Barone
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
NEW YORK USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
cases very cheaply made. Break when opening. Not worth shipping cost waste of money
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000067VBM:too_hard_to_open:nsc
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
545138
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000067VBM
</asin>
<product_name>
50-pack Slim CD/DVD Jewel Cases (5mm) Clear: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Too hard to open
</title>
<date>
January 7, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
NSC
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
It is difficult not to break them when first trying to open them.  On the flip side once they have been opened once, they don't reclose very well
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000A98AC:very_unreliable:jbat_"jbat"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
546813
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000A98AC
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 4x DVD+RW 25-Pack Spindle: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Very unreliable
</title>
<date>
July 31, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
jbat "jbat"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Fla
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Very unreliable .......... I have used DVD RW and CD RW Memorex disks on multiple computers and DVD recorders.  I find that they.....1) don't last....get about 50 re-recordings NOT 1500  2) may crap out on any occasion.......multiple CD RW's with critical material would NOT read on multiple computers.

AVOID MEMOREX DVD RW and  CD RW DISKS!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008EM7W:bad_compatibility:scott_baret
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
549030
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008EM7W
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex CD/DVD Compact LabelMaker System: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Bad Compatibility
</title>
<date>
October 14, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Scott Baret
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Pittsburgh, PA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have the older, larger version of this product. However, it uses the same software. The labels are great and the spring device that is used to apply the labels is great, but the software is awful. There is no direct Macintosh program; rather there are templates. They were written for old versions of software and really don't work right. The Windows side includes an actual Print Shop-style program which works awfully. If you do get this, make your own template on AppleWorks or PowerPoint
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008EM7W:it_does_not_work_with_macs:"cporro"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
549032
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008EM7W
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex CD/DVD Compact LabelMaker System: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
It Does not Work with Macs
</title>
<date>
January 10, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
"cporro"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York, NY USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
They totally misrepresent this product. It does not work with Macs. I feel cheated and lied to by Memorex, shame on you
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000CO77RI:service????:charles_p._cathcart
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
550694
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000CO77RI
</asin>
<product_name>
2-Year Service Plan for Personal Electronics $200 to $599.99: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
12 of 16
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
service????
</title>
<date>
November 3, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Charles P. Cathcart
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
CENTRAL PA.
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
after purchase they want the buyer to call for the service agreement.  of course you want a hard copy, that is why you bought it. just do it.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000CO77RI:n.e.w_sucks_big_time!:kidnice_1
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
550695
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000CO77RI
</asin>
<product_name>
2-Year Service Plan for Personal Electronics $200 to $599.99: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
296 of 297
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
N.E.W sucks big time!
</title>
<date>
June 5, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Kidnice_1
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
e.g. you dropped it, forget about it they aint gonna fix/replace it whatever.
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Okay,

This is not a review of the product itself. But, I strongly
encourage you to consider not getting an N.E.W warranty. They are
really not in the business to fix things but to make money not fixing things. 

If you had anything to do with the device not working (e.g. you dropped it, forget about it they aint gonna fix/replace it whatever.) 

They have a very sparce network of repair companies so if there is no one who can fix it in your area you have to ship it to them in Virginia(of course you have to pay for the shipping!)

Lastly, they tend to screw over their repair companies so in some cases they will refuse to repair items covered under an N.E.W warranty or they will take forever to repair it since they know N.E.W will take months to pay them for the work they did.

If you want a nightmare for a warranty then by all means go for it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000CO77RI:prepare_to_fight_every_step_of_the_way:l._gildart
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
550696
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000CO77RI
</asin>
<product_name>
2-Year Service Plan for Personal Electronics $200 to $599.99: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
273 of 273
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Prepare to fight every step of the way
</title>
<date>
May 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
L. Gildart
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Somerville, MA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
N.E.W. will waste your time, money, and your every last nerve before repairing your product.  Eventually they will, but not without an exhausting, protracted fight
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009V308:a_boom_box,_not_a_karaoke_machine:ari's_mom
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
552215
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009V308
</asin>
<product_name>
GPX C1625 CD+G Karaoke Party Machine: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
A boom box, not a karaoke machine
</title>
<date>
December 2, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Ari's Mom
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I'm not sure what I expected after I purchased this for fifty some-odd dollars and was handed a coupon for a $40 rebate.  But I wish that someone had informed me before I lugged it all the way home that when you sing into the mic, your voice doesn't come through the speaker.  I'm cool with the machine's sound quality when it comes to playing a CD-G.  If I tap the mic, I can hear an extremely faint thud, so I know it's on, but the volume's too low--and, yes, I adjusted the mic controls--if you want to sing along. Which makes this a dinosaur: a boom box in the age of the iPod.  

Really had to dig through the stacks of machines to find a box that hadn't been opened.  So, when was my first clue?  Doh
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005MIS8:inexpensive,_but_not_reliable:j._yan
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
553100
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005MIS8
</asin>
<product_name>
Viking CF512M 512 MB CompactFlash Card: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Inexpensive, but not reliable
</title>
<date>
May 30, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Yan
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Silicon Valley, CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I used to like my Viking 512MB CF card a lot.  I had such a card for more than a year.  In that period, I used it in my camera.  It's filled up for several times.  Also occationally I use a card reader (SimpleTech) to write/read that card, to transfer some big files between computers.  It's all fine, and suddenly one day, when the card was half full, and after a card reader reading, I got "CF card error" on my camera.  Fortunately, after I delete a few pictures, I could move on.  I gave the card to  other people, so I don't know how it's doing now.

After that, I purchased another Viking 512MB, half year ago.  I used it to transfer files for a few times, and have never filled it up using my camera yet.  Now I am getting consistent "CF card error" message on my camera, even after re-format for several times, while I don't have that problem if I use another card.  

One theory I heard was that a card reader may damage a card.  I can not verify though.  Anyway, I will have to buy another card now, and it won't be viking for this time.

===== One month later =====
I contacted with their customer support.  They gave me a number for return, and I mailed back my damaged CF card.  They sent back a new one in a week.  The new one is working fine so far.  The exchange was not difficult.  They did not ask for ridiculous things like my old receipt.  They only verified the serial number.  That's good
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000093IRC:coasters!:cool_jeff
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
554735
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000093IRC
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 4.7GB 4x DVD+R Media (25-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Coasters!
</title>
<date>
July 23, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Cool Jeff
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I wish they had a rating for zero stars.  I bought the fifty pack and had 12 good burns and 38 coasters.  That's a 24% success rate.  I subsequently bought verbatim data life and have burned 14 so far with no coasters.  Memorex has really gone downhill. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000093IRC:waste_of_money:c._ambrow_"renegade"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
554737
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000093IRC
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 4.7GB 4x DVD+R Media (25-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Waste Of Money
</title>
<date>
January 21, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
C. Ambrow "Renegade"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Tennessee
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought these discs at CompUSA because I needed a few before I got the ones I ordered online. Well, I just wated a good 25 bucks because out of 5 discs, I got one that burned good. Not much bang for the buck. I have burned many discs but never Memorex, usually Verbatim or Ridata or MAM. Very disgruntled with these discs making coasters. Maybe my burners don't like them but whatever the case, I won't buy them ever again. I thought Memorex made good products
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002CPBWI:great_while_it_lasted...:k._hossein
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
557841
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002CPBWI
</asin>
<product_name>
Microsoft Wireless Notebook Optical Mouse 3000 -Slate: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Great while it lasted...
</title>
<date>
November 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
K. Hossein
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York, NY
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this mouse eight months ago and was quite satisfied - until last week when it stopped functioning altogether.  I really expected a better product and durability from Microsoft.  I've since bought a Logitech VX Revolution Cordless Laser Mouse for Notebooks and love it.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000A5TN8U:small_but_deadly.:m._hoogland
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
561511
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000A5TN8U
</asin>
<product_name>
HP Deskjet 3930 Color Inkjet Printer (C9067A#B1H) Gray: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Small but deadly.
</title>
<date>
November 3, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
M. Hoogland
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Being a graduate student and living in an apartment, I was hoping to find a cheap printer that would allow me to print off course materials and assignments.  It prints off things quite well and it is fast.  It does not, however, print 500 pages per month.  50-100 pages per month is a more reasonable estimate and then the cartridges cost over $20, which is high considering how often you need to buy them.

The item did arrive in a timely fashion and it arrived in the specified condition. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00026KJ26:slooooooooow:matt_jones_"matomizer"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
563132
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00026KJ26
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar Media 32X 1 GB Secure Digital Card (SD1GB-32-231): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
slooooooooow
</title>
<date>
February 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Matt Jones "matomizer"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Orlando, FL
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This card is such a disappointment.  It is soooo sloooooow.  I use it for my digital camera, mp3 player, and ipaq.  It takes forever to copy anything to and from it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00026KJ26:worst_choice_of_my_life:yeppy_fan_"alan"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
563134
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00026KJ26
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar Media 32X 1 GB Secure Digital Card (SD1GB-32-231): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 21
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
worst choice of my life
</title>
<date>
March 6, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
yeppy Fan "alan"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
NY
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Bought this a month ago for use with my DX4330 kodak 3MP digital camera. It worked for 2 days.After that, everytime I on the camera, it wanted me to reformat the card,WTH is that?
Now I can't use it at all....
I'm always so confidence with my previous purchases from Amazon.One mistake I made,I threw away the shipping and product packages once I tested out the card, thought It worked and It would be OK.I can no longer return it now.
Needless to say,I'm too over confident with LEXAR's products.
Buyers beware...
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007SL4IW:dissapointing:linda_kennedy_"linofjt"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
567637
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007SL4IW
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex DVD+R 16x 4.7GB 100 Pack Spindle: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
dissapointing
</title>
<date>
October 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Linda Kennedy "linofjt"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Joshua Tree Ca
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I record dvd movies as a hobby and am always looking for better media, software etc.- I'd been using Ridata for some time w/ next to no coasters but figured I'd upgrade and go with memorex this time around. Big mistake. They skip, pixelate and freeze up. I have had to recopy at least 5 out of the last dozen or so movies I've done. Were it a compatibility issue I could understand, but it appears to be strictly a problem with the quality of the media. I'm going back to using my cheap disks! 
The lesson here is: " If it works, dont fix it!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009XSYZ:worthless!!!:brien_penn
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
570777
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009XSYZ
</asin>
<product_name>
ADS Technologies HDUP1500 HDTV Upconverter: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
18 of 20
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Worthless!!!
</title>
<date>
February 10, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Brien Penn
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Baltimore, MD
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought the ADS upconverter because I bought a HDTV only to find out that my cable co. didn't offer HDTV and after 3 failed attempts to switch to a satellite provider that did offer HDTV (too many trees around my house).  I wasn't expecting the upconverter to magically turn my standard signals into an amazing HDTV picture, but for $550+ I was expecting the upconverter to do something that was actually noticable.  When I first turned in on I asked my wife to look at the picture and tell me what she thought.  She looked at the TV and said okay I'm ready turn it on.  I said andquot;it IS ON!!andquot; This is pretty much the reaction I had also when I looked at it.  The image I got for my digital cable was certianly different, but that's all it was, different.  It was NOT noticably better.  In fact, in some instances I though the picture was worse.  I called ADS tech support and they kept insisting I try it with my DVD because that is what the product is best for (even though that's not what I got it for).  So I did and to be honest I really preferred the picture I got directly from my DVD over the picture I got after running it thru the upconverter.  It didn't matter what display format I put it in it just didn't do anything to improve the picture.  Save your money.  If you can't get HDTV don't expect this box to give you anything close to the next best thing
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000050AVT:compatibility_issues:joel_greenberg
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
577924
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000050AVT
</asin>
<product_name>
KB Gear Jam Studio: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Compatibility Issues
</title>
<date>
January 7, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Joel Greenberg
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Orange County, CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Cosmetically pleasing is about the only good thing you can say about this unit.  The included software does contain viruses.  The included software is a reminate of the late 80's to early 90's.  The tablet itself does not work under Win2000 nor WinXP.  Under 98 second edition it stops responding quite frequetly and you have to unplug and plug the unit back in to get it to respond again.  This unit would be great, if it came out 7 years ago.  You get what you pay for
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000050AVT:install_cd_has_viruses:nicole
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
577925
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000050AVT
</asin>
<product_name>
KB Gear Jam Studio: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Install CD has viruses
</title>
<date>
December 2, 2003
</date>
<reviewer>
Nicole
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Houston, TX
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I just recently bought this and when I installed it Norton caught 2 viruses on the install CD.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000093IRD:incredibly_inconsistent,_and_a_waste_for_me.:shopping_dude_"gary"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
579992
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000093IRD
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 4.7GB 4x DVD+R 4.7GB (50-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Incredibly inconsistent, and a waste for me.
</title>
<date>
February 16, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Shopping Dude "Gary"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Ohio
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Out of the past 20 burns, I have only had 10 DVD's burn successfully.  I use Roxio CD Creator version 7, which does a great job with my CD's, so I'm pretty sure it's the DVD media.  Not only am I wasting all my money, but my time as well.  I've tried to lower the burn speed, but it does not matter.  I'd try something else
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002A9SJ2:not_impressed...at_all._will_just_have_to_keep_buying_new_copies_until_something_better_comes_along!:ajax
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
582132
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002A9SJ2
</asin>
<product_name>
Aleratec DVD/CD Disc Repair Plus: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Not impressed...at all. Will just have to keep buying new copies until something better comes along!
</title>
<date>
May 19, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Ajax
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Kansas City, MO
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I ordered this on the recommendation of another Amazon customer. I wasnt impressed. I though this would save me money because until then I had been just buying new copies of my favorite CDs that were scrathced up. I cleaned a few discs and ran them through all three "processes" without successful results. It didnt seem to make much difference with any of my discs. I dont think this is a good "repairer" of any disc thats more than mildly scratched. My suggestion would be to just replace your damaged discs by buying another copy of your CD or DVD on AMAZON!! Many of my CDs I have replaced for $7-10 bucks on here. I wish I wouldve kept my $25
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001WV6ZU:decent_when_it_worked_right:hacad_"hank"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
583472
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001WV6ZU
</asin>
<product_name>
Panasonic DVD-F87K 5-Disc HD-Compatible DVD/CD Player (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Decent when it worked right
</title>
<date>
October 21, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Hacad "Hank"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
SF Bay Area
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Not sure if I just got a lemon or what but would never purchase this player again. It worked right most of the time, but found that at times it would confuse the change disc button with the eject button. I would have to turn the unit on and off to get it to "reset" and work correctly.  It's now about 9 months later and the unit decided it was time to stop working.
Bought it because it was cheap and I guess I got what I paid for. Fork out the extra cash and purchase another brand
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000A0AJH:what_happened_to_the_region_code_free_setting???_help!:valerie_c._feurich-sponsel_"val"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
584744
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000A0AJH
</asin>
<product_name>
CyberHome CH-DVD 300S Progressive-Scan DVD Player (Silver): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
What happened to the region code free setting??? HELP!
</title>
<date>
July 25, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Valerie C. Feurich-sponsel "Val"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Hi! I bought my Cyberhome 300 in April 2006, and was able to set the region code to "0" to watch all DVD's. 
After not using the DVD Player for a few weeks (and unplugging it), the region code has automatically set back to "1" and I cannot change it anymore! What happened?? When I try to change it now I can only choose between the settings "1" and "-". Anyone who has the same problem? Thank yo
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00004XRDM:dead_after_a_few_months:brian_morris
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
585671
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00004XRDM
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys L03040 Power 2GO Inverter - Car Cigarette Lighter Power Supply: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 12
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Dead after a few months
</title>
<date>
September 4, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Brian Morris
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Pittsburgh, PA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
As with some of the other reviewers, mine stopped working and blew the fuse in my car for the cigarette lighter.  I bought a Vector brand inverter at Wal-Mart and it is much better
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000A3WS8O:received_bad_service_:j._varela-carver_"jfc"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
593693
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000A3WS8O
</asin>
<product_name>
Apple 60 GB iPod video Black (5th Generation): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 16
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
RECEIVED BAD SERVICE 
</title>
<date>
November 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Varela-carver "JFC"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
LONDON, UK
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
AMAZON FAIL TO DELIVER ITEM WITHIN A REASONABLE TIME.  THE ITEM FAIL TO ARRIVE AND THEREFORE WE NEVER RECEIVED THE GOOD
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009WSWYA:not_good:schlebbs
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
594937
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009WSWYA
</asin>
<product_name>
Remanufactured Philips HTS3400/37B DVD Home Theater System: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Not Good
</title>
<date>
September 12, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
schlebbs
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
York, ME
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The sound was great, but the DVD would lag every 10-15 seconds during any and all movies.  It drove me nuts. I had to return it.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009WSWYA:sad!_because_i_have_to_keep_it_for_my_birthday!:g._tran_"batman"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
594938
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009WSWYA
</asin>
<product_name>
Remanufactured Philips HTS3400/37B DVD Home Theater System: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Sad! Because I have to keep it for my birthday!
</title>
<date>
September 4, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
G. tran "batman"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
NM
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This Philips HTS3400 DVD has all the features I need, but its mp3 player is really bad: Audio just pops before moving to a next song . It looks like what Philips' people just do in all of their electronics.  I really don't want to talk about this any more because William R. French and  A. Isaicu all talke about these problems
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002H7F3G:great_idea_--_bad_execution!:brandon_m._parise
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
600530
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002H7F3G
</asin>
<product_name>
Ideazon Zboard Gaming Keyboard: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
16 of 16
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Great Idea -- Bad Execution!
</title>
<date>
May 15, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Brandon M. Parise
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Mount Pleasant, SC
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The Good:
When I first heard about this board I was incredibly excited.  I have been playing BF2 (Battlefield 2) for almost a year now and still continually find myself stumbling over the keys. So it was a godsend to be able to purchase something like this directly intended to help me be better at my game. 

The interchangable keysets for different games and applications is quite intriguing -- the first that I have seen.  But the price for each is kind of high but well worth it.

The Bad:
The board is constructed well but don't expect this to replace your home keyboard.  The "Windows Keyset" that comes standard with this board has all the keys as any run-of-the-mill keyboard but it is awkward to type with (I might be biased since I have a MSoft ergonomic split keyboard). 

In-game typing is difficult at best (with the gaming keysets). With most of the gaming keysets the keys on the left 1/2 of the keyboard are laid out like your home keyboard but on the right 1/2 side they are all vertical (not staggered.. like U,J and M  keys are 90 degrees vertically on top of each other). The keys feel a little "cheap" .. When you push them down they don't bounce back as much.

The Ugly:
About 2 weeks after I purchases this board (and the BF2 keyset) 9 keys went completely dead.  I tried to reinstall the software, reboot and even resinstalled a fresh copy of Windows XP to no avail.

I contacted support and it has taken us 3 weeks to finally reach the decision that I have a faulty base unit. DUH!  They are "reviewing my warranty" but most likely it will not be covered because it has been longer than 30 day. Maybe this post is premature but I don't think I am getting a new base unit.

Conclusion:
The expression "Great Idea, Bad Execution" holds true here. My opinion: Don't buy this board. Ideazon has too many issues, not enough support staff and a website that doesn't do anything but look good
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000204SWE:good_product_but_only_lived_a_short_life_-_1_year:gorillaqueen
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
601200
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000204SWE
</asin>
<product_name>
Philips DVP642 DivX-Certified Progressive-Scan DVD Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
good product but only lived a short life - 1 year
</title>
<date>
November 22, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
gorillaqueen
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
It was a great product when it worked.  Sleek design, super user friendly, sharp image and easily unlock to all region.  Never had any problem loading or playing until last week.  Went completely dead for no reason in the middle of a movie.  Swallowed the DVD with it.  It would've been a greater product if it lived pass 1 year at least
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000204SWE:broke_in_less_than_a_year:john_w._lamb_jr._"editor,_hispanic_nashville_notebook"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
601201
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000204SWE
</asin>
<product_name>
Philips DVP642 DivX-Certified Progressive-Scan DVD Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Broke in less than a year
</title>
<date>
November 18, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
John W. Lamb Jr. "Editor, Hispanic Nashville Notebook"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Nashville, TN
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The player stopped working after only a few months - it would accept DVDs but not play them and refuse to eject them.  That behavior started out as intermittent, but it finally gave up the ghost and swallowed a DVD and never let go.  We had to take the player apart just to get the DVD out before throwing the player away in the trash.  Our previous DVD player lasted over 5 years before it started skipping.  This one lasted less than a year before it stopped working altogether - what a waste.  Save your time and money and buy another machine
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006B91Z:rip-off:_doesn't_advertise_that_you_need_an_ac_adaptor:teacher_"teacher"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
603932
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006B91Z
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus PA055U 4 Port USB 1.1 Ultra Mini Hub: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 15
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
RIP-OFF: Doesn't advertise that you need an AC adaptor
</title>
<date>
February 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
teacher "teacher"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York, New York USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I would like to believe that this hub works well- but I wouldn't know.  I bought it to reduce clutter on my desk from all my devices hooking into my powermac.  I hooked up my printer, ipod and digital camera and nothing happened.  I called Targus and they said I needed an a/c adaptor.  It doesn't come with one and doesn't say anything about one in the manual or instructions, or their website.  They said I could get it at radio shack and gave me the info (5 volt, 2.1 amp, center positive).  I've been to two radio shacks and online- they don't carry it.  I'm upset.  Any advice
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BNHPRC:i_need_more_power_scotty!:richard_d._moller_"rm_hm"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BNHPRC
</asin>
<product_name>
Aa Nimh Rechargeable Batteries Bulk Pack: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
I need more power scotty!
</title>
<date>
January 1, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Richard D. Moller "rm_hm"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Gig Harbor, WA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought these thinking they were a good deal but now I have to agree with some of the other reviewers. I bought 24 of these and one year later I have four left that will take any sort of charge. The ones that died maybe had six recharges on them each. I also have several high end chargers that don't want anything to do with the ones that died. On the bright side I have several Lenmar DLCRV3 batteries for my digital camera and they have been A+ after 2+ years
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BNHPRC:short_lifespan:p
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BNHPRC
</asin>
<product_name>
Aa Nimh Rechargeable Batteries Bulk Pack: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Short lifespan
</title>
<date>
November 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
P
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Honolulu, HI
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
O.k., I purchased these batteries over a year ago and only opened the pack now.  These batteries will not hold a charge and my charger indicates that the batteries are past their useful lives.  I don't know what the normal lifespan of rechargeable batteries is, but these didn't last being on the shelf for a little over a year.  I will never buy this brand again
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BNHPRC:ok_performance_but_can_be_dangerous:mark_twain
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BNHPRC
</asin>
<product_name>
Aa Nimh Rechargeable Batteries Bulk Pack: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
12 of 12
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
OK performance but can be dangerous
</title>
<date>
June 4, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Mark Twain
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
To be short, the performance is less than great but OK, but I can live with that since I have dozens of them, I don't care if it runs out faster. But what I couldn't stand if that it also set my charger on fire since one of them leaked, I couldn't imagine what would happen if I didn't come to my desk in time
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000HHOD5O:junk,_junk,_junk-stay_away:p._c._schaefer
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000HHOD5O
</asin>
<product_name>
Solio Universal Hybrid Solar Charger (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
JUNK, JUNK, JUNK-STAY AWAY
</title>
<date>
February 2, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
P. C. Schaefer
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this as a travel charger for my Blackberry. All I can say is awful, awful, awful. I followed instructions in the manual (which are pretty easy) and charged up the Solio. After waiting twice as long as required, I tried to plug it into my Blackberry 7250 to see how it charged--big mistake. Not only did it not charge a weird red "battery" icon came on in the upper left of the screen and then the blackberry promptly crashed.
I tried this routine several times over several days with the same result, rereading the manual so many times it was ridiculous. Finally, I had enough and told the customer service for Solio that I was returning it. Not only did they never return my money (I had to call my CC company to handle it) no one ever said what the problem could be.
My advice: Stay away from this thing--it may seen cool or environmentally friendly, but it is junk a piece of over-priced junk
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000FPLTRI:garbage:dutch
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000FPLTRI
</asin>
<product_name>
Belkin N1 Wireless Desktop Card ( F5D8001 ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Garbage
</title>
<date>
September 5, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
dutch
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Stafford, VA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
C. Musselman can add 2 more cards to his connector problem.  I have gone through 2 desktop cards that do not have proper fittings for the external antenna - I plan to return it all.  Avoid this product
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005I9RU:disappointed_in_sony:e._mangiaratti_"edman"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005I9RU
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony CDP-CE375 5-CD Changer: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Disappointed in Sony
</title>
<date>
December 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
E. Mangiaratti "EdMan"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Amherst, MA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Sound quality was fine but this CD changer doesnt work well at all. I am one of the buyers that had the same problems as many others with the CD changer. Tried to play shuffle with all discs and it just stops playing after a while. It also has problems just changing to the next sequential CD. Apparently Sony didn't do proper quality testing on this product. I returned mine and after these other reviews won't be replacing it with a Sony. I hope this is a message to Sony. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005I9RU:don't_buy_it_-_you'll_regret_it:k._detro
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005I9RU
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony CDP-CE375 5-CD Changer: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
23 of 24
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Don't Buy It - You'll Regret It
</title>
<date>
September 12, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
K. Detro
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Boise, ID United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
There are brands I trust and ones I don't.  Sony has always been a trusted brand.  But after buying and returning two of these units for very basic operationing flaws my confidence is shaken.  I should have read these other reviews before I made my purchase, but because this unit is a Sony I trusted it would be a superior product.  The problems I had in both units are the same ones mentioned by other reviews: When playing CDs in random mode the unit consistently fails to play all the songs before failing to load a CD and quitting.  I followed the advice of another reviewer and bought the ONKYO DX C390 6 disc changer.  I am hoping I have better luck.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008W2M5:not_worth_the_$40:john_duffy_"jjd"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008W2M5
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony SRF-H11 S2 Sports AM / FM Radio Walkman with Rear Reflector Headphones: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
18 of 19
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
not worth the $40
</title>
<date>
August 7, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
JOHN DUFFY "jjd"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
columbia sc
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I recently bought my second of these. The first had a digital tuner. You had to get used to the feel. After about a year of use, one earphone went out. The one I just bought has an analogue tuner, and it is extremely hard to get any station other than the very high-powered pop (and around here, country) stations. The tuner requires extremely small movements to move way up the dial. I can't believe Sony is charging $40.00 for this cheap piece of junk
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0006DOX04:looks_great_works_bad:amy_j._heflin
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0006DOX04
</asin>
<product_name>
Old Fashioned Snow Cone Maker: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Looks great works bad
</title>
<date>
February 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Amy J. Heflin
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this for my 4 kids who love the frozen drinks. But, I soon found that it does not work well. After a few uses the gears began to stick. It would no longer crush/shave ice. Stick with the smaller units
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002MK9IE:starry_eyed_over_this_one,_but_lets_me_down:k._montgomery_"mercedes307--contributing_author_for_highland_press's_second_time_around_anthology"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002MK9IE
</asin>
<product_name>
HP PhotoSmart 8450 Inkjet Printer: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Starry Eyed Over This One, But Lets Me Down
</title>
<date>
October 1, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
K. Montgomery "mercedes307--Contributing Author for Highland Press's Second Time Around Anthology"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Columbus, GA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Upon the joyful news that we were having a girl, my husband decided to invest in a new digital camera and a photo printer. The digital camera still works great--the printer is another matter. While this one prints beautiful pictures, the cost of ink far outweighs the beauty of them sometimes.

As we all know, this is how printer companies make their money, through the ink. Replacing every cartridge at once will run you about $75 at a time, give or take a few. The gray ink is used up the quickest, and has also been one of the hardest for us to find here locally. The main problem I have with this printer is that the quality is excellent after you replace the ink, but for only about the first 50-70 pictures. After that. The pictures take on too much of a magenta cast and start to get out of register--very frustrating when you're printing out any pictures, let alone ones of your child. Yes, we do what the manual sugests for such occasions, and the main one is to clean the printer cartridge heads, but this has only actually worked for us on one occassion. Every other time get us no results and we are still stuck with pictures that resemble something a third grader took a crayon to. In the long run, I will not be buying a photo printer for home use, but will rather take them to a store for processing. 

Quality-wise, it gets you in the beginning, but doesn't hold out for the long run. We have fiddled with it for two years. Enough's enough
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002MK9IE:hp_warranty_really_sucks_-_beware,_should_be_zero_stars_:david_davis
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002MK9IE
</asin>
<product_name>
HP PhotoSmart 8450 Inkjet Printer: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
27 of 34
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
HP Warranty Really Sucks - Beware, Should Be Zero Stars 
</title>
<date>
January 4, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
David Davis
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Jose, CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
My wife purchased an HP Photosmart 8450 Printer as a Christmas present for me. I installed it and it worked perfectly for one week. Then the colors started to change. Photos had extreme amount of yellow in them, such as yellow faces and hands, no proper flesh tones. 

I call HP support and was told that my printer was out of warranty because the warranty starts when the printer was manufactured, not the purchase date. I was offered one free call but my call was interrupted because of an appointment that I had. I was given a case number, but when I called HP back stating my case number, they said that this was no longer a free call. I explained it was an extension of the first call, but they refused to work with me.

I think HP warranty policy stinks, and would not purchase another HP product as long as this policy stands. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00029ZE2S:satisfactory_but_too_slow.:satish_seshadri
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00029ZE2S
</asin>
<product_name>
TiVo TCD540040 Series2 40-Hour Digital Video Recorder: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Satisfactory but too slow.
</title>
<date>
August 24, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Satish Seshadri
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Fanwood, NJ
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This DVR works ok.  But when it is recording, forget about changing channels.  It is really really slow and takes like forever to even receive any remote clicks. 
Broadband feature is nice; but USB doesn't come cheap. Its like [...].  
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009I95X6:no_buttons_-_big_hassle:mitchell_"tech_user"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009I95X6
</asin>
<product_name>
Bose Wave Radio II - Graphite Gray: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 13
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
No Buttons - Big Hassle
</title>
<date>
April 8, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Mitchell "Tech user"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Kentucky
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
A clock radio that you have to fumble for a remote to use....I don't think so.  I have the older models (CD and Clock Radio) and they are nice but the new model is irritating. 

 I also have the IPOD player and at least the volume controls are on the system.  I can't keep a system that I have to locate a remote to operate.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000069DOV:poor_distant_transm_ition:william_morris_hembree_"wmh"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000069DOV
</asin>
<product_name>
Cobra HH Road Trip Hand Held CB Radio: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
POOR DISTANT TRANSM ITION
</title>
<date>
June 4, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
William Morris Hembree "WMH"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
MURPHY, NC
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
JUNE 04,2006
I PURCHASED THIS RADIO FOR EMERGENCY PURPOSES, HOWEVER IT SEEMS TO BE VERY WEEK. I AM A DOUBLE AMPUTEE AND AM CONFINED TO A WHEEL CHAIR. I DEPEND ON MY RADIO TO RAISE HELP. BUT, I AM AFRAID THIS ONE WILL NOT BE DEPENDABLE. I AM NOT ASKING FOR THEM TO BE RETURNED OR FOR A REFUND JUST LETTING YOU AND YOUR CUSTOMERS KNOW OF A VERY WEAK PRODUCT AND I COULD NOT RECCOMEND THIS PRODUCT TO ANYONE. COBRA WAS THE TOPS IN RADIOS BUT SOMETHING HAS HAPPENED TO THE QUALITY.
THANK YOU FOR LISTENING;

WILLIAM HEMBREE
 WmHembree@aol.com
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00081A2UY:belt_clip_ripped_off:margaret_a._burnett
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00081A2UY
</asin>
<product_name>
Apple M9940G/A iPod Photo Carrying Case with Belt Clip: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
14 of 16
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Belt clip ripped off
</title>
<date>
August 26, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Margaret A. Burnett
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Seattle, WA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This carrying case worked well for me until I jumped in my car and the case caught on the door frame and the belt clip ripped right off of it, causing my iPod to fall to the pavement.  It turns out the clip isn't fastened on all that securely
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002VRP8C:what_did_i_expect...:j._clifton
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002VRP8C
</asin>
<product_name>
Griffin Technology GarageBand Guitar Cable 3101-GTR: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
What did I expect...
</title>
<date>
May 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Clifton
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Atlanta, GA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
for $20 bucks...After finally figuring out that I had to turn my mic inputs ALL the way up, I still can't get more than a -20db signal from my guitar...Save your money..
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000V8XHG:didn't_work_for_dell_700m:chih_chen_ku
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000V8XHG
</asin>
<product_name>
Kingston Technology PC2700 1GB ValuRAM CL2.5 SODIMM Memory ( KVR333X64SC25/1G ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
didn't work for dell 700m
</title>
<date>
November 30, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Chih Chen Ku
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Costa Rica
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought one of these modules for my dell 700m. Installed it easily but once every few days my system crashes or I get a blue screen. I contacted kingston and they said that this module hasn't been tested on dell machines and is configured to work on generic computers only! I wouldn't recommend this memory for dell 700m users. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008I9K9:do_not_buy:robert_poulton_"rob"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008I9K9
</asin>
<product_name>
Netgear WG602 54 Mbps G Access Point: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
DO NOT BUY
</title>
<date>
February 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Robert Poulton "rob"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Canada
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I wish I had read the problems and netgear.com forums before purchasing this product.

Huge flaw in this product requires that it be restarted daily. This requires you unplug and plug back in the AP in order for it to stay visable to your computers.

Second problem I am noticing is that the 54mbps speeds are very rare, and even at 3-5feet from the AP the unit is around 11-36mpbs.

Do not buy this product, find another company who stands behind there products. All of my contacts with them have landed me somewhere in India. People on the phone dont know how to help you and email support is a joke. Latest firmware fixes none of the problems
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002ZAEYA:terrible!_don't_waste_your_money.:s._kuipers
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002ZAEYA
</asin>
<product_name>
PalmOne Zire 72 Special Edition Handheld Silver: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Terrible! Don't waste your money.
</title>
<date>
September 7, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
S. Kuipers
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Carlos, CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought the Zire 72s as an upgrade to my previous black and white Palm that I had no problems with. It has been nothing but a lemon since I got it. Often when I turn it on it has lines going across the screen and has to be turned off and then on again to get rid of them. The graffiti is terrible and rarely works. I have to reset it all the time. Customer support is terrible and did nothing to rectify the problems. I even sent it to them at one point and they sent it back in exactly the same condition I sent it to them. I don't think they even looked at it. After my experience with this Palm, I will never buy Palm again
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EG5UAA:what_a_piece_of_crap:t._begley_"mother_of_disappointed_child"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EG5UAA
</asin>
<product_name>
Nextar MA933A-2B 256 MB Digital MP3 Player (Blue): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
What a piece of crap
</title>
<date>
January 28, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
T. Begley "mother of disappointed child"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Colorado Springs, CO
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This thing worked for two days and then started cutting off songs and starting them over.  We thought it was the battery going bad but a new battery didn't help.  Don't buy this item.  I am not even going to bother getting it replaced after reading the other reviews here
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000E658Q:poor_quality_control:j._a._white
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000E658Q
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys WPS54GU2 Wireless-G Print Server for USB 2.0: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
poor quality control
</title>
<date>
December 29, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. A. White
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have had various WiFi networking solutions in my home and office for several years.  While some Linksys units have worked for me, more often I have found them undependable.  In particular, the WPS54GU2 set up fine, but I almost always had to cycle the power to get it to work each time I printed.  Not worth the hassle
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000AY7A5O:do_not_buy_this_junk!!!:kevin_kauss_nguyen
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000AY7A5O
</asin>
<product_name>
LaCie 250GB d2 External Hard Drive Extreme  USB 2.0 and FireWire 400/800 Interfaces (300790U): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
DO NOT BUY THIS JUNK!!!
</title>
<date>
December 26, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Kevin Kauss Nguyen
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Huntington Beach, CA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
My drive FAIL after one year and a half...!!! This company really suck BIG TIME....I lost all of my data ...!!! ALL OFF IT...!!! THIS IS THE THIRD ONE THAT FAIL OUT OF FOUR OF THEM I PURCHASED LAST YEAR!!!  Total JUNK...!!! NEVER buy a LACIE AGAIN FOR SURE....MAXTOR EXTERNAL IS THE BEST!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000G2BGFK:beware:josh_stone
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000G2BGFK
</asin>
<product_name>
Western Digital My Book Pro Edition 500 GB External Hard Drive with Triple Interface: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Beware
</title>
<date>
March 22, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Josh Stone
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this HD because my Lacie (which had lasted over 5 years) crashed on me finally. So I figured I would try a different company. Out of the box this  product looked great, although it was very large and heavy. I immediately plugged it in to test it and it came up - however that was the one and only time that it booted. I tried several more times and it wouldn't boot up. VERY VERY scary when you buy a new device to hold all you important data and it won't boot up out of the box. I don't know if this product just happened to be the one that sucked - but I am not taking any chance on a defective HD and my data. Going back to Lacie
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00001W0DT:does_this_work_with_desktop_pcs?:seshadri_g
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00001W0DT
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony ECMMS907 Digital Recording Microphone: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
does this work with desktop pcs?
</title>
<date>
November 22, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Seshadri G
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
India
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I purchased this and shipped to US and finally had it delivered to India in gurgaon. Iam a musician and I desperately wanted a good microphone. I record my violin pieces on my laptop and used an ordinary computer mike for this. But I wanted a more sensitive recording and couldnt believe the dismal output of this mike. The gain was lower than the ordinary mike, it doesnt work at all without the battery, but the sound is tiny and totally unsatisfactory. Unfortunately sony doesnt have good service centres who'll entertain me in delhi and I consider 70 bucks down the drain. :andlt;..
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002ICGDY:does_not_work_on_vista:l._coleman
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002ICGDY
</asin>
<product_name>
TURTLE BEACH Audio Advantage Micro: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
DOES NOT WORK ON VISTA
</title>
<date>
February 13, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
L. Coleman
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Orange Beach, AL United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
DOES NOT WORK ON VISTA.  SOOOOO disappointed because my laptop sound completely disappeared with Vista upgrade (save for the Windows startup music).  I thought this new sound card would bring my sounds back.  Might have, but it says not compatible with Vista.  I guess I'll be getting a new computer.  :
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000CGCCM:what_do_you_think?_its_awful:shelly_mitchell_"cool_boy"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000CGCCM
</asin>
<product_name>
Casio TV-980 2.3" Portable Color TV: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
what do you think? its awful
</title>
<date>
May 31, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Shelly Mitchell "cool boy"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Seattle, WA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
are you serious?  I bought this a while ago to see if it was cool. It is a piece of junk, u can barely get any channels, and even if you do, you can barely see them and it has loud static.  dont buy it its garbage
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000CGCCM:don't_waste_your_money_and_time:john2006
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000CGCCM
</asin>
<product_name>
Casio TV-980 2.3" Portable Color TV: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
don't waste your money and time
</title>
<date>
April 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
John2006
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Michigan
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The screen is too small. if you want to watch it in your car, you have to cover it because the back light is too week.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000A2AGZC:check_compatability:michael_e.dorsey
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000A2AGZC
</asin>
<product_name>
Articulating LCD Wall Arm for 22IN-37IN LCD Screens - Silver: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Check compatability
</title>
<date>
November 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Michael E.Dorsey
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Lancaster county,Pa.
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The item was not difficult to install but the adaptor plate did not fit my tv so I called peerless customer service and they had one sent to me but that cost me another 40 bucks. I was disappointed it was NOT as universal as advertised. once I got the tv up it is ok, and getting the tv up to it is a 3 person job and it takes two to lift it up as it should  for safety reasons but a 3rd person needs to hold the arm steady. I did find out there is another one that could have fit without having to spend the extra 40 bucks. I had to return the first tv to the store and round up help when I got a replacement. Now it looks like I may need to do that again as the replacement tv has problems also.This whole thing with the mount and tv has been very frustrating.
Mike D. live and learn
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007M0VWS:worst_media_ever_--_made_by_cmc_magnetics!:gern_blanston
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007M0VWS
</asin>
<product_name>
Verbatim CD-R 80MIN 700MB 52X LightScribe (30pk Spindle Box): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Worst Media Ever -- Made by CMC Magnetics!
</title>
<date>
January 13, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Gern Blanston
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Grand Rapids, MI
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
These Verbatim discs are hands down the very WORST blank media I've EVER encountered! They're made by CMC Magnetics -- well known as the worst media manufacturer in the world. But not only are they CMC Magnetics, they're the worst of the worst of CMC Magnetics!

The latest KProbe *hangs* when faced with these, forcing a hard reset. The latest Nero Burning ROM *hangs* when faced with these, forcing a hard reset. The program continues, non-stop, to display "waiting for media" when I use these, and an attempt to abort hangs Windows XP SP2 the same way it hangs Kprobe.

Curiously, the media IDs on these are exactly the same as that on Philips LightScribe CD-R media (they're made by CMC Magnetics as well). However, at least the Philips are recognized by all my software and hardware, quite unlike the Verbatims. That's why I say that these Verbatim are the worst of the worst from CMC Magnetics. (The Philips are no prize, either, but they perform minimally well).

The *ONLY* thing that worked with these media are the LightScribe labeling.  But what's the point of labeling discs you can't even RECOGNIZE, let alone burn?

I had the exact same problems with these media in both my Lite-On LH-201AH burner and my NEC ND-2510A burner (the latter is universally recognized as and ideal burner for even low-quality media).

Note that Verbatim had a great reputation when they sold media manufactured by Taiyo Yuden. But, stupidly, they chose to go ultra-cheap and turned to the dreaded CMC Magnetics Corp. Thus, they lost all credibility!

*AVOID THESE LIKE THE PLAGUE!*
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000HZD2YE:not_sure_about_the_durability:smacco_"glenn_w"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000HZD2YE
</asin>
<product_name>
Western Digital 80 GB USB 2.0 Passport 2.5" External Hard Drive ( WDXMS800TN ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Not sure about the durability
</title>
<date>
April 20, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Smacco "Glenn W"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
St. Louis, MO United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
YMMV, but my 80GB drive died after 6 months.  I found this be very handy to have around to transfer large files between work and home, but I expected it to last longer than 6 months given that it was well taken care of.  I'm glad I back up my data in more than one place
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002W5QXW:very_disappointing_product:kai_zhang
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002W5QXW
</asin>
<product_name>
Planon DocuPen DPEN-R700 Rechargeable Handheld Pen Scanner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
22 of 23
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Very Disappointing Product
</title>
<date>
July 11, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Kai Zhang
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York, NY
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This product looks and feels very flimsy. Do not be fooled by the flashy, metallic-looking picture. The plastic shell of this device is the quality of McDonald's toys. One would think that for $300, the company would at least commission a manufacturer that did not leave plastic whiskers hanging off the rims due to bad cutting. 

The buttons are hard to press. In order to turn the device on, you have to press very firmly, which is a risky thing to do considering the cracking delicacy of the shell.

The cable port for the DocuPen is also extremely flimsy, and you have to hold the cable firmly in place in order for the downloads  to take place; otherwise, the connection will be lost. 

I am a pre-medical student, and I very stupidly invested a lot of money in this product, believing that I could (for 8 seconds a page and 100 pages per disk) scan my science textbooks in the library, including the colored diagrams, and in that way, I thought I would make back my investment, since textbooks go for at least $100 each. However, I now see that this belief was naive, to say the least. The Docupen is extremely difficult to use. The words come out distorted, like a jammed fax machine, and although the free Paper Port software which comes complimentary with the DocuPen is rather useful for annotating PDF's, the DocuPen does not produce texts that are legible enough to annotate.

Furthermore, downloading is very slow (at least 15 seconds per page on my fast computer), and since you can't see how your scans have turned out until you load them into the computer, you will have to re-scan about 80% of pages due to stretches, smudges, blurriness, suspicious blank spots, and general illegibility.

I wish I had read some of the other negative Amazon reviews before buying this product. I would have saved myself a lot of money and time.

If you are a user who is only looking to scan pictures or a few flat documents, then this product may work okay for you, although a digital camera will probably deliver better results. If you have been harboring grandiose visions of going all-out "paperless" with this product, you will find yourself extremely disappointed. 

Until PlanOn decides that this product is worthy enough to invest in a semi-decent shell manufacturuer, it will not a good buy. The idea is wonderful and has a lot of potential, especially when coupled with a Tablet PC. However, the execution of the idea needs improvement. I hope to see a far better version of this product in the next few years, at a price that is comparable to quality.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00016UVHU:memorex_software_good_(or_bad?)_for_your_neck_muscles:rc
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00016UVHU
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex DVD Case Inserts (White Matte, 25-Pack): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
11 of 11
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Memorex software good (or bad?) for your neck muscles
</title>
<date>
February 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
rc
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Maryland, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This product is a sad joke.  It's expensive of course.  The paper is just heavyweight paper that's perforated so you can bend it and break out the inserts themselves... which takes some effort (not sure if it'd be quicker just getting heavyweight paper and using a paper cutting board).  But, whatever.  

However, the software is crap.  That's the appropriate term.  Reading this I can save you an hour of your precious time.  No you can't make the template show right-side up.  That's right... to use the software you have to TILT YOUR HEAD SIDEWAYS.  I'm not kidding!  I guess you could also turn your monitor on it's side.  You can rotate the text so it shows the way it should.  But when you edit it, it'll be sideways again.  So you'll have to turn your head (or monitor) back and forth sideways.  What kind of company would sell such a product? 

And oh yeah... if you're looking for templates for the DVD Inserts?  ... nada.  They're not there! 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000E4778U:does_not_fit_the_new_80_gb_ipod_video:joy_banerjee_"indoloony"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000E4778U
</asin>
<product_name>
XtremeMac IPV-SPW-00 SportWrap for iPod Video - Black: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Does not fit the new 80 GB Ipod Video
</title>
<date>
December 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Joy Banerjee "indoloony"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
State College, PA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
FYI: This does not fit the new generation 5.5 of ipods (80 GB). Another thing is that there isn't a hole for the headphone jack which is rather odd
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001JXAUW:be_very_careful:joltar
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001JXAUW
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus APD10US Mobile 70 Universal Auto/Air Adapter: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Be very careful
</title>
<date>
January 26, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Joltar
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Petaluma, CA, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I was (wrongly) advised by tech support to buy this instead of waiting for a new supply of power supplies from Voodoo.  Be sure your computer is supported, because Targus tech won't give you any info about voltage , amperage or wattage on this thing, so you can't safely maake it work with an unsupported computer.   So Amazon, As usual, graciously took it back.  Love Amazon.  I just now read the other reviews and now consider myself lucky I didn't keep it and try to make it work
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000051299:noisy_blower:veets
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000051299
</asin>
<product_name>
Antec Cyclone Blower Case Fan for Any Expansion Slot: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Noisy Blower
</title>
<date>
January 9, 2002
</date>
<reviewer>
Veets
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Chicago, IL
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
After about 3 weeks of operation, the fan clicks and buzzes like crazy.  Looking for a better option
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009RML8S:don't_buy_this_product!:j._elliott
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009RML8S
</asin>
<product_name>
Netgear SC101 Storage Central: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Don't buy this product!
</title>
<date>
February 25, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Elliott
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this product as a way to keep a large amount of backup data saved, however I have fought with the drivers for days now. Whenever the drive is working the usb on my computer does not work, if I try to use multiple computers on the same drives it crashes (even with the newest updates) I will be returning this product ASAP. I'm very disappointed and will not be buy netgear again! 

I only wish there was a 0 star revie
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009RML8S:not_for_the_faint_of_heart.__better_products_out_there,_skip_this_one:j._sigler_"jonbarter"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009RML8S
</asin>
<product_name>
Netgear SC101 Storage Central: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Not for the faint of heart.  Better products out there, skip this one
</title>
<date>
February 21, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Sigler "jonbarter"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Connecticut
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This was my second Netgear product I bought (previously a wireless modem which I was only okay with not impressed)  The idea of a network storage appeals to me.  But this drive just is not good.  
 
In reading the previous reviews I found that it was a finicky thing, and be careful on the drives you buy for it.  Well I searched and searched and found a drive that worked and bought both yesterday. 
 
Tried to set it up today and connecting the drive went pretty well, but that is where everything started to go down hill.  Midway through the install it tells you to okay any error messages (which turn out to be things like this is untested on XP and might not work kind of errors) and suddenly my computer reboots.  Figured it would have told me it was going to do so oh well, and it never goes back to the install like most programs do when they require a reboot.  Tried again, same thing happens.  Started poking around and find out that not only do you have to check the drive you put in to the SC101, you need to look in to your own computer.  To quote Netgears web site, "SCSI disk drivers from the Promise company conflict with the SC101 device drivers. Promise drivers are typically used for RAID 1 or for SATA drives. Many newer computers use Promise SATA drivers."

My computer is just a week old and has these newer drivers.  Back in the box the SC101 goes, and I try to uninstall the software as this product will not work for me.  Tried the 3 things when you have trouble it suggests, and none work.  This is where I get really frustrated, Netgear support.  I waited 35 minutes for someone to pick up the phone, who ultimately told me it was my own fault and I'd have to pay to have that "cr*p", yes he said it, from my system.  I needed to hire a local computer vendor and it would be my bill.  I have to pay to get this junk off my computer.  Way to support your products Netgear.  The tech support person who got on the phone had an accent that was hard to understand, and went through huge mood swings during the call, from happy, to argumentative, to depressed, to happy again.  I was freaked that this person knew my home address!
 
All in all, this is a great concept.  After reading up on it and now experiencing it, I think it needs a ton more engineering and refinement before it is brought to market.  Maybe by a company with better customer service.  It really requires a level of technical expertise that is not there with the average consumer
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009GWX46:not_as_expected:paul_m._farber
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009GWX46
</asin>
<product_name>
Motorola Talkabout FV200AA GMRS / FRS Two-way Radio (Pair): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
12 of 14
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Not as Expected
</title>
<date>
March 22, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Paul M. Farber
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Needham, MA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Range is very weak probably less than half a mile. Don't waste your money
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007Z4XUQ:2_flaws_in_excel:j._kim_"amazon_fiend"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007Z4XUQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Logitech V250 Cordless Mouse/number Pad: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
2 Flaws in Excel
</title>
<date>
January 18, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Kim "Amazon fiend"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York, NY United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
everything works fine except for two flaws in Excel: on the numpad, the minus key actually toggles shift and the slash key acts as the alt key.  this is unacceptable, i had a logitech keyboard also with all sorts of annoying little flaws which surfaced when playing games.  logitech has some great ideas and sleek looking products, but they are plagued with small yet crucial technical shortcomings.  i will never buy logitech again
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009MFPZ4:don't_buy_this_product:david_p._pollak
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009MFPZ4
</asin>
<product_name>
Boston Acoustics Receptor HD Clock Radio (Platinum): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Don't buy this product
</title>
<date>
February 7, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
David P. Pollak
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I live in San Francisco and have generally good radio reception.  This unit could not receive normal FM stations that table radios sitting right next to it could pick up... and I used the fancy "Dipole" antenna on the Boston Accoustics unit and the other table radios only had an internal antenna.

The HD part of the radio is total junk.  Sometimes the audio "skips" and sometimes the signal is lost and reacquired (meaning 3 or 4 second drop-outs.)

All in all, there's nothing good about this radio.  Don't buy it.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009MFPZ4:comparing_recepter_radio_hd_with_sangean_hdr-1:james_j._flannery_"k0unx,_jim_flannery"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009MFPZ4
</asin>
<product_name>
Boston Acoustics Receptor HD Clock Radio (Platinum): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
15 of 16
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Comparing Recepter Radio HD with Sangean HDR-1
</title>
<date>
January 12, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
James J. Flannery "K0UNX, Jim Flannery"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Littleton, Co United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
de K0UNX.  I know radios.

I purchased the Recepter Radio HD a year ago, used it for a weekend and returned it immediately.  Even in the Denver market, with lots of very strong HD signals, this radio had trouble finding them.  I'd be listening to a strong station, and the radio would lose lock, go silent, and rebuffer before coming back to life.  This was one of the few HD radios available when I bought it.  I have since purchased a Sangean HDR-1 and love it.  Read my review under the Sangean HDR-1
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007UVRVO:doesn't_work_on_windows_vista!:s._wood
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007UVRVO
</asin>
<product_name>
Wyse USB to Parallel Converter Cable - Parallel adapter - USB - parallel: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Doesn't work on Windows Vista!
</title>
<date>
March 20, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
S. Wood
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Cincinnati, OH USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Tried this with two different computers using Windows Vista.  Got this message: "One of the USB devices attached to this computer has malfunctioned, and Windows does not recognize it."  The mini-disk that came with it was no help.  No response from Tiger Direct.  Went to Radio Shack and got one.  It works
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007UVRVO:not_working:s._kim
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007UVRVO
</asin>
<product_name>
Wyse USB to Parallel Converter Cable - Parallel adapter - USB - parallel: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
not working
</title>
<date>
March 19, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
S. Kim
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New Haven, CT USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
After one successful printing it didn't work at all. My printer is HP deskjet 712C. This cable seemed to be recognized correctly at first but kept from being connected
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006I62X:like_resting_your_feet_on_a_small_mountain_of_plastic_trash:xane_grey
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006I62X
</asin>
<product_name>
Fellowes Standard Foot Rest: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
9 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Like resting your feet on a small mountain of plastic trash
</title>
<date>
October 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Xane Grey
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Satsuma, TX
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
What more can I say than the above?  It is flimsy, doesn't stay in adjustment, rattles around when you move, and looks cheap to boot.  Don't waste your money, this thing is junk. It would be more appropriately priced at $5.00.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006I62X:not_smooth_and_feels_cheap_(is_cheap).__:mike_calhoun
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006I62X
</asin>
<product_name>
Fellowes Standard Foot Rest: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
9 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Not smooth and feels cheap (is cheap).  
</title>
<date>
June 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Mike Calhoun
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Seattle, WA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Tilting the foot rest back and forth is not the easiest thing in the world.  It's just cheap plastic rubbing on cheap plastic so it sticks a lot.  Mine broke in 2 different spots within a month..
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002Y7DO0:it_will_let_you_down:j._thomas
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002Y7DO0
</asin>
<product_name>
PalmOne Tungsten T5 Handheld: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
It will let you down
</title>
<date>
March 18, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Thomas
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Nashville, TN USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
There are many aspects of the T5 people want to count as negatives. For me I consider them annoyances but not killers. I would like to have WiFi with my PDA but I am not dead with out it. More memory is always good but the T5 isn't on the hurting side. It's not a good mp3 player with the memory it has. And even if you have a 2G card with mp3's it's not like this is what you would buy for MP3s. But as far as contact information, on the go applications etc.. I would consider this as good as any other. The problem as I have just found out is these are known to die. I haven't heard of this issue till it happened to me but it seems the T5 will at some point Die. It will lock up and even after all the resets listed from Palm it will not come back to even a factory state. You will have a Palm Powered logo screen with a small black line flashing on the top. 

There are a couple of fixes. If you are under warranty you can send it back to Palm for them to make it better. Or you can remove the battery and solder it back. This is a serious design issue that Palm is more than happy to charge you for.

Until I ran into this I would have rated this a 4/5. Until this happened the device did what I expected it to do. I read the box before buying it and knew it had some lack of cool factor with the no WiFi. But it has one of the fastest processors (available at that time) in a PDA. Which was a different type of cool. The bluetooth
works well enough I haven't had any issues with it. You can surf the net with bluetooth so wifi isn't really that big of a deal.

But if you can't trust your device is going to be working the next day it really 
doesn't matter what cool feature it has. This has been a very expensive let down.
I don't want to buy another Palm after this experience but I am not sure what to
switch to...
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002Y7DO0:poor_reliability:ceng_"ceng"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002Y7DO0
</asin>
<product_name>
PalmOne Tungsten T5 Handheld: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
poor reliability
</title>
<date>
September 8, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Ceng "Ceng"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Maryland
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
First T5 lasted 6 months, then just refused to start - was replaced under warranty. This one locked up after about 3 months - was replaced again under warranty. The third T5 lasted about 5 months. It's now out of warranty and won't start or reset. No - I'm not rough on my PDAs. None of them got even as much as a scratch. Each one looked like new when it "broke". The first 2 times, Palm told me the ROM had failed. I guess it's the same problem again, but I'm not spending $169 to get it swapped for another faulty T5. Good bye Palm.

Out of the box I think it's a good PDA, so check those 4 and 5 star reviews to see how long the users have had their PDAs before you buy
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EVSXMC:decent_sound_but_zero_comfort:g._rummell
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EVSXMC
</asin>
<product_name>
Pc Headset Binaural Nc Multimedia with mute/vol Ctrl: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
decent sound but zero comfort
</title>
<date>
January 26, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
G. Rummell
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this headset from retailer (offline), and returned it the next day. First off, I have to make it clear that I had NO problems with sound. Even though the speakers could have been just a tiny bit bigger (they use 40mm drivers), the sound quality of the headset was just fine.

However, when it comes to wearing these headphones, the only words that come to mind are "uncomfortable as sin". The awkward squarish shape of the cups made it hard to get any kind of decent seal around the ears (and a bad seal on closed-back headphones ultimately leads to poor sound isolation). Also, I have no idea what material they used for the cup pads, but it is nowhere near soft enough... in fact, I litterally couldn't wear these things for more than five minutes without my ears turning red (flush) from discomfort. Mind you, I also own a cheap pair of Koss headphones I can keep on for hours at a time, so my ears are definitely no stranger to being cupped in speakers either... but these things, they just plain hurt to wear after a very short period of time, which isn't good at all. Discomfort and being unable to obtain a good seal around the ears were ultimately the main reasons for the return. 

If your ears are tough, you should have no problem with this headset. The sound quality is decent and it should work just fine for you. However, if you're looking for comfort and good sound isolation, you'll want to look elsewhere..
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EVSXMC:no_front/rear_sound.:willywonka
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EVSXMC
</asin>
<product_name>
Pc Headset Binaural Nc Multimedia with mute/vol Ctrl: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
No front/rear sound.
</title>
<date>
December 31, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
willywonka
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I dont recommend these for 1st person shooter gamers.
Impossible to tell if enemy is in front or behind you.
Probably ok if direction of sound is not important to you.
Left and right work ok but not front/rear for some reason.
My hp laptop earbuds work better
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006HOL1:static_producer:dee_"adees"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006HOL1
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony AC-E45A Worldwide AC Power Adaptor with Folding Plug Blade: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
STATIC PRODUCER
</title>
<date>
May 21, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
dee "adees"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Clemente, CA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The use of this AC power adaptor has increased the amount of static to the point where using the radio with the adaptor is pointless. On battery the radio works very well, just attach the adaptor and all reception is lost.

Invest in batteries rather than this product.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0006A7X2W:card_didn't_work_-_poor_customer_service:siddharth_jain
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0006A7X2W
</asin>
<product_name>
Belkin F5D8010 Wireless Pre-N 802.11x Pre-N Notebook PC Card Adapter: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
card didn't work - poor customer service
</title>
<date>
April 16, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Siddharth Jain
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this card and the Belkin Pre-N wireless router in Nov. 2006 at a BestBuy store during Thanksgiving sale. The router worked but the card did not. I called Belkin many times. Everytime they asked me to re-install the drivers and software for the card but the card never worked. I wasted more than 4 hours on phone and re-installing drivers again and again. Then finally Belkin asked me to ship them the defective card to get a replacement. I pointed out that I should not have to bear the shipping costs because the card never worked to begin with but Belkin was not ready to cover the shipping costs. I have shipped them the defective card today and am awaiting a replacement to arrive
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000086150:4_months_and_waiting:"cstelzer3"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000086150
</asin>
<product_name>
Garmin 010-10425-00 Handlebar Mounting Bracket: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 21
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
4 months and waiting
</title>
<date>
October 3, 2003
</date>
<reviewer>
"cstelzer3"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Spokane, WA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I ordered this product June 21st and am now told i should receive it by Oct 28th.   I wouldn't waste my time ordering this product from Amazon
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00000J0SH:help_on_tri_color_ink:shawna_long
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00000J0SH
</asin>
<product_name>
HP 41 Tri-Color Ink Cartridge (51641A): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 11
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
HELP ON TRI COLOR INK
</title>
<date>
March 20, 2003
</date>
<reviewer>
SHAWNA LONG
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
LOUISVILLE, KY
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
THIS SITE IS HARD TO FIND THE INK CARTRIDGE I NEED. #78 TRI COLOR FOR MY HP 750
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00000J0SH:need_help_finding_hp_inks....:"vk518"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00000J0SH
</asin>
<product_name>
HP 41 Tri-Color Ink Cartridge (51641A): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Need help finding HP Inks....
</title>
<date>
December 8, 2002
</date>
<reviewer>
"vk518"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Dear Sir/Madam: Its very difficult to email you regarding things I can't find.! Or you don't sell? I am looking for HP black ink. #20 for 656C printer. Now, you tell me which ink I need? No way you can tell.!! Because you are NOT selling or what? You site is very difficult to find Ink I need
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00076FVP6:works:marshall_folsom
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00076FVP6
</asin>
<product_name>
Belkin RF Modulator ( F8V3063 ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Works
</title>
<date>
March 19, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Marshall Folsom
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Overall I don't like it. When the screen is black between scenes and what not, their is a lot of mixed in red and other colors from interference. Buy a different one, this one is just not up to the task
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005N5X1:don't_expect_the_a1500:j._desalme
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005N5X1
</asin>
<product_name>
Cobra HG A1000 High Gear CB Antenna: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Don't expect the A1500
</title>
<date>
December 19, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. DeSalme
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Arizona
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I ordered the A1500 and received the A1000. I opted not to send it back when I read the other feedback on this page. I didn't want to lose shipping costs and not get reimbursed (as the other fellow did below). Amazon is usually pretty good, not this time, and not on this product.
If you want, you can call them at: 
1.800.201.7575 (Toll free, US and Canada)
1.206.346.2992 or 1.206.266.2992 (Outside US and Canada)
1.877.586.3230 (Canada only)
UK customer service: +44.208.636.9200
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005N5X1:they_send_the_wrong_antenna:m._w._courson_"michael__{8-)"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005N5X1
</asin>
<product_name>
Cobra HG A1000 High Gear CB Antenna: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
They send the wrong antenna
</title>
<date>
February 21, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
M. W. Courson "Michael  {8-)"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Philadelphia, Pa United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I ordered the Cobra HG A1500 High Gear CB Antenna. They keep sending the Cobra HG A1000. Now I'm stuck with a antenna I did not order nor do I want.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000056HL5:not_so_great_for_tracheostomy_use:james_tee
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000056HL5
</asin>
<product_name>
Vicks Ultrasonic Humidifier: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Not so great for tracheostomy use
</title>
<date>
November 24, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
James Tee
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Diego, CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This Vicks ultrasonic humidifier was thoroughly recommended by everyone when we needed a humidifer with the possible hose attachment that goes to a mask around my dad's new tracheostomy.  Problem is, it puts out TOO much mist even at the lowest setting!  We've tried everything including taping the hole, but it then goes from 'all' to 'nothing' because the small hole desired quickly coalesces water preventing steam from passing through. Of course it wasn't until we started mentioning it to the various RN's that come to take care of my dad that 'everyone' using it for the same purpose complains of the same excessive mist problem.  So... I've resorted to making large hole cuts in the plastic tubing leading up to my dad's mask.  Not a great way to do it (and just asking to be seeded by bacteria), but if anyone has a better suggestion, I'm all for it, even if it means suggesting a different humidifier..
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000MQNMQ6:overpriced,_under-featured,_misleading.:katherine_anne_welles
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000MQNMQ6
</asin>
<product_name>
Apple TV: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Overpriced, under-featured, misleading.
</title>
<date>
April 24, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Katherine Anne Welles
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
O.K., so I'm paying $300 for a set-top box with a 40Gb hard drive, but I can't use it as a DVR? Why not? Also, the only content I can play on this set-top box is content that comes through iTunes? That's right. if it isn't in your iTunes library, you can play it on the Apple TV. This means you caqn play your DVD's, you cant't play saved DVD, iMovie, or other movie files, you can't play anything unless it has been successfully;y added to your iTunes library. Also, make sure you see the fine print about having to have a widescreen TV. they aren't joking about this. If you don't have one, you can still use this item but it will show up as a frame about half the size of your screen (it won't go to the edges and be borderless) so you have a tiny window to view inside a large black box. 

Any pros? It has to be the easiest setup I have ever experienced with an electronic item. I mean less than 5 minutes and I was set. also, I thought it was really coll that with zero configuring on my part, it was able to communicate perfectly with iTunes  just because I plugged the Apple TV into my Airport Extreme router that my computer was also plugged into. basically, Apple TV saw this is a direct link. I didn't think it would be that easy without having to configure something, but it was. Also the menus are very helpful and attractive. This will be a good product down the line when this will have a larger hard drive and DVR capability. Right now it's time to sell this one on ebay and wait a few years for something better. if this had only cost me $100 or $150 I would probably keep it, however. $300 is too much for too little
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000GJ5J6A:palm_pad_keeps_peeling:madminor
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000GJ5J6A
</asin>
<product_name>
Marware Protection Pack 13" MacBook White: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
palm pad keeps peeling
</title>
<date>
January 18, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
madminor
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The left palm pad keep peeling, possibly from the uneven heat.
This make the protection pad a lot less useful than one would
think, which is most people buy this pack fo
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001WXTF0:what_a_piece_of_crap!!!:ben_perron
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001WXTF0
</asin>
<product_name>
D-Link DSM-320 Wireless Media Player, Audio/Photo/Video, 802.11g: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
What a piece of crap!!!
</title>
<date>
April 4, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Ben Perron
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Not very happy with this product.
The software on the pc side doesn't work well at all.
Won't list all my files and I can't get it to update changes or new folders.

This bugger has way to big of a foot print.

The remote needs a skip function to fast foward through movies.
Hey I have a Xbox with XBMC on it. Get a clue, and copy some of it's functionality. It continues to blow away any of the media players I have purchased
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001WXTF0:stay_away_from_this_device.:m._moss
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001WXTF0
</asin>
<product_name>
D-Link DSM-320 Wireless Media Player, Audio/Photo/Video, 802.11g: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Stay Away from this Device.
</title>
<date>
February 24, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
M. Moss
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I read the other reviews, some glowing, others well.. not so glowing.  The price was right, ($149 - 50 rebate) So I thought I would take a chance.  I read the other reviews so I have no one else to blame but myself.

  First off, I am only interested in playing videos from my computer, so I have no idea how well the image viewing or MP3 playing works.  

  I also notice other people reviewing this product had all kinds of problems with wireless connections.  My house is fully wired with CAT5, therefore I am using this product wired, not wireless.

  I was able to get the device connected to my network and reading files from the media server within 10 minutes of opening the carton... so far so good.   The first thing I did was check for updates.  An update was found and updated successfully.

  I then had the DSM-320 look for media servers.  It found the tversity server right away and I was able to see the contents listed.  This unfortunately is the end of the good news.  It's all went downhill from here.

  1.  Neither server, tversity or the Dlink were smart enough to view a folder of VOB files as a movie.  They listed them as VOB_1, VOB2 etc.  So for example, I clicked on my Casablanca folder, I would then need to click on VOB_1 to start the movie.  When VOB_1 ended after about 20 minutes, it did not go to VOB_2.   I needed to use the remote and manually select the next item to play.   arrrgghh!!  P.O.S. thing.

  2.  As another review stated, the FF simply does not work properly.  Oh, sure if you press FF the movie will fast forward.  But there is no way to stop it.  If you press play while the movie is FF'wding, the movie starts to play from the beginning of the current VOB.  more, arrrrgghh!
This alone is enough of a nuisance to return the device.  Which I will be doing first thing in the morning.

My final advice to any prospective buyers:  S T A Y   A W A Y !!!!

My final advic to D-Link, Great idea, but your product absolutely sucks.

Oh one more thing,  Someone mentioned that their tech support was very freindly.  Yes the two ladies I spoke to were both very friendly, their English was terrible.  (Guess which county you call for tech support... oh come on, just one guess)  It also sounded like each of the tech support personnel are sitting shoulder to shoulder to one another.  I could hear at least 2 other tech support people communicating with their clients.  Which made it very difficult for the lady helping me.  She needed to ask me to repeat myself over and over.  Sheesh,  I must have read my phone number to her at least 4 times before she got it right.

One last interesting tidbit, on the packaging, they mention Nero recode CE.  So I went to the nero site to check it out.  Nero has a list of Supported Media Players listed.  And you know what, D-Link is NOT one of them.  I will return this D-Link junk and purchase one the Nero certified product instead.

I bow my head in shame, As I had read the reviews but I bought the product anyway.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001BXV9U:i_swore_i_would_never_buy_a_d-link_product_again...:mike
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001BXV9U
</asin>
<product_name>
D-Link Wireless Internet Camera, Home Security, 802.11b, 11Mbps: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
I swore I would never buy a D-Link product again...
</title>
<date>
January 11, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Mike
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Columbus, OH
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
And I was right....I should have passed on this.  It was a pain to configure, and then none of the settings would stick.  Whenever I changed the default password, it would never let me log back into the camera without having to do a reset.  That kind of defeats the point.  Returning this item so I can get something decent.  The money saved is NOT worth it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000ENMOSY:bad_customer_service_:d._ho_"dr._dh"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000ENMOSY
</asin>
<product_name>
Panasonic CQ-VD6503U 6.5" Wide Screen Touch-Panel LCD Monitor/DVD Video Receiver: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
BAD CUSTOMER SERVICE 
</title>
<date>
April 3, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
D. Ho "Dr. DH"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Georgia
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
bad customer service its been almost a month and i still have not received this product. ive sent 3 emails and called twice noone really helped me with anything, neither did anyone answer the phones. i dont even know how to rate the item because i dont have it. im pretty sure its really nice its just ive been waiting for almost a month and this is getting frustrating with no help
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009YNCSO:waste_of_money:tcat92_"tcat29"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009YNCSO
</asin>
<product_name>
iPod Car Audio Cassette Adaptor With Compact Digital Sound and Auto Reverse: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
waste of money
</title>
<date>
December 29, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
tcat92 "tcat29"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
You'll end up looking for something better.  Sound fidelity is pretty bad. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009YNCSO:don't_waste_your_money.:r._chan
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009YNCSO
</asin>
<product_name>
iPod Car Audio Cassette Adaptor With Compact Digital Sound and Auto Reverse: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Don't waste your money.
</title>
<date>
December 21, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
R. Chan
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
California
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
There's a reason this thing is only 6 bucks.  It's absolute junk.  I put it into the cassette player in my car, and the sounds were completely distorted.  The voice constantly skips, and the casette sometimes clicks.  The quality of sound in my car is usually amazing, and basically there was no bass sound coming through my speakers using this device.  I've tried both sides, but still no avail.  I plan on returning it if shipping doesn't cost more than the product itself
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007XCT0E:d-link_customer_service_is_terrible:netizen_fair
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007XCT0E
</asin>
<product_name>
D-Link DCS-6620 10/100TX PTZ Internet Camera, Optical Zoom, Dual Codec, 0.05Lux: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
D-Link Customer Service Is Terrible
</title>
<date>
October 21, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
netizen fair
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
NJ, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have a DCS-900W camera that failed within a year. After that, I made 7 calls to their customer service and tried to get it returned and replaced. Obviously I was talking to some indian people overseas that don't seem to care about the "service" that much, and usually after a couple of transfers, the line got cut off or picked up by another layman. During conversation, the line quality is very bad.

After a while, I just decided that $100 camera is not worth the time of the calls. I am in the process of reporting their practice to the better business bureau.

Based on my experience, I would be reluctant to buy any expensive things from D-Link. Once you have any problem, they just won't honor the waranty
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009XDKNW:weightlifters_beware.....:s._scapellati_"scap"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009XDKNW
</asin>
<product_name>
IPOD Shuffle Armband Carrier: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Weightlifters beware.....
</title>
<date>
January 10, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
S. Scapellati "Scap"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
SoCal
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I was pretty disappointed with the Tune Belt because of two main reasons.  First, I had to take my Shuffle out of the protective rubber case that I usually keep it in so that it would fit inside the Tune Belt.  That wasn't such a big deal since it is somewhat protected inside the neoprene sleeve.  But then I went to wear it for a run, and the arm-band was too small for my arm!  I have fairly developed biceps from years of weight training, but nothing outrageous.  I would have thought that with a velcro strap there would have been enough range to accommodate most users.  This is unfortunately not the case.  So if you have larger than average biceps (say 17" amd up), save your money...
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000N5WNKM:another_case_of_buzzing_sound:hari
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000N5WNKM
</asin>
<product_name>
Samsung 206BW 20-Inch Digital/Analog Widescreen LCD Monitor (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
another case of buzzing sound
</title>
<date>
April 24, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
hari
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
ca, united states
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
i bought my monitor yesterday and found to have a buzzing sound at lower brightness (andlt;100%). just scheduled an exchange LCD
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000F007K8:notorious_base_problem:christian_baude_"boomboom"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000F007K8
</asin>
<product_name>
TomTom GO 910 Portable GPS Vehicle Navigator: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Notorious Base Problem
</title>
<date>
April 19, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Christian Baude "BoomBoom"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
After having installed the unit for 43 days, the suction cup snapped off the plastic mounting.  This was a spantaneous break while driving sending the unit "Flying"! Very dangerous!!

Tomtom would not replace the unit, as the claim that paart is warranted only for 3 weeks! buyer beware.  See the TomTom forum for description and picture:

[...]

and other links to the base issue
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000B60GY8:poor_quality_control,_even_worse_sharp_customer_service:jeffrey_few
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000B60GY8
</asin>
<product_name>
Sharp Aquos LC-26D6U 26" HD-Ready LCD Flat-Panel TV: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
18 of 18
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Poor quality control, even worse Sharp customer service
</title>
<date>
November 1, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Jeffrey Few
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Seattle, WA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I ordered this television with high hopes, knowing that despite reports of firmware problems and other defects that I would luck out and save a bundle.  But you get what you pay for.  Every Sharp Aquos LCD TV manufactured before April 1, 2006 shipped with bad firmware.  What does this mean to you?

For me, it meant that 15 minutes after unpacking the TV and turning it on, it turned itself off and never turned back on again.  Resets, system resets, power cycling, unplugging components didn't help.  My TV was completely bricked.  A search turned up threads on websites like AVS Forum with other owners of Sharp TVs in the D4U and D6U series all reporting similar power management problems almost immediately after purchase.  For them, the fix was a visit to a Sharp authorized service center to either have the firmware replaced or a physical replacement of boards inside the TV.  I say a "visit" because Sharp does not cover in-house technician visits for TVs under 32", a fact they could have informed me of before letting me wait 1 week for a tech visit that would ultimately be canceled.

So here I am, 10 days later and hundreds of dollars poorer with no TV to show for it.  Instead, it sits at the authorized service center (because Sharp obviously does not vet its service centers to make sure you get good service from them either).

I'm willing to bet all of the inventory of D6Us that TigerDirect is selling at fire sale prices were produced before 4/1/2006.  Check the serial number on your TV if you do order one.  If it begins with a 501-512, 601, 602 or 603, immediately demand a firmware upgrade from Sharp (1-800-BE-SHARP), regardless of whether or not you're experiencing these issues; you will eventually, and hopefully while Sharp's warranty is still in effect for you.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00083XXTY:damaged:douglas_a._daugherty
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00083XXTY
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDMX2-1024 Sansa e140 1 GB Digital Audio Player with SD Expansion Slot: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
damaged
</title>
<date>
January 11, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Douglas A. Daugherty
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
i received my mp3 player with a big black spot in the middle of the screen, i sent it back and it has been 2-3 months and i havent heard anything back whether they will replace it or give me a credit
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000E5E6KG:wont_work_for_me:s_young
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000E5E6KG
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys WMB54G Wireless-G Music Bridge: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Wont work for me
</title>
<date>
March 8, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
S Young
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Oregon
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have not been able to get this to work again. It was great for the first week, then it made my computer crash and now I cannot get it installed again. I am not sure I like that
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BM946S:what_a_let_down_._._._:c._burnside_"jabba_jaw"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BM946S
</asin>
<product_name>
Creative Zen Micro Photo 8 GB MP3 Player, Green: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
What a let down . . . 
</title>
<date>
March 22, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
C. Burnside "Jabba Jaw"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
the same planet as you.
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I purchased this MP3 player thinking it was a good purchase.  Boy was I wrong.  Creative Labs tend to have glitches whether it be computer hardware, software, or other products like this one.  Now having problems with the product is one thing, but customer service is lousy and they could give a rats [...].  Also when I ordered seperate batteries from their online store they mentioned AFTER I purchased their product that it was going to be delayed for an extra month.  My MP3 player stopped working after 3 months, I did get it to work again.  Two months later the screen told me I had hardware problems.  OK, so I download the drivers that is supposed to fix the problem, no go.  Oh, and I forgot to mention that I am working in Eastern Europe at the time so it makes matters even better trying to get ahold of them via phone.  

Save yourself some frustration and get something better.  iriver maybe?  Just stay away from Creative Lab products. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BM946S:bad_choice!:tiffany_burton_"green"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BM946S
</asin>
<product_name>
Creative Zen Micro Photo 8 GB MP3 Player, Green: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Bad Choice!
</title>
<date>
March 11, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Tiffany Burton "Green"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Seattle, Wa
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this Mp3 player because it was just a few bucks cheaper than the Ipod and I ended up paying dearly for it.  It is a piece of junk that stopped working only after a couple months.  The firmware decided to stop recognizing songs, albums titles, and eventually that there was even any music to listen to.  Now I have a 200$ dollar mp3 player with no music on it that will not interface with my PC.  Customer service? Don't count on it.  So if your into extensively troubleshooting, highly frustrating, pieces of junk, this is a great product. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EGC9B8:no_handle:sam_"gsc"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EGC9B8
</asin>
<product_name>
Red Classic CD WALLET-128: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
11 of 12
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
NO HANDLE
</title>
<date>
January 17, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Sam "gsc"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Brooklyn, NY United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Nice product before they decided to save a few pennies - I have purchased seven, but now it is made with out the handle - so if that was part of the atraction of this case, note that the discription says 'sturdy padded handle' -- NOT!
5 STARS if it still had the handle or if you don't need one
</review_text>
</review>
</reviews>