<reviews>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008SCFU:fast_and_accurate:j._n._fong
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
30207
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008SCFU
</asin>
<product_name>
Kingston 256 MB Secure Digital Card ( SD/256 ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Fast and Accurate
</title>
<date>
March 19, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. N. Fong
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Castro Valley, CA  USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I received my Kingston 256MB SD card just as advertised.
The unit came in the mail exactly 2 days after I
ordered. Worked perfectly and I'm very satisfied
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000234UFG:good_design:unhchabo
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
42659
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000234UFG
</asin>
<product_name>
Power Strip Liberator II 1' "Y" Cable: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Good design
</title>
<date>
May 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
UNHchabo
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Works well, especially for anyone who still has their old console systems in use. I have my NES and SNES, both of which have huge AC adapters, plugged into this. It saves tons of space on my power strip.

The design is a little clumsy though, so it's only getting 4/5
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001IXUEY:excellent_buy:judith_carson_"jc"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
45944
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001IXUEY
</asin>
<product_name>
Panasonic RX-D29 CD / Radio / Cassette Boombox with MP3 CD Playback: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Excellent Buy
</title>
<date>
March 22, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Judith Carson "JC"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Ca
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Not as easy to use as a larger Panasonic I used to own but
otherwise fine. Good sound.  Using CD player and radio.
Buying via Amazon as usual is super
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006IC4E:excellent,_but_fragile:geoffrey_levine
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
46280
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006IC4E
</asin>
<product_name>
Fellowes 21100 Book Lift Holder (Silver): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
excellent, but fragile
</title>
<date>
January 24, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Geoffrey Levine
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
It worked much better than expected. The page clips also were very good, but one fell off about 5 minutes into owning/using the item (I put it back on, but fell off a couple more times). I also get the feeling that the other parts are fragile as well.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001Q5SZK:better_than_my_old_belkin_model:krystal_hillsman_"icekryztol"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
64342
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001Q5SZK
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus PAUH217U 4 Port Ultra Mini USB 2.0 Hub: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Better than my old Belkin model
</title>
<date>
January 30, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Krystal Hillsman "icekryztol"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
TN
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
It's speedy and space saving and inexpensive. I bought this to replace my Belkin because the Belkin needed to be plugged in. This one is powered by your computer so there's no extra power cords, which is a big plus to me. 

The only thing I dislike about this is the fact that the Hub takes up two Usb ports instead of just one like the Belkin. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000CQP5YS:it's_all_about_the_lighting:thx-1138
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
78884
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000CQP5YS
</asin>
<product_name>
Monster MCC AVL300-S Home Theater and Lighting Controller: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
It's all about the lighting
</title>
<date>
August 28, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
THX-1138
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Jose, CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I've had a number of universal remotes over the years and each has had pluses and minuses to offer. The monster remote is a very effective universal remote on all accounts but there is ONE thing that stands out here above all the other remotes. Wireless control over lighting. I replaced my dimmers and switches with the Monster dimmers and switches and now I can control every light in my house. Monster really doesn't talk much about this feature but being able to hit "ALL OFF" at night on my way to bed and have the remote turn off all the house lights is killer. You can even map ligthing scenes to activities. If you hit watch a movie it can turn down the ligths at the same time. Really cool. Good job monster.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00004Z5QI:what_can_i_say?__it's_a_nice_book_holder.:robert_shook
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
86739
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00004Z5QI
</asin>
<product_name>
Fellowes Book Lift Copyholder - For Use with Textbooks and Large Manuals: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
9 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
What can I say?  It's a nice book holder.
</title>
<date>
August 21, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Robert Shook
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I really don't have much to say about this book holder, not that it's just a book holder.  It's a nice one.  It does it's job.  It's a little too expensive for just a piece of plastic.

It's strong, sturdy, and it's big enough, even for those massive heavy textbooks, like the Calculus ones.  Although, I would not recommend putting a dictionary or reference that's like 6" thick (even though it still may hold).  It's got little clamps at the bottom to prevent the page from flipping all over the place, although those tend to fall off when you move them.  But that's no big deal.  Just put them back on.  

This book holder is kind of big, and I would not put it on a small desk in the middle of a classroom, but it's not too big.  You should be able to put it almost anywhere when studying on your own time. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BKE8QQ:best_headphones_i've_ever_used:j._weaver_"jweavis"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
105791
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BKE8QQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Altec Lansing inMotion iM716 Headphones: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Best Headphones I've Ever Used
</title>
<date>
August 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Weaver "JWeavis"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Michigan
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
After using my iM716s for about 4 months now I have a few things to say about them.

1) Price: Lists for $199 on Altec's site.  $70 is a steal.
2) Quality: Top notch in the earphones, the clip on the volume module is weak.
3) Performance: Bar none best I've had.  These things outperform the huge Logitech ear muff set I use mainly to mow in.  These things allow me to mow the lawn without having to jack up the volume to drown out the mower.
4) Conclusion: The only thing that stops me from saying these are perfect is the volume module can be a pain and get in the way.  When moving around, you NEED to have it clipped to something, otherwise it can create inner ear noise.  This can get quite annoying.  I've also caught the cord on things, causing the clip to bend away from the module.  It is removeable and I was able to bend it back.  If there were a pair of equal quality w/o the module, even for the same price, I'd go that route.  With that said, I am in no way regretting my purchase and will recommend these to anyone asking me about them or my 60GB video ipod
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000ULJWS:belkin_tunedok_for_ipod:cindy_a._murray
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
106229
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000ULJWS
</asin>
<product_name>
Belkin TuneDok for iPod: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Belkin TuneDok for iPod
</title>
<date>
February 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Cindy A. Murray
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is perfect for my iPod and keeps it totally secure while driving.  Great price and you get different sizes to match your car perfectly. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000CO77FA:2-year_replacement:k._spencer_"magna_man"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
108372
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000CO77FA
</asin>
<product_name>
2-Year Replacement Plan for Electronics Products $50 to $74.99: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
2-Year Replacement
</title>
<date>
August 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
K. Spencer "Magna man"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
MO.
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Always something that might come in handy my last remote quit working after a year
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002MSTW2:fast_reader/writer_:shawn_m._matheson_"smatheso"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
117024
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002MSTW2
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar Media 1 GB 80x Pro Series Compact Flash Card (CF1GB-80-380): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
9 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Fast Reader/Writer 
</title>
<date>
March 3, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Shawn M. Matheson "smatheso"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Spokane, WA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This CF card is so fast that I can run my shutter on my camera non stop until the card is full at a frame rate of 3.5 fps. No lag or slow down. That is amazing. It makes my camera perform better. (Canon Rebel XT
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006HYUC:great_bang_for_the_buck!:george_w._roden
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
118161
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006HYUC
</asin>
<product_name>
APC BE350U 350VA Back-ups Es: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Great Bang for the Buck!
</title>
<date>
March 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
George W. Roden
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Cassville, MO USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I installed this unit on my HP AMD 64 X2 with a 19-inch LCD monitor.  Installation was very straightforward, with no problems experienced.  The unit has two rows of power outlets - eight outlets total.  All are surge protected, but only one row has battery backup.  Each row includes an outlet that is offset to allow transformer power supplies to be connected and still accommodate use of the other outlets.  The unit also surge protects the incoming telephone line, and interacts well transparently my DSL service.

The unit comes with a USB connector cable that is used to transfer information between the unit and the computer.  Also included is "PowerChute Personal Edition" software.  This software replaces the UPS option used under the "Power" icon of Widow's XP Control Panel.  PowerChute PE allows user selection of alarms and power options to best fit the user's needs.  PowerChute PE automatically loads at computer startup, and resides as an icon on the right-side of the Window's task bar.  It monitors the unit's status, and provides information concerning abnormal power events that have occurred for future reference.

In order to assure that there is enough battery power for this unit to operate properly, I only attached the PC and monitor to the powered row of outlets.  Transformers seem to use a lot of power, and to gain the most time available for adequate shut-down times they should only be plugged into the "surge only" outlet row.

When A/C power fails, the unit immediately picks up the power load.  It will then begin to shut down the PC if A/C power does not become available shortly .  The default method it uses is to place the PC into "hibernation mode", saving the desktop exactly "as is" for future start-up.  It accomplished this task with my PC perfectly.

If I had wanted a UPS to keep my computer running for several minutes during an A/C power outage, this is not the unit I would have purchased.  However, to keep my system from re-booting due to the power being interrupted momentarily, or to shut down the PC safely should the power outage last longer, this is a cost-effective solution for those tasks.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00016L0VQ:512_mb_secure_digital_ultra_ii:r._yap
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
120339
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00016L0VQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Sandisk 512 MB Secure Digital Ultra II (SDSDH-512-901, Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
512 mb secure digital ultra II
</title>
<date>
August 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
R. Yap
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I used it in Brasil and had it developed.  I was very happy with it.  It was the very first time I've used a digital camera
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008EM7V:great_product:r._fodo_"therage800"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
128289
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008EM7V
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex Optifix Motorized CD/DVD Cleaner and Scratch Repair Kit: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great Product
</title>
<date>
September 15, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
R. Fodo "therage800"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I had two unworking disks (One a PS2 game and the other a PSX game) so I picked this up and both work fine now! The only thing is you'll have to run it through a couple times. If you run it through once you'll see little difference... But for the price and since it does work... eventually, I still give it a 5 out of 5.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BBCTHU:fantastic_piece_of_kit:p._cook
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
135375
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BBCTHU
</asin>
<product_name>
Wacom Graphire4 4x5 USB Tablet (Silver): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Fantastic piece of kit
</title>
<date>
November 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
P. Cook
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
What an amazing product for such a small price.  It works right out of the box, but to get full functionality you need to install the encolsed drivers.  The option of mouse or pen makes it useful for everyday PC work as well using the pen for graphics.  I use it mainly for teaching via phone and use the whiteboard in messenger to communicate in words and pictures.  It really makes a difference.
The unit seems well made and I like the fact you can personalise the tablet to add a picture of your choice.  I opted for the smallest in the range for value, and was not disappointed, but I am sure for more commerical use or for artwork a much bigger screen would be better, but at cost.
The software bundle is ok too if you don't already have photoshop tools.
The one quibble is that at home when I installed the drivers it continued to crash my PC with my wireless keyboard installed.  Not ideal, but as I dont use it at home any longer it is not a problem for me, but be careful, I am sure there will be a fix somewher
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00070QI1S:very_good_sd_card:gabriel_gore_"geebi"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
135751
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00070QI1S
</asin>
<product_name>
Kingston 512MB Elite Pro Secure Digital Memory Card ( SD/512-S ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Very good SD Card
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Gabriel Gore "geebi"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Algood, TN
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I like it very much, I use it in an outdoor trail camera for wild game and it hold several pictures and has been in the camera in all kinds of weather. I would buy Kingston again
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001ZIYQ6:very_good_but_it_has_little_problems.:b._huang
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
137988
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001ZIYQ6
</asin>
<product_name>
Hagiwara Sys-Com HNT-MSW1 802.11b Memory Stick Wireless Lan Card for Sony's CLIE Handheld: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Very good but it has little problems.
</title>
<date>
January 31, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
B. Huang
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Irvine, CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I got this card last month and I've been using it heavily. Its been great. Its sturdy and can has great range. There are a few problems though.

#1 There is no case for the card.
#2 The included browser only lasts for 30 days and its horrible. Luckily I had NetFront 3.1
#3 Memory Stick LAN software will occasionally error, but a soft reset will fix it.

Otherwise its a great little expansion card
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000ER23M2:good_but_sluggish:reggie_hammond_"oreginaldesigns"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
143752
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000ER23M2
</asin>
<product_name>
Logitech NuLOOQ Navigator (965162-0403): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Good but Sluggish
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Reggie Hammond "Oreginaldesigns"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I love my tooldial and its' software.  My only complaint is that you must have a very large proccessor to run it effectively.  I frequently find that it gums up photoshop and in-design a little.  Overall great product and I expect them to have some updates to work out the bugs.  Works very well in tandem with a WACOM tablet
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000AKVHF:great_card_reader_for_the_price:t._tom
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
144479
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000AKVHF
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDDR-88-A15 8-in-1 USB 2.0 Hi-speed Reader (Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Great card reader for the price
</title>
<date>
September 19, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
T. Tom
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Marin County, CA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is a great card reader for the price. Why pay more if this one reads the all cards that you have? Personally, I only use CompactFlash and SD cards. It reads these cards and it does it fast and reliably.

The shape of this card reader is a bit awkward but then again it does help you grab the unit while inserting and removing cards, which you'll want to do a bit carefully. It would be a bit more difficult to do that with the unit lying flat on the desk. Remember to never force the card in and remember the label side faces towards the Sandisk logo on the card reader. It is slightly tricky to get the cards into the slots at first, but once you get the feel of it, it beccomes quite easy and routine.

This Sandisk has LED indicators that are helpful. One Amber LED to tell you the unit is connected to your USB, and other green ones by each card slot to let you know either that you have a card insert (solid green), or that it's reading or writing (blinking green).

This card reader comes with a 1 year warranty and I feel it represents a good value. I would recommend it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000AKVHF:near_perfection_at_a_great_price!:sea-psych
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
144484
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000AKVHF
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDDR-88-A15 8-in-1 USB 2.0 Hi-speed Reader (Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
near perfection at a great price!
</title>
<date>
July 28, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
sea-psych
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The Sandisk reader is impossible to misuse. It loads quickly and it's compact shape offers most options for memory. It can be mounted vertically with attached stand for sleek ease of use or compacted flat to be discreet. I would prefer a little more weight so that it doesn't move around on my desk so I'm giving it only 4 stars. If I had to replace this reader, I would buy another SanDisk
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002KQRBY:these_media_worked_fine_on_my_computer:sudarshan_karkada
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
144721
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002KQRBY
</asin>
<product_name>
Velocity DVD-R 4X 4.7GB, 10-Spindle: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
These media worked fine on my computer
</title>
<date>
February 18, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Sudarshan Karkada
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Missouri City, TX USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I agree that these are not top of the line. But they aren't bad at all. I get coasters occassionally even from top of the line media.

I always burn at half the speed the media is designed for - 2x in this case. It takes longer, but I get good results. I am rarely in a hurry to burn a DVD.

I would buy these again.

** Updated on 7/3/2005 **
I have bought a new computer recently and I have been burning these DVDs with full speed supported by the writer and no coasters what-so-ever. Very happy with this product
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009Q4U7Y:look_no_further!!!__really!!!!!!!!!!!:mark_p
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
147639
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009Q4U7Y
</asin>
<product_name>
iAudio X5 20 GB Portable Multimedia Player with FM Tuner and Voice Recorder (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Look No Further!!!  Really!!!!!!!!!!!
</title>
<date>
August 2, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Mark P
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Oklahoma City, OK
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I, like many other people that have written reviews here, researched the purchase of an MP3 player in great detail.  Other members of my family own iPods, and that is the direction that I was heading until I did a massive amount of research.  If you want to rip the thousands of songs that you already own on CD, this is the unit that you want.  iPod will not let you download your own songs, I did not know that until after I purchased this player (thankfully).  This unit was the highest rated unit by far that I was able to scour the internet for.  If this is your first purchase of an MP3 player (like mine) buy this one, no questions asked.  Do not worry about trying to buy $80 ear buds the sound from the ear buds that come with the player is unreal.  Crisp, clear, awsome base and I have only turned up the player to 23 on the volume it goes up to 40.  I cannot hear the home stereo that my wife is listening to or my kids that are running around the house playing.  I received this player in the mail today at 5:30 when I got home from work and by 6:35 I have transfered the 114 artists folders (about 4,000+ songs) that I had ripped on my computer last week (about 35 to 40 minutes to transfer the music to the staging folder and then to the player).

I would recomend buying the cradle, it helps in standing it up on the desk or over the stereo, which I plan to do to play all my music on my outdoor speakers by the pool.

Absolutley buy this unit.  I have only messed wit it for a couple of hours and I have a high performance expectation and it has met it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000AY0HTU:not_just_for_gaming:richard_doyle_"web_lacky"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
148029
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000AY0HTU
</asin>
<product_name>
Logitech G15 Gaming Keyboard: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Not just for gaming
</title>
<date>
November 3, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Richard Doyle "web lacky"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Fairfax, VA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this keyboard originally for the LCD screen and the wide range of possibilities that exist with programming it for various games I play.  I was suprised to learn that this is more than a pretty keyboard with an LCD hanging off of it.  It's the best-feeling keyboard I've ever owned.  The keys take just the right amount of pressure to operate, and the switch to disable the windows key is a welcome feature.  The backlighting is bright, day or night, and the programmable G-keys make executing complicated key combinations in games or business applications a thing of the past.  Highly recommended
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000A2K3XW:very_good_tv:rick_d._tucker
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
148799
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000A2K3XW
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony KDFE42A10 42" LCD Rear Projection Television: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Very Good TV
</title>
<date>
November 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Rick D. Tucker
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Oklahoma, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I'm very happy with the set.  Although not listed in the specs, it must have a QAM tuner, because I am able to watch unscrambled digital broadcasts through my cable service even though all I have is basic cable.  I was thrilled when I made this discovery.  Watching football games in HD, without paying for digital cable, almost made me weep with happiness.

The picture quality for analog channels is only so-so.  I really wish the remote was illuminated.  Also, Amazon took much longer to deliver the TV than was promised.  Other than these negatives, I'm very happy
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000B622CW:mine_works_perfectly:music_lover
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
149658
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000B622CW
</asin>
<product_name>
Griffin Technology 4026-LCDT iTrip LCD FM Transmitter for iPod: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Mine works perfectly
</title>
<date>
October 22, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Music lover
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Denver, Co
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
We have the original Itrips but wanted this one for travel since it is much eaiser to tune in. The originals work great around town because it is always set on the same station. After reading the instructions I plugged the new Itrip in and it worked perfectly just like the originals. Not only did it work but it worked from 40 feet away. That is better than I expected after reading all the feedback. I'm not sure what everyones problem is. It's not a radio tower, it's a transmitter the size of your finger. I get the feeling that some people think it should power the City block.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000050AOP:flawless:kirk_w_horne
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
151035
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000050AOP
</asin>
<product_name>
Hewlett Packard CD-Writer C4503A 9510i 12x8x32 Internal EIDE Kit: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Flawless
</title>
<date>
February 5, 2002
</date>
<reviewer>
Kirk W Horne
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Graham, NC United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have used the 9510i for about 2 years and have found it to be flawless in performance. The Disaster Recovery software provided with this drive is it's biggest star. You can format your hard drive, put in the restore disk that you create for your system, and in about 15 minutes your system is put back to EXACTLY the way it was when you created the disk. Or you can simply replace selected files if you want. It does not miss a single thing. Fanstastic. The software is extremely user friendly and guides you through the process easier than an andquot;ABCandquot; book. I would highly recommend this drive for performance and ease of use
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006J05Z:excellent:l._lyskowsky
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
155416
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006J05Z
</asin>
<product_name>
Phonex Broadband PX 442 Modem Jack Extension unit: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Excellent
</title>
<date>
February 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
L. Lyskowsky
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Phoenix, AZ
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Works great!!!  I have a flat roof that does not allow me to add a phone line and the only way to use my satilite system is with a long phone cord accross my room.  This jack extension helped me eliminate the long ugly cor
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002ZAIM8:it_is_like_part_of_me!:david_chen
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
155509
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002ZAIM8
</asin>
<product_name>
Apple 1 GB iPod Shuffle: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
It is like part of me!
</title>
<date>
November 19, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
David Chen
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Ok, I got this as gift so I got nothing to lose right!  Well, this little gadget will be my first open door to the ipod world and i gotta say that it really gives me an awsome impression toward what apple has accomplished for ipod shuffle.
Ever since I unpacked this little thing, it has been with me everywhere!  On the go, exercise, sleeping....anywhere you have pockets to put it, ipod shuffle is always with me whenever I needed some kick of tunes, its ultra light and portability has really achieved what it meant to accomplish in the first place and talking about 1 GB of stores mp3 for about 16 hrs of playtime, it is just too hard not to fall in love with this little part of me...lol!  Sound quality is decent too and it is quite easy to charge and transfer/update tunes on the go.  So if you are a fast paced, mobile and not a control freak, then ipod shuffle is definitely a good way to get giggy with it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006HXHU:best_in_class:dja
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
155777
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006HXHU
</asin>
<product_name>
Canon CP-100 Digital Photo Printer: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
12 of 14
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Best in Class
</title>
<date>
November 21, 2002
</date>
<reviewer>
DJA
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Boston, MA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
If you own a Canon digital camera this printer is great.  It is portable and makes great prints.  People think they are from a photolab.  It is also vey easy to use.  I have seen other mini printers from Olympus and Sony and they are not as good.  They cost more too
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BNMDC4:among_the_best_for_fm_transmitters...:joshua_i._huffines
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
156806
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BNMDC4
</asin>
<product_name>
DLO 009-3032 Transpod All-in-One Car Solution for iPod (Silver): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Among the best for FM transmitters...
</title>
<date>
June 13, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Joshua I. Huffines
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Seattle, WA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I recently purchased this as a replacement for my Monster Cable.  I must say that I am quite impressed.  This is the best FM transmitter I have encountered.

I live in Seattle.  There is a fairly saturated FM dial, and the unique topography of the surrounding area has a tendency to deflect certain signals.  That said, I only have minor problems with interference, the most common of which is moderate distortion in the upper ranges.

Functionality is pretty much seamless in my car.  I drive a 2003 Ford Focus.  The 12v power jack is position to the left of my in dash CD changer, so accessibility is not an issue.

If anyone is in the market for an FM transmitter for their iPod, I highly recommend this one.  "That'll do, pig.  That'll do.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002IOIMQ:a_very_nice_charger:--chris
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
159662
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002IOIMQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony BCG-34HRMF4 Super Quick Charger with LCD Indicator and 4 AA Batteries: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
A very nice charger
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
--chris
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New Jersey
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Overall a very nice charger, though recharge times aren't even close to what is advertised.  The display is very nice as is the ability to charge individual batteries instead of having to do it in a pair.  The 900 mAH hold such a small charge that they are almost worthless.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BVB2FK:wacom_intuos3_tablet_review:d-mag.org_reviewer
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
160842
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BVB2FK
</asin>
<product_name>
Wacom Intuos3 6X11 Pen Tablet: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
13 of 13
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Wacom Intuos3 Tablet Review
</title>
<date>
June 28, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
D-MAG.org Reviewer
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Lexington, KY USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Title: Intuos3 Tablet
Publisher: Wacom
Publish Date: Unknown
ISBN/Model #:  PTZ631W
Reviewer: Robert Saucier
Rating: 5 stars

In 1997, after buying a new top-of-the-line 450MHz Pentium II system, I splurged on a Wacom ArtZ II tablet.  Oh, my!  Pressure-sensitive, tilt-sensing, pointer control, assignable function pads; it was Heaven.

After a couple of years, every time I tried to use it with my primary graphics application, my computer would spontaneously reboot -- a bit counter-productive.  I watched for new drivers and new versions of my application but, as technology marched on, my beloved tablet and graphics application continued their spats.

Sadly, I disconnected the tablet and gently packed it away.  Lately, I've been feeling the pull once more, that urge to use a pen to do photo touch-ups instead of my mouse.  Miraculously, a Wacom Intuos3 6-inch by 11-inch tablet dropped, almost literally, into my lap.  Sleek, gun-metal gray, sexy -- with a comfort-grip pen (much like my coveted Pilot G2 pens) AND a mouse!  Even better, the Intuos3 comes bundled with 3 applications that show off its capabilities:  Adobe Elements 4.0, Corel Painter Essentials 3, and nik Color Efex 2.0 lE.  Heaven just got better!

The Intuos3 has over 5000 lines per inch of resolution, over twice that of the Wacom Graphire product line, and, with its USB 2 connection, there's more than enough communication bandwidth, meaning better tablet to application response.  One hesitation I have when adding a new piece of hardware is in regard to what the driver will do to my system; will it introduce instability or get along with everyone else.  The Intuos3 driver has been rock-solid in the two weeks that the tablet has been living with me.  I've used all of my "usual" programs and have had no problems at all.  The tablet has also been peacefully co-existing with two external drives, a wireless desktop receiver, a card reader, a scanner, and a printer, all riding the same USB bus.

The Intuos3 has 8 "chordable" buttons, 4 at each side of the tablet, to which keys, macros, or other actions may be assigned.  The default for each group are the usual ALT, CTRL/Command, and Shift, along with "space".  The placement of the buttons allows you to keep a grip on the tablet, holding one or more of the buttons, while tapping whatever key on the keyboard with your pen hand.  Being chordable, you can hold any or all of the buttons down for those tricky shortcuts like ALT-CTRL-S or To the side of each of the two button pads are touch strips which can be independently programmed as well.  The default setting is to scroll or depending on the context.  The ends of the strip, in keystroke mode, can be set to playback macros.  The pen, with its 1024-level pressure-sensitive stylus AND "eraser," also has a DuoSwitch.  The DuoSwitch's two positions may also be programmed.

The pen action is smooth with the default nylon nib -- there are different types of nibs to simulate different types of tactile feedback.  With the ergonomic grip, the pen is extremely comfortable to hold.  The 5-button mouse, designed to be used by either "righties" or "lefties," is not as ergonomically correct but considering the versatility, this is more than acceptable.  As with every other clickable/pressable feature associated with the Intuos3, the mouse buttons are programmable with a ridiculous number of options, although I've yet to find the "fix photo,"  "illustrate article," or even the "design website" settings.

I can see only two very minor changes that I would make to this fantastic product.  I would love to see the ability to add weight to the pen.  It is just a bit too light for my personal tastes and considering how configurable the tablet is already, this feature would be the feather on the cap to me.  The other change would be making the drawing surface transparent as it is on the Graphire (and was on the ArtZ II).  Sometimes, having the ability to trace an outline can save significant time.

For the casual home user, I would recommend the Graphire product line -- this Intuos3 model's SRP of $369 may be a bit high where a $99 entry point on the Graphire is more affordable.  For the pro-consumer or professional, however, whether doing photo editing (my primary use) or illustration, the Intuos3 line is well worth the investment.  It's great to be in Heaven again ...
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BP50AY:sansa_m240_:a._cahill
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
169038
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BP50AY
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk Sansa M240 1 GB MP3 Player (Silver): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Sansa m240 
</title>
<date>
November 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
A. Cahill
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought the Sansa M240 two months ago and am quite happy with it. It's light-weight, holds plenty of media (I have yet to fill it up) and the sound is suprisingly good. No complaints
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EDK8V4:incredible_picture!_with_one_flaw_on_old_dvds:no-nonsense_consumer
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
173172
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EDK8V4
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony DVPNS75H Single Disc Upscaling DVD Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Incredible picture! with one flaw on old DVDs
</title>
<date>
November 11, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
No-Nonsense Consumer
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The other effusive reviews are spot-on...  the picture is fabulous on new DVDs (Lord of the Rings, Nemo, Harry Potter).  A $20 Cables to Go HDMI cable does a great job.  We have the  Sony KDF-42E2000 42" 3LCD Rear Projection HDTV and are thrilled with the combination.  A few annoyances:  The machine responds and loads slowly, but that's not too bad; a minor sacrifice for the incredibly low price.  And, certain DVDs of old movies (Some Like it Hot, The King and I) stretch the picture horizontally, making things look squat.  I'm sure there's a solution, but just can't figure it out.  Any tips
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005BC0H:excellent_scanner:martijn_van_heeringen
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
181620
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005BC0H
</asin>
<product_name>
C Pen 800C Handheld Scanner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Excellent scanner
</title>
<date>
June 1, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Martijn Van Heeringen
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Oostburg Netherlands
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this item, since I always make a lot of notes from books and other papers, and don't want to type it in manually anymore. This scanner, probably like any other model, needs a little training to get it right over the paper, but once done, it really works and faster than typing!
I dont use the addressbook or options with your GSM but they are no doubt very handy.
I just scan in from papers, and beam it to my laptop. Both Infrared and the cable work. The cable is especially great for using the scanner 'live'on the screen: the scanned text appears on the pc as you type!
The dictionary also comes in very handy.

It must be a very complex product, but just like the Ipod or ZenXtra mp3 players: they work!
So buy one and save some time! Excellent and recommended for anyone that needs to make notes, or studies, or just wants to stop cutting out pages in newspapers in a train e.g
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000050AQ7:excellent_jewel_cases:coordinator_"spectre"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
182702
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000050AQ7
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 32021926 Clear Slim Jewel Cases (25-Pack): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Excellent jewel cases
</title>
<date>
November 5, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Coordinator "spectre"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Minnesota
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
As your DVD/CD collections grow, these are ideal for protecting and storing your "treasures". Easy to open and take up little storage space. The center lock tab is secure but allows you to remove the discs from the case with ease.
Just a great product
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00063RT5K:great_batteries_at_a_great_price:dave_gilbert_"sureshotstl"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
187575
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00063RT5K
</asin>
<product_name>
Tech B BTAA4801 AA Alkaline Batteries 48-Pack: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great batteries at a great price
</title>
<date>
October 3, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Dave Gilbert "SureShotSTL"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Saint Louis
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Excellent value -- these batteries are just as good as name brands for about half the price.  If you use a lot of AA's, this is the way to go -- made especially nice if you use them as a filler to get your shipping free on your entire order if it is hovering in the $18 range
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00017IX10:sound_is_great:j._legallo
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
195050
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00017IX10
</asin>
<product_name>
Altec Lansing inMotion Portable Audio System for iPod: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Sound is great
</title>
<date>
June 26, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Legallo
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Virginia
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Very pleased w/item.  Compact.  Easy to move from place to place
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00080YK9Y:has_been_working_fine:neil_serdinsky_"yankee710"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
197539
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00080YK9Y
</asin>
<product_name>
Skip Dr. Motorized Automax Scratch Repair System: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Has been working fine
</title>
<date>
July 4, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Neil Serdinsky "yankee710"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this to clean up all of my kids DVDs. They have a ton of discs that are dirty, scratched, etc. I have cleaned over 30 discs so far and have fixed all but one (it was *really* scratched up).

I am suprised at the negative reviews on this item since I have considered this one of my smartest buys this year
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002IWCAQ:nice,_long-lasting_batteries:mikerman
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
201212
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002IWCAQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony NH-AACE AA Rechargeable Batteries In Slide Case: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Nice, long-lasting batteries
</title>
<date>
June 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
mikerman
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Redwood City, CA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Just wanted to echo what others have said, that these batteries seem to really last.  I received a new camera and was using generic rechargeable batteries in it, almost as powerful as the 2500s here, and the batteries ran out after a few hours.  Replaced those batteries with these, and these just seem to last on and on.  Am very happy with them
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002WPSBC:home_theater_in_a_box.:mark_b._wiest_"jkmw"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
206680
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002WPSBC
</asin>
<product_name>
Logitech Z-5500 Digital 5.1 5-Piece Speaker System with Subwoofer: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Home Theater in a Box.
</title>
<date>
November 11, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Mark B. Wiest "jkmw"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
You really can't go wrong with this one.  Not great response but what do you expect for less than $300?  On the other hand, The possibilities for this surround system are endless.  Want something just for the effects to complilment your bedroom wide screen?  How about using it for a dedicated gaming sound system, (this is how my daughter has it configured).  It's our second one.  First one died as a result of recent electrical storm, (Yes the circuit was 'protected', but so what).  Couldn't be happier for the investment
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001WV08S:backup_of_my_computors:a._gerst_"plandust"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
208163
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001WV08S
</asin>
<product_name>
Belkin F6C550-AVR Battery Backup with Surge Protection (550VA): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Backup of my computors
</title>
<date>
March 8, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
A. Gerst "plandust"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Jose, CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This appears to be a good piece of equipment. I hav'nt had any major outages as of yet but a minor fluctuation was handled very well.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009EXVIA:couldn't_have_asked_for_more.:couch_potato_"noddy"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
208456
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009EXVIA
</asin>
<product_name>
Samsung HL-R4266W 42" Widescreen HDTV DLP TV: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Couldn't have asked for more.
</title>
<date>
March 17, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Couch potato "noddy"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Baltimore, MD
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The service from Amazon was great, delivery people were most cooperative, made delivery as promised, placed TV in space where we wanted and hooked up and checked it out.
They even offered to take away the empty carton. We saved about $250 by buying from Amazon rather than from local retailer
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EOJ792:excellent_system_for_price.:k._der
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
212402
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EOJ792
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony HT-DDW700 Complete 5.1-Channel DVD Home Theater System: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Excellent System for Price.
</title>
<date>
August 24, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
K. Der
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
If you want a budget home theater system for under $200 there is probably not many systems better then the Sony HT-DDW700. This system is ideal for small rooms such as a bed room or a tiny living room.

Considering the price, sound quality is actually better then expected for me. The tiny cube speakers presents pretty good clarity. They may look like cheap computer speakers but they aren't and are a bit heavier then they look. The center channel may be a little underpowered since dialog during dvd movies sound a tad soft and a little too low. The surround effects during movies in dolby digital and dts are very good though.
If set up properly the speakers handle surround effects very well.

Some minor complaints is that the speaker wire attached to the speakers are very thin. They are fixed and can't be replaced. Also, if you want heart stopping bass then this system might not be for you. The 8" subwoofer is okay considering the price of the system. It is currently better then any other sub included in a home theater system under $200. It isn't powered, is very light (only 9 lbs) and you have to be pretty close to actually feel the bass. The volume would have to be cranked up extremely high for the sub to actually rattle your walls. 

The receiver comes with 1 optical and 1 coxial digital input and 4 rca analog inputs. It should be enough in most cases. An extra digtal input or two wouldn't hurt but again the system is under $200. Setup couldn't be easier. You just hook up the included microphone, place it at your listening postion and press a button on the remote. The system will automatically sets up the speaker distance, delay and volume levels. The receiver comes with the basic pro logic II music and move modes to upmix your stereo sources. It also has other sound fields and effects to enhace the sound but they don't really seem to enhance the sound by that much if at all.

Basically, if you want a home theater system for a small room and for under $200 then there isn't much better then the Sony HT-DDW70
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EH4Y56:good_performance_for_$150;_but_cheaply_made_(in_china).:t._agoston_"tawmbooks"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
217846
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EH4Y56
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony MHCEC70 Mini Shelf System with 3-Disc CD Changer, Cassette Deck, and AM/FM Tuner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Good performance for $150; but cheaply made (in China).
</title>
<date>
October 2, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
T. Agoston "tawmbooks"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Connecticut, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I've owned many Sony electronics in the past and have always liked their styling and functionality -- lots of hardy Walkmen, useful shortwave and portable radios, stylish TVs and high quality cassette recorders.  I still have a Sony mini component stereo model FH-E656 (made in Japan) which I bought in 1992 for US$400+; but rather than pay to fix its worn-out CD player, I decided to purchase this new Sony MHCEC70 component stereo (made in China).

PLUSES: 
decent sound
good functionality
easy set-up and intuitive operation
simple remote -- but only covers basic functions

CONS:
very short speaker leads
unattractive styling (for my tastes) -- resembles a boombox
only holds 3 CDs vs 5 for comparable Panasonic units

At first glance, I was disappointed by the cheap construction, skimpy manual and very short speaker leads -- the manufacturer seemed to be counting pennies.  But then I thought: in 2006 for $150, I can't expect the same quality as I received in 1992 for $400.  Everything is made more cheaply now and almost all in China.  So, for the money, it suits my purposes as a nice sounding stereo unit for the bedroom.  The real test will be how long the CD changer works -- to be safe, this time I bought the 2 year replacement warranty.  I haven't blasted it at full volume, but it seems to have plenty of power when needed.

I originally bought a $300 Panasonic unit (SC-PM71SD MP3 SD Micro System) which was returned because it didn't have the full data recording feature as advertised (data recording was crippled by DRM limitations).  This Sony stereo costs half as much, and has almost all the same functionality
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000DLB91A:great,_does_exactly_what_it_says,_great_price!__:grace_"grace_smith03"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
230302
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000DLB91A
</asin>
<product_name>
Belkin F8Z060 iPod Nano Silicon Sleeve (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great, does exactly what it says, great price!  
</title>
<date>
November 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Grace "grace_smith03"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
MA, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The silicone is great quality, fits the nano snugly, and the arm band is nice.  Wonderful product, does what it's supposed to do, for a fabulous price. Recommended
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00003G1RG:wow!_great_item:sankar_"sa"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
232963
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00003G1RG
</asin>
<product_name>
Viking 128 MB CompactFlash Card (CF128M): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
WOW! great item
</title>
<date>
January 6, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
sankar "SA"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Oak Park, CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this 2 years back and still it is in great shape. Recently i forgot compact flash in my shirt pocket and went for washing and then followed by Drying. My wife found compact flash in dryer and i thought it would not work. Surprisingly it is working fine and i could see my past snapshots with out any problem.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EH4Y3S:good_enough_for_the_money:yue_t._hu
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
234254
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EH4Y3S
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony CMT-NEZ30 Audio Micro System with CD Player, Cassette Deck, and AM/FM Tuner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Good enough for the money
</title>
<date>
July 25, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Yue T. Hu
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Seattle, WA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
It does everything I expected to do. Easy manual and set up. Great sound. I am keeping it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000068IHH:everything_i_was_looking_for!:s._ingle
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
234311
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000068IHH
</asin>
<product_name>
Case Logic DMB-5 CD Sports Pack: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Everything I was looking for!
</title>
<date>
January 9, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
S. Ingle
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Indiana, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I am very pleased with this item. It is fits comfortably, holds my CD player snugly and has room for my ID, keys, extra batteries and CD's
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000BZ40B:best_available_multi-purpose_4g_ipod_case:gary
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
242010
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000BZ40B
</asin>
<product_name>
DLO Action Jacket for 3G iPod Graphite: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
16 of 16
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Best Available Multi-Purpose 4G iPod Case
</title>
<date>
October 23, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Gary
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
TX
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
After looking around at the local stores (Fry's and CompUSA) I had just about given up on finding a single case that would offer reasonable protection for my iPod in multiple environments - on my belt and also in exercise, and had resigned myself to having a "skin" type case for just everyday use and then shifting the iPod to an arm band for exercise. Not a particularly great solution - expensive (around $20 for each) and a lot of shifting back and forth to cover both uses.

Then I ran into the DLO Action Jacket at Best Buy, which seemed to cover all my intended uses. Unlike the prior reviewer, I found my 40g iPod fits VERY snugly - absolutely zero slop, and I really like not having to worry about keeping up with more than one case. Also, at $29.95, it's cheaper than the two-case approach. The only criticism I have of this jacket is that when you want to convert from belt clip to sport use you have to snake the band through two loops on the backside of the case and over the little plastic belt clip receiver that protrudes from the back of the case. The process is a little tedious, but the end result is great. The unit feels very secure on my arm and it's easy to forget that it's there.

This jacket is a winner
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006F2WD:i_guess_we're_the_exception...:jeannie-linc
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
245084
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006F2WD
</asin>
<product_name>
Canon S530D Photo Printer: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
I guess we're the exception...
</title>
<date>
June 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Jeannie-Linc
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
N. MS, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
We've had this printer for almost two years. I do a good amount of printing, both color and b/w. While I do need to do cleanings more often with this printer, mine is not sucking up ink at an unreasonable rate at all. And it is very affordable. Photos don't always print well... the only photo paper I have found to work well with my S530D was very the glossy trial pack that came with it when I bought it. No other photo paper has done well at all, so I suggest theirs. This is the best printer we have had in 10 years, and belive me I've thrown my share out the window! I can offer THIS advice to owners of ANY printers. Always use the power switch ON THE PRINTER to turn it on off, never use the power strip switch, or the switch from properties. For some reason doing so supposedly wastes ink? I don't get it, but I've always followed that advice and this printer has been an absolute gem for us. Good Luck! Jeanni
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00007LTAU:product_desciption_could_be_more_specific:r._david_maurer_"david_maurer"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
246675
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00007LTAU
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus PA050U USB 2.0 High-Speed Hub (4-port): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Product desciption could be more specific
</title>
<date>
May 28, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
R. David Maurer "David Maurer"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
St. Louis metro area
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I,ve seen complaints about the ac adapter you "must" plug in. Hey guys, try it without an outside energy source, I just hope I,m not gonna fry something but it seems to work fine just plugged into a powered USB port. I have a VERY high end system though with wattage to sprare, but no more PCI slots, Damn 7900 512 gtx graphics cards, why do 2 of em have to take up so much room. Oh well, trade offs are a bi---, but a reality and 7 extra USB slots are awfully nice
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BONJXU:great_product_for_the_price:r._mutha
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
246748
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BONJXU
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk Sansa M230 512 MB MP3 Player (Blue): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great product for the price
</title>
<date>
November 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
R. Mutha
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Houston, Texas United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I am extrememly happy with this one.  For the price, it delivers well.  The voice recorder works well.  My key need was to record lectures and listening to them.  Worked out very well
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007Z1M50:excellent_mouse:p._mcclory
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
247324
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007Z1M50
</asin>
<product_name>
Logitech MX518 Gaming Optical Mouse - Metal: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
excellent mouse
</title>
<date>
November 2, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
P. MCCLORY
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Pittsburgh, PA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I've been a gamer for almost 20 years.  This is the best mouse I've ever owned.  It is fast, accurate, well formed and constructed.  I would definitely recommend it.
The DPI adjustment is a nice touch.  I prefer corded mice due to cordless being to heavy, this mouse is just right
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00068NF0I:it's_a_good_little_unit:k._mackeigan_"uber_chk"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
252330
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00068NF0I
</asin>
<product_name>
JVC KT-SR2000 Plug 'n' Play Sirius Satellite Radio Receiver: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
It's a good little unit
</title>
<date>
June 7, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
K. Mackeigan "UBER CHK"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have two seperate units.  One hardwired to my car, and the other is the JVC unit.  I hooked it directly into the audio (aux) ports of my Radio, rather than use an fm station.  It works great, the sound quality is excellent as well - (and my radio is so old it play's 8-tracks!!!!).  I did notice that the unit tends to run a bit warm to hot.  I agree with the previous reviews, that it is something that JVC needs to look into, perhaps it is simply a matter of a "heat sink-er" not being in specs, as yet, I have encountered no problems (having had the JVC unit for 1.5 years)  No matter.  As to the commercial free: Sirius (which I have had a subscription to for the past 4 years) has commercial free radio, though the news stations and a few others do have commercials.  Those stations are clearly defined as being in the commercial block.  The music stations are 100% free of commercial. 

All in all a damn cheap price to pay for avoidance of all those really irritating DJ's, commerical's, and lack of variety in stations!  ~Cheers!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00000JPPI:works_with_dvd_recorders,_too!:larry_j._commons
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
257016
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00000JPPI
</asin>
<product_name>
Maxell DVD-LC DVD Lens Cleaner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
11 of 13
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Works with DVD Recorders, too!
</title>
<date>
September 6, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Larry J. Commons
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Arlington, TX USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I was about to retire an old standalone DVD recorder, because it would no longer let me create menus or finalize discs.  I bought this lens cleaner and -- voila! -- the recorder is working again.  Super easy to use (it's simply a DVD that you insert into your machine, and the menus tell you what to do).  Highly recommended
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008VFAF:does_what_it_says:l._severson_"amurderone"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
257136
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008VFAF
</asin>
<product_name>
D-Link QuickMedia DUB-H7 7-Port USB 2.0 Hub: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Does what it says
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
L. Severson "amurderone"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
IL, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
IT's a USB hub. All I ask is that it works. It does.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002OD0N8:worth_it:freddy_mogollon_"safarrancho"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
269479
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002OD0N8
</asin>
<product_name>
Apple M9339LL/C iPod Stereo Connectivity Kit: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Worth it
</title>
<date>
August 19, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Freddy Mogollon "safarrancho"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Venezuela
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Is it expensive?, yes it is!!!
However, I was conecting my Ipod mini to my speakers with two cables, mini jack cable and power cable and it was very unconfortable to do every day. The dock is a great solution for this issue. Now, I just insert the Ipod mini in the dock. Easy, fast and confortable. Additionaly, I can read easyly the song I am listening to
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000VYJOM:usb_2_reader:kimberly_a._mccoubrey
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
272726
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000VYJOM
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar Media RW020-001 USB 2.0 CompactFlash Reader: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
USB 2 Reader
</title>
<date>
October 22, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Kimberly A. Mccoubrey
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Chicopee, MA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Quick reader, poor design. It does a great job copying images to my Mac, but the flimsy lid is a piece of poo-poo. It stays on tight, which is good, until you try to open it. The force required to open it pulls the lid completely off making the ball-groove hinges useless. It's only a matter of time until the weak arms containing the hinges snap off, leaving the reader exposed to the elements
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000D8Q8W:adorama_slinger_bag_**_great_**:dr._ronald_berman_"photoaz"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
273016
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000D8Q8W
</asin>
<product_name>
Adorama Slinger Bag, Single Strap Backpack / Shoulder Bag, Navy.: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Adorama Slinger Bag ** GREAT **
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Dr. Ronald Berman "PhotoAz"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Scottsdale, Az
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I purchased the Adorama Slinger Bag after first purchasing the Tamrac Velocity 5.  The Tamrac bag is a nice bag and can be worn as either a shoulder bag or a waist bag. Unfotunately, it lacked sufficient support when worn as waist bag and did not have an attached pouch to carry a water bottle.  The Slinger Bag addressed both of these deficiencies.  When worn as a waist bag, it also uses the shoulder strap to keep the bag firmly in place which also helps to balance the weight of the bag.  There are two water pouches on the Slinger Bag (which is a real requirement as I live in Arizona).

The Adorama Slinger Bag is a great travel bag. It is light weight and has great utility.  I highly recommend it.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002ZAIMI:works_great:b._rivers
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
275353
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002ZAIMI
</asin>
<product_name>
Apple M9837LL/A iPod USB Power Adapter: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Works Great
</title>
<date>
August 25, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
B. Rivers
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Great for if you are not near a computer and need to charge your Ipo
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007SL4IW:no_problems_here:obrien_admirer_"cscoder"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
277934
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007SL4IW
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex DVD+R 16x 4.7GB 100 Pack Spindle: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
No Problems Here
</title>
<date>
October 22, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
OBrien Admirer "cscoder"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I've never had any problems with Memorex DVD's or CD's. When I was ordering and read some of the reviews here, I had to go back and look at what I was using to make sure. I've always taken it for granted and only posted this review to counteract some of the negative ones. I don't know why some users are having problems, but these DVD's always worked great for me, and I record on average over one a day
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007TC38G:reliable!:j._welch
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
278652
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007TC38G
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk Cruzer Mini 2GB USB 2.0 Flash Drive (SDCZ2-2048-A10, Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Reliable!
</title>
<date>
November 19, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Welch
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Monee, IL United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I agree that this drive can be a little slow, but it hasn't caused a problem for me. I keep copies of many files (about 1 GB total) related to a large project at work on mine. When I first copied all the files to the drive it took a couple of minutes, but now I just make changes or updates to the individual files and the write times are short enough that I don't even notice them (just a second or two). I also seemlessly work on the files on both a PC at work and a Mac at home. 

To me the best feature is the reliability. Between my husband and I, we've had several Cruzer Minis in various sizes and each one has worked great, even through accidental abuse. One of his 512 MB drives accidently went through the washing machine. We thought the data was gone, but when it dried out, it worked fine. Just today I found my 2 GB drive at the bottom of the dryer; it had been left in a pocket and had gone through both the washing machine and dryer. Yep, it still worked! I'm buying a new one to replace it (just in case) because I don't know it there might be some long-term effects from the water and heat, but I'll keep using this one for less important applications. Changes are good, though, that it'll never have a problem. These things are amazingly reliable
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000CD0B7:great_addition_to_a_great_camera:the_smiths_"sann3187"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
287614
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000CD0B7
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDCFH-1024-901 1 GB Ultra II CompactFlash Card (Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
great addition to a great camera
</title>
<date>
August 7, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
The Smiths "sann3187"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Front Range, CO, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I recently ordered this for a week long trip I was planning to Olympic National Park.  WOW what a great find.  I didn't have to worry about how many pictures my memory card would hold and could just snap away.  I think it also increased my shutter speed too. I would definitely recommend this to anyone and have actually
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000095SB4:just_what_i_wanted:julie_husth_"jb_in_nj"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
289782
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000095SB4
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony MDR-IF240RK Wireless Headphone System: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Just what I wanted
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Julie Husth "JB in NJ"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New jersey
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought these as a gift for my husband to watch TV late at night without disturbing me.  He loves them.  The sound is fine and the headphones are comfortable. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000GAUZFO:the_amazing_motivator!:dawn_m._gendron_"d._gendron"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
290255
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000GAUZFO
</asin>
<product_name>
Nike + iPod Sport Kit: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
The amazing motivator!
</title>
<date>
November 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Dawn M. Gendron "D. Gendron"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Surrey, ND
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The Nike+ system has really been a good motivator for me. As a new runner, I need all the motivation and positive reinforcement I can get. The challenges and goals are a good way to keep on track as well.

I didn't buy the Nike+ shoes - I use mine with the Marware Sportsuit Relay set up. It's a great system and a lot cheaper than spending $100 for a pair of running shoes when I already have a couple good pairs in the closet. 

Both products are highly recommended
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000058DRT:works_perfectly!:farty_a._stankus
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
291145
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000058DRT
</asin>
<product_name>
SimpleTech STI-SD/128 128MB SecureDigital Card: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Works perfectly!
</title>
<date>
November 2, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Farty A. Stankus
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Boston, MA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I've had this card for about 1 1/2 years now and it has performed flawlessly. It has seen thousands of photos (no exaggeration!) on my digital camera and now holds data/mp3s for my palm too. Did you know you can pop your SD card out of a camera and into a palm to view photos? I just learned this. Anyway it's a nice product and I'm about to get another SimpleTech with 512 megs or higher if they have one. If you are new to SD memory, always get more storage than you need because eventually you'll buy something that will use one (camera, handhelds, cell phones, etc. -- note that many cell phones use a smaller "MiniSD")
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000A3WS8O:bad_timing_on_my_behalf...:b._mccafferty_"podperv"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
295056
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000A3WS8O
</asin>
<product_name>
Apple 60 GB iPod video Black (5th Generation): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Bad timing on my behalf...
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
B. Mccafferty "podperv"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
NH
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is a perfect mp3 player. I had the 40Gb model before this and needed a bit of extra room. You can't ask for anything more than this. It does everything an mp3 player should, and more (podcasts, videos, photos). I bought the 60 a couple of weeks before the 80 was released at the same price. Bad timing on my behalf..
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006I5FQ:works_great,_good_price:auction_queen_"love_them_bargains!!!!"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
296187
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006I5FQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar PD-128-231 128 MB JumpDrive Portable USB Flash Drive: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
works great, good price
</title>
<date>
March 18, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Auction Queen "Love them bargains!!!!"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Gardena, CA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Great price for a 128MB jump drive, works perfectt for my daughters college work, such a good price I bought 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006B91Z:it's_called_the_ultra_mini_for_a_reason!:c._dray
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
301710
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006B91Z
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus PA055U 4 Port USB 1.1 Ultra Mini Hub: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
It's called the Ultra Mini for a reason!
</title>
<date>
March 17, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
C. Dray
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Sacramento, CA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This review pertains specifically to the Targus PAUH217U 4 Port Ultra Mini USB 2.0 Hub. 
The cord is about 2.5 feet long - long enough to reach from my pc, which sits on the ground, to the top of the desk. It has a cable which is split into two USB plugs - one just to transmit data, the second to power the unit. The second plug does not need to be used unless you plan on using some heavy-duty hardware, and if so what are you buying a hub called the ultra mini for anyways? If you insist on trying to run a blow dryer off the thing, then it does have an input for a separate power source, which you will have to buy separately. 

In short, If you have an old school machine with USB ports which are inaccessible /inconvenient to use, this little hub will give you quick access while taking up minimal space on your desk
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000CD08M:great_choice_for_my_nikon_d70:dave_"climbing_yggdrasil"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
306533
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000CD08M
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDCFH-512-901 512 MB Ultra II CompactFlash Card (Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great choice for my Nikon D70
</title>
<date>
October 12, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Dave "climbing_yggdrasil"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Sterling, VA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this card about 10 months ago to go with my Nikon D70 and I've certainly had no regrets. I haven't tried pushing the card to its limits to see how quickly it can write, but it's been plenty fast enough to keep up with me in single-shot mode. The card is always ready when I am. Downloading from the card to computer via my SanDisk Imagemate is fast too.

I like it so much, I'm buying a second one today
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007UVYI0:magnificent!!!:alberto_white
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
308563
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007UVYI0
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDSDM-512-A10M Mini SD 512 MB Flash Memory Card (Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Magnificent!!!
</title>
<date>
March 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Alberto White
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Must say that the item was better than I expected. Thanks to the seller and will buy again!!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009O5MWI:awesome_value!!_highly_recommend!:s._tucker_"dance_freak"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
314657
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009O5MWI
</asin>
<product_name>
Philips HTS3400D/37 Home Theater System with DVD Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Awesome Value!! Highly Recommend!
</title>
<date>
February 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
S. Tucker "dance freak"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this system recently after my Panasonic DVD Surround System broke. I was a little leary about this system since other reviewers have mentioned a hissing noise here on Amazon and other sites for that matter. But I couldn't find anything like this value and decided I could just take it back if I didn't like it. Well, I love it! The sound is great! Subwoofer is awesome! I do not hear a hissing noise at all. This sounds so much better than my Panasonic which broke and that I had paid $100 more for
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009R9BJ:great_idea!:brian_koch_"aspiring_photographer"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
330213
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009R9BJ
</asin>
<product_name>
Op/Tech Hood Hat - Medium (4.0" diameter +/- .25"): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great Idea!
</title>
<date>
November 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Brian Koch "Aspiring Photographer"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
MI United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have been looking for an easier way to protect the front my my lens without having to either take off my lens hood or trying to fumble around with the lens cap with the hood still on.  Op/Tech came up with the solution!  All you have to do is stretch the proper size hood hat over the hood and everything is protected and ready to go.  Super easy to take off, putting on takes a little more time, but you never miss a picture putting it on anyway.  Basically this is an inexpensive way to add some extra insurance against getting dirt, water, etc on your front element while you are walking around looking for shots.  It is also very flexible and easy to stick in a pouch or pocket when not being used
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000A5TBM8:sony_dru-810a:tammera_moore_"llcd"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
333247
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000A5TBM8
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony DRU-810A Internal Double/Dual Layer and Dual Format DVD Burner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Sony DRU-810A
</title>
<date>
November 3, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Tammera Moore "llcd"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
 I had owned an LG burner and from the time I got it, it never worked right. I must have made 60 or 70 coasters before I decided that it was'nt the media, it was the crappy LG brand burner. I was really afraid because there are so many burners on the market and all of them claim to be good, but as I found out with my LG experience, that is not always true. 
 My brother has an older model Sony burner and although his is slow, it has made a handful of coasters in the 5 years that he has owned it, so I took a chance and purchased the Sony DRU-810A. That was the best decision I could have made. I will never buy another brand burner other that Sony brand. I have had this burner about 7 or 8 months. I am a very heavy burner and I have not made one coaster. 
 One thing I loved about my brother's Sony burner is that I could use any brand of media. The same thing is true of the DRU-810A. I don't have to worry about where the media was manufactured or who the maker is. This burner loves everything. I had looked at the Plextor brand, but I did'nt want to pay $100.00 and I looked at NEC brand, LiteOn, BenQ. etc., but I am so happy that I passed on them all and got the Sony. It burns super fast. Some people say that it is loud, but it's not loud to me.
 I got my burner from Tiger Direct for $50.00. My sister's computer came with a crappy LG brand burner too and for almost 2 years she has not been able to burn at all because she gets nothing but coasters too, so for Christmas I am buying her a Sony DUR-810A so she can finally burn some movies. For my money, this is the best burner bar none.

</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00065AO0K:no_problem.:ernesto_sabogal_gomez
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
336384
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00065AO0K
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDSDH-1024-901 1 GB Ultra II Secure Digital Memory Card (Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
No problem.
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Ernesto Sabogal Gomez
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Bogot, Colombia
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought it for my Canon S3 IS. First I tried it without formatting and fill it up with photos and video and no problems. Then I did the suggested format by Canon and it worked the same: perfect. Fast enough to cope with the demands of the camera; haven't any problem of corruption. 

I've been tempted to buy another one. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006IC4E:great_book_holder:cherie
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
339376
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006IC4E
</asin>
<product_name>
Fellowes 21100 Book Lift Holder (Silver): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great Book Holder
</title>
<date>
July 27, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Cherie
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
dont be like me and wait until you start to feel some neck strain from hours of studying hunched over before buying one
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I read the other reviews on this bookholder and wasn't so sure about it.  However, after buying and trying it out, I have no regrets.  Don't know why I waited soo long to get one (dont be like me and wait until you start to feel some neck strain from hours of studying hunched over before buying one).  Although made of plastic, it is very study and has nice rubber feet to keep it from sliding.  The clips on the bottom work very well to keep pages open and you can change how firm or loose you want it to hold.  Unlike other models, this one folds completely flat so you can carry it in your backpack between books.  I have used it mostly for softcover textbooks and have no problem
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009YUPS:it_definitely_works..._and_its_cheap:sean_malowney
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
340468
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009YUPS
</asin>
<product_name>
ADS Tech DVD Express 2.0 (USBAV-701): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
It definitely works... and its cheap
</title>
<date>
July 29, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Sean Malowney
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Seattle, WA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Look, for a bargain-basement product, what do you expect?  First, you expect it to work, and I can confirm it definitely does work.

When plugged in to USB, it signals XP correctly.  The driver software is very tolerant.  You can install it at any time and there is never a resource conflict or problems with the system recognizing the device.  So installation is a 5 minute process.

Next comes the capture and initial encoding.  Well, the software is a bit lame as far as features and GUI.  Typical.  But it absolutely saves in MPEG2 / DVD format just as you'd need it to for making DVDs of all your Dish Network or PS2 or VHS content.  

The frame rate is full on 30 fps.  It takes an SVIDEO or standard RCA video signal.  Both are just fine in quality.  The resolutions are not that great... but its passable for DVD when you crank it up.  Don't think you can encode some Blu-Ray quality MPEG with this though.

As far as the overall durability of the product, I've literally left mine plugged into the wall and running for about 1 year straight.  It gets hot, but its never so much as flickered or needed reset.  

Bottom line?  This thing is like a kids toy- its cheesy but tough as nails.  Get it for your first analog signal MPEG encoder.  Its a good value.



</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000B3AKR:cheap_option:b._finzi
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
341532
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000B3AKR
</asin>
<product_name>
Viking USB00512L2 512 MB USB 2.0 Portable Mini Flash Memory Device: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Cheap option
</title>
<date>
February 23, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
B. Finzi
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Brazil
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The cheapest option I found at the time but an excelent pen drive. Small and with a good style
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000DK3I4:things_to_consider_if_you're_getting_a_2gb_card:anonymous
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
342502
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000DK3I4
</asin>
<product_name>
Kingston 512 MB Secure Digital Card (SD/512): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Things to consider if you're getting a 2GB card
</title>
<date>
November 11, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Anonymous
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I purchased the 2GB Elite Pro SD card but found out that my older SimpleTech FlashLink card reader is not able to recognize the card under WinXP SP2 with and without the most recent SimpleTech drivers. I don't have another card reader for my computer, but the pictures recorded on it by my digital camera can be viewed on my PDA so I assume that it's the card reader. Shortly afterwards, I also discovered that Kingston makes a combo kit that includes their USB 2.0 SD/MMC reader for a bit less in price than the card alone.

I also noticed the ATP line of 60x and 150x SD cards. I have no experience with their products, but their SD cards are potted versus placed in a plastic shell. They tout their cards as being more rugged and waterproof. I'm very careful and have not had any flash cards fail on me, but with the rising capacities and smaller form factors, I will consider the ATP cards in the future.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001YM07G:a_great_addition:r._j._gravelle_"johnnyg"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
347415
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001YM07G
</asin>
<product_name>
Xbox Cordless Precision Controller: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
A Great addition
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
R. J. Gravelle "JohnnyG"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
WDC
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I thought when I up graded to the plasma things couldn't get any better I was wrong the wireless is the cherry on top I love this thin
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001CNMFM:good_compact_flash_card.:n.e.
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
349554
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001CNMFM
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDCFH-2048-901 2GB ULTRA II CF Card (Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Good compact flash card.
</title>
<date>
November 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
N.E.
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Los Angeles
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is a good compact flash card.  This is faster than most cameras can handle so there was no real reason to go with faster cards that are much more expensive. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000AKA8Y:cool_your_laptop_:thomas_hinojosa_"tomhin"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
350588
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000AKA8Y
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus PA248U Tornado Notebook Chill Pad: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
COOL YOUR LAPTOP 
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
THOMAS HINOJOSA "TOMHIN"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
VICTOR VALLEY, CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
GREAT ITEM, POWERED OFF LAPTOP ITS FANS WORK QUIETLY TO KEEP LAPTOP COOL. SO YOU CAN ACTUALLY US YOUR LAP, WITHOUT FEAR OF OVERHEATING YOUR COMPUTER. AN INEXPENSIVE SOLUTION TO PREVENTING COSTLY REPAIRS. WISH I'D PURCHASED EARLIER AS I ALREADY FRIED MY CD/DVD DRIVE AND HAD TO REPLACE THEM. GOOD PRODUCT TARGUS
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00070QI1S:things_to_consider_if_you're_getting_a_2gb_card:anonymous
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
352945
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00070QI1S
</asin>
<product_name>
Kingston 512MB Elite Pro Secure Digital Memory Card ( SD/512-S ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Things to consider if you're getting a 2GB card
</title>
<date>
November 11, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Anonymous
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I purchased the 2GB Elite Pro SD card but found out that my older SimpleTech FlashLink card reader is not able to recognize the card under WinXP SP2 with and without the most recent SimpleTech drivers. I don't have another card reader for my computer, but the pictures recorded on it by my digital camera can be viewed on my PDA so I assume that it's the card reader. Shortly afterwards, I also discovered that Kingston makes a combo kit that includes their USB 2.0 SD/MMC reader for a bit less in price than the card alone.

I also noticed the ATP line of 60x and 150x SD cards. I have no experience with their products, but their SD cards are potted versus placed in a plastic shell. They tout their cards as being more rugged and waterproof. I'm very careful and have not had any flash cards fail on me, but with the rising capacities and smaller form factors, I will consider the ATP cards in the future.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001ZIYQ6:excellent_piece_of_work_!:scott_"mang"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
356451
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001ZIYQ6
</asin>
<product_name>
Hagiwara Sys-Com HNT-MSW1 802.11b Memory Stick Wireless Lan Card for Sony's CLIE Handheld: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Excellent Piece of Work !
</title>
<date>
December 29, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Scott "Mang"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
M'sia
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Works like a charm, the Wi-Fi sniffer in the software is definitely a big plus ! You can get details of the connection i.e. connection strength, AP name and etc. Worth every penny 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002IWC9C:a_great_buy!:s._sharma_"maverick"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
357296
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002IWC9C
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony BCG-34HE4 Super-Quick Worldwide Battery Charger with 4 AA NiMH Batteries: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
A great buy!
</title>
<date>
November 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
S. Sharma "maverick"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Texas
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I purchased this product 2 years back and it is still working without any problem. I use the batteries mostly for my digital camera and have no complaints so far. Highly recommend this product
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EOMXM0:excellent_purchase_...:anthony_s._cristobal_"maverick"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
360409
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EOMXM0
</asin>
<product_name>
Kingston 2GB Secure Digital Memory Card ( SD/2GB ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Excellent purchase ...
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Anthony S. Cristobal "maverick"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Hendersonville, TN
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The initial flash card that came with my camera was far too short to save pictures.  When I went surfing for another flash card with some depth, Amazon really came through for me and the price was excellent. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008EM7U:thought_i_needed_a_new_dvd_player:steven_prettyman
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
361797
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008EM7U
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex CD/DVD-Player Laser-Lens Cleaner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Thought I needed a new DVD player
</title>
<date>
August 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Steven Prettyman
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
My DVD player was ready to be thrown out, until I saw this product on amazon.  My DVD player wouldn't even load a DVD.  It kept saying "please check disc". After loading this disc, my DVD player has worked perfectly ever since.  Don't spent $30 on one of these "clean up discs". This one does the job
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000AKVHF:memory_card_reader:david_l._gee
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
366206
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000AKVHF
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDDR-88-A15 8-in-1 USB 2.0 Hi-speed Reader (Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
memory card reader
</title>
<date>
September 7, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
David L. Gee
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Yakima, WA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This memory card reader worked like a charm for me.  We've used both SD and Sony memory sticks in it with absolutely no problems
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006BBY4:kingston_128mb_memory_card:ralph_w._bolt_"stingray75"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
367089
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006BBY4
</asin>
<product_name>
Kingston 128 MB Secure Digital Memory Card (SD/128): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Kingston 128mb Memory Card
</title>
<date>
February 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Ralph W. Bolt "Stingray75"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Lester,WV
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This card has all of the memory space required for my personal use. I would recommemd it to others
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00093IIRA:excellent_universal:thomas_j._easter
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
369282
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00093IIRA
</asin>
<product_name>
Harmony 880 Remote Control: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Excellent universal
</title>
<date>
November 13, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Thomas J. Easter
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Washington, DC  USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Overall this is a very good remote.  It replaced 5 of my remotes, which is all except my Bose, which is RF controlled.  It even replaced my Windows Media Center Edition remote and works with my PS2 with no problems.
My negatives for this device are that the layout is a little less comfortable and intuitive than some of my other remotes and the default functions aren't necessarily the most used functions therefore requiring additional time to set-up.  These negative however are more than acceptable when you remember that it works with so many devices.  I am definitely happy with this remote and would undoubtably purchase again
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00093IIRA:excellent_remote:rodney
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
369286
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00093IIRA
</asin>
<product_name>
Harmony 880 Remote Control: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
excellent remote
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Rodney
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
dallas,texas
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
easiest remote to program. has tremendous ability to tweek. will keep recommending to all my customers
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009Q4U7Y:pleased_as_punch:nathan_wiehe
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
370892
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009Q4U7Y
</asin>
<product_name>
iAudio X5 20 GB Portable Multimedia Player with FM Tuner and Voice Recorder (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Pleased as Punch
</title>
<date>
August 3, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Nathan Wiehe
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Raleigh, NC United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
After doing a fair amount of Internet research about MP3 players and their features I was under the impression that I would go with an iPod.  Having been in the computer industry for almost 15 years I have never been fond of the Mac and have always been a little biased towards PC's.  This added to my reticence to own a Mac product and the growing complaints about service on the iPod being a 'bit' over priced I forged on.

I started reading through all of the reviews I could find on the Internet and as always, found a wealth of them here on Amazon.  To my dismay all the reviews I could find on product names I knew absolutely trashed the products they were reviewing which scared me immensely.  Thats is, until I got to the iAudio line.  The reviews were almost all positive and the complaints that were present were things I could easily overlook.  I love the control, I am big guy with big hands and I have rarely, if ever, pushed the control and not had the result I was intending.

I have had my iAudio X5 for over a month and I have nothing bad to say in the least.  I am an avid Linux user and it works flawlessly with Linux, the sound quality is phenomenal, except the ear buds that came with mine have a lot of static in them so get rid of those.  The FM tuner is great (you wont get that on an iPod).  I travel a lot and I pipe my X5 through my car stereo using a cassette tape converter plugged into the stereo out port.

What else can I say, this is a great product with great features and it looks good too!  I also bought a case from zCover which fits the purpose but I think that as time goes on some better more versatile cases will come to market.

A Satisfied Custome
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000AY0HTU:not_just_for_gaming:richard_doyle_"web_lacky"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
371485
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000AY0HTU
</asin>
<product_name>
Logitech G15 Gaming Keyboard: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Not just for gaming
</title>
<date>
November 3, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Richard Doyle "web lacky"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Fairfax, VA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this keyboard originally for the LCD screen and the wide range of possibilities that exist with programming it for various games I play.  I was suprised to learn that this is more than a pretty keyboard with an LCD hanging off of it.  It's the best-feeling keyboard I've ever owned.  The keys take just the right amount of pressure to operate, and the switch to disable the windows key is a welcome feature.  The backlighting is bright, day or night, and the programmable G-keys make executing complicated key combinations in games or business applications a thing of the past.  Highly recommended
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009V9I80:good_but_not_great_for_person_who_is_renting_apartment:ghost
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
376332
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009V9I80
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony DAV-FX100W Wireless Home Theater Dream System: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
9 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Good but not great for person who is renting apartment
</title>
<date>
March 26, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Ghost
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Philadelphia, PA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is a great piece of hardware, the wireless rear speakers was a big selling point for me. But in my apartment I would like to have more control over the subwoofer speaker, it's volume slider is hidden in a settings menu there is no separate knob for it on the speaker itself. The bass sound from subwooferis overbearing at default. The other thing is that I would like to be able to have better control over the sound itself with an equalizer. That's not going to happen with this system, you can't change that easily. And yes the 5 disk changer is slow. The maximum volume setting doesn't seem that loud to me, but then I have the decibal settings at default. All the sound quality you expect from a theater system is here, it has all the flavors. Hooking it up to an xbox directly didnt work the way I'd like it too, but I only tried RCA and not the digital. I have a sony 32" Wega and I had the xbox patch to it and then routed to the DAV-FX100 reciever. That works like a charm, even with 5.1 sound from XBOX. One huge complaint I have is the shielding for the mid and left and right front speakers are not the best. I see a bit of haze from the magnetic fields from both the front 3 speakers, even had to elevate my center channel for fear that would permanently damage the tube on my TV. There is mention of this problem in the manual but that should be on the front page not the middle of the manual! Beware! Four Stars
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00032Q3WY:true_plug-and-play:j._a._maglasang_"zargouz"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
378824
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00032Q3WY
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar Media MULTI CARD READER ( RW022-001 ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
12 of 12
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
True plug-and-play
</title>
<date>
May 7, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
J. A. Maglasang "zargouz"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
OH USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I used Lexar Media Multi Card REader in my P2120 Fujitsu laptop via a USB 2 PC-Card adapter.  It's truly plug-and-play without any need of drivers in Windows XP
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000COCQYC:i've_not_used_it_yet_but_its_a_good_idea_to_stay_protected:bill_sudderth
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
379135
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000COCQYC
</asin>
<product_name>
2-Year Replacement Plan for Electronics Products $25 to $49.99: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
I've not used it yet but its a good idea to STAY PROTECTED
</title>
<date>
November 8, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Bill Sudderth
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Murphy,, North Carolina USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I like to purchase service or replacement contracts on all my electronics needs, just set back and relax....YOUR COVERED. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002ZAIM8:worth_the_price:c._murakami
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
382806
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002ZAIM8
</asin>
<product_name>
Apple 1 GB iPod Shuffle: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Worth The Price
</title>
<date>
November 23, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
C. Murakami
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Los Angeles, CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
If you are looking for an inexpensive iPod, then I would recommend this. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001Q5SFU:pretty_useful_product:bharat_t._madhavan_"maddy"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
383248
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001Q5SFU
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus PAUH216U 4 Port Slim USB 2.0 Hub: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Pretty useful product
</title>
<date>
October 21, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Bharat T. Madhavan "maddy"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
RI, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
You will appreciate this product only if you don't have enough USB ports. In my case, I had plenty of ports, but needed an extension cable, which would help me in plugging the flash drives, whithout bending down and plunging into the cave of wires(I keep my CPU, under the table).The only complaint I have is the the wire lenght is not long enough.
Overall good value for price
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00029BQ98:samsung_lt-p1545_15"_flat-panel_lcd_tv:edward_j._libucha
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
386031
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00029BQ98
</asin>
<product_name>
Samsung LT-P1545 15" Flat-Panel LCD TV: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Samsung LT-P1545 15" Flat-Panel LCD TV
</title>
<date>
January 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Edward J. Libucha
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
First, I would buy it again if I needed to.  This 15" takes up less space on the kitchen counter, i.e., speakers are on the bottom. Second, picture and sound are excellent, i.e, clear.
I would not buy this item if I wanted a true VESA mount to monitor configuration.  The stand, not the monitor, has the screw holes for the VESA wall mount.  Not enough or clear info in the description. However, it is just as easy to turn on the counter as on the wall.  If you need counter space then buy something else.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BVB2FK:intuos_6x11_:giuseppe_gallina_"magnetos"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
390788
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BVB2FK
</asin>
<product_name>
Wacom Intuos3 6X11 Pen Tablet: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
intuos 6x11 
</title>
<date>
August 17, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
giuseppe gallina "magnetos"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
brooklyn, new york United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought the intuos 6x11 pen tablet couple weeks ago and I use it
almost every day so far so good, I don't expect to have any problems with it.
I used to have a small wacom graphire and I used for years then unfortunately the pen broke so now I own a new one 
the only advice I can give to you is to keep it clean, wipe it out every now and then with a wet cloth 

jo
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009RGLSE:works_great_with_my_palm_tx:julie_l.
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
391083
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009RGLSE
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk 2 GB SD Memory Card ( SDSDB-2048-A10, Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
works great with my palm TX
</title>
<date>
November 5, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Julie L.
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Los Angeles, CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I love my 2 GB SD memory card. I use it all the time and have had no problems with it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009R6VB:hand_strap_e1:kwong_ng_"ngboy"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
392276
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009R6VB
</asin>
<product_name>
Hand Strap E1: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Hand Strap E1
</title>
<date>
March 15, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Kwong Ng "NgBoy"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Francisco, CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Alot Better Then Wrapping The Neck Strap Around Your Arm Or Hand...
It Really Depends On What Kind Of Photography You Do. I Shoot At Night Clubs And Weight Can Add Up. I Have A Canon Rebel XT, Hand Grip With 2 Batties, Canon 550EX Flash, And 50mm F/1.4 Or 17-40mm F/2.8
It Feels Alot Better Using The Hand Strap...
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007PGADE:great_dvd_media:joel_laika
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
394959
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007PGADE
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex DVD+R 16x 4.7GB 50 Pack Spindle: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great DVD media
</title>
<date>
July 15, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Joel Laika
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have burned over 100 of these in the past 6 months, I have only had 1 burn badly.  Haven't found a dvd player yet that they won't play in
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BP50AY:great_deal:mark_m
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
403082
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BP50AY
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk Sansa M240 1 GB MP3 Player (Silver): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great Deal
</title>
<date>
November 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Mark M
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Marlton, NJ  USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I recently purchased this item and I am very happy with its performance and quality. I use it daily in the gym it delivers excellent sound and you dont even realize you have it on due to its light weight
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000050AQ7:perfect:irishmare
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
423389
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000050AQ7
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 32021926 Clear Slim Jewel Cases (25-Pack): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Perfect
</title>
<date>
February 25, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Irishmare
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
These boxes are half the size of regular cases, just right--not too bulky like the regular ones
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0008KL7B8:great_for_a_small_office:brian_p._walsh
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
425248
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0008KL7B8
</asin>
<product_name>
Philips MCM240/37 Micro Hi-fi System: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
9 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Great for a small office
</title>
<date>
August 2, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Brian P. Walsh
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Mamaroneck, New York United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I recently purchased this item for my wife who has a small office.  the reception on this unit is great.  Bieng in a steel building she is able to get all the local radio stations. The sound quality on it is perfect for a small room considering the price range it is in.  If you are looking for a booming sound this is not for you but it will provide a solid quality sound. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0003009AI:wacom_intuos3_9x12_usb_tablet_:stephanie_lee
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
425640
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0003009AI
</asin>
<product_name>
Wacom Intuos3 9X12 USB Tablet - Metallic Gray: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Wacom Intuos3 9X12 USB Tablet 
</title>
<date>
September 29, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Stephanie Lee
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is an awesome tablet! It has great pressure sensitivity and the pen allows for fantastic freehand drawing in programs like illustrator, photoshop and painter. The pen is a more natural feeling tool to use in these applications than a mouse. The size of the tablet allows you to get into greater detail without having to zoom in all the time.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00083Y4HO:fast_and_simple:a._perez
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
436769
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00083Y4HO
</asin>
<product_name>
IOGEAR Universal Memory Drive Hi-Speed USB 2.0 Memory Card Reader/Writer: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
fast and simple
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
A. PEREZ
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Santiago, Chile
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This device is great for carriying around with your camera, you can review and share the pictures with any PC with USB available, data can also be recorded and easily recovered.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001A06GW:can't_beat_this_price_anywhere_for_a_1gb:same_old_same_old_"monitress"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
450426
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001A06GW
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDSDB-1024-A10 1 GB Secure Digital Card (Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Can't beat this price anywhere for a 1gb
</title>
<date>
November 11, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Same Old Same Old "monitress"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Houston, TX  USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought a 1GB with my new camera because I was giving my other camera and it's 256 memory card to my sister.  The smaller card would fill quickly and I'd have to develope the pictures or deleat them.  I paid about $9.00 more for my card in Sept., and thought that was a deal.  Now, you can get this card for $20.00.  That's a steal for a 1 GB.  also, I like the little case provided to keep the card safe when I take it to the store to develope the pictures.  Love it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002IWCAQ:great_for_my_digital_camera:c._mack_lane_jr.
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
451444
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002IWCAQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony NH-AACE AA Rechargeable Batteries In Slide Case: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great for my digital camera
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
C. Mack Lane Jr.
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Houston, TX USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
These batteries have been awesome.  My digital camera uses 4 of them at a time and they last for 100's of photographs.  Flash recharge is very quick.  Highly recommended
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000092YQW:great_sound,_and_indestructible!:joel_loudermilk
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
459359
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000092YQW
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony MDR-EX71SL Fontopia In-The-Ear Headphones (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great sound, and indestructible!
</title>
<date>
November 19, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Joel Loudermilk
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Orlando, FL USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I've been using these earbuds for several months now, and they're far better than the ones that come with the iPod. They're more comfortable, and there's so much more bass, although as everyone else pointed out you have to push them way into your ears to get the bass.

My pair has gone through the washing machine twice and the dryer once, and they still sound just as good as the day I got them! (I did have to glue one of the earpieces back together, though.) I thought I'd certainly destroy them by getting them wet, but these things are industrial strength
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000092YQW:excellent_headphones:geoffrey_w._haynes_"g-off"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
459363
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000092YQW
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony MDR-EX71SL Fontopia In-The-Ear Headphones (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Excellent Headphones
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Geoffrey W. Haynes "G-off"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Washington, DC
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I am a mild audophile, and I love these headphones. They have great base response, treble, and isolation. If you listen to music on the bus on train while listening for your stop, don't get get these! You won't be able to hear a thing outside of the music
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009UDABW:pain_to_figure_out,_but_yes,_it_works!:discriminating_shopper_"discriminating_shopper"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
464188
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009UDABW
</asin>
<product_name>
ADS Tech Video Xpress USBAV-191-EF: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Pain to figure out, but yes, it works!
</title>
<date>
November 5, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Discriminating shopper "Discriminating shopper"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Kansas
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
You may as well pitch the instructions because they're worthless (and the only reason I'm not giving a 5-star rating for the ADS Tech Video Xpress).  I was about ready to pitch the product as well, after losing two evenings trying to figure out how to get it to work.  Ultimately, I gave up on relying solely on the program it came with, and I instead opted to try it on my Windows Movie Maker.  Yahoo!  Perseverance paid off!  Once I switched to Movie Maker, this tool worked great!  

To date, I've converted about a dozen videos of content to computer files that I was able to burn to DVDs.  I just leave my Xpress hooked up to the back of my television so I don't have to try to remember later how to hook it up again.  Doing that, I can connect my laptop to the Xpress and start the video converting process within 3-4 minutes.  My Movie Maker program takes over the entire process.  

The ADS Tech Video Xpress has been especially useful for me because I teach a college telecourse and often show edited video clips to my students.  Before purchasing Xpress, I had crudely edited videos that I was reluctant to use; my videos had lots of amateur stop/start points.  Using Movie Maker with Xpress, I was able to download these videos to my laptop, then easily edit them so transitions between stop and start points became smooth and seamless.  

Pretty cool.  I'm glad I took a chance on this product!

Below are hook-up and program instructions I've written to myself for easy reference later.  Hopefully they'll be of more help to you than the instructions that come with this product:

First, hook up the Video Xpress equipment as follows:
1.  S-cable (buy one, since it doesn't come with the VideoXpress) goes from the back of your television to the VideoXpress.  
2.  Use red/white/yellow cords running into the back of the VCR/DVD that is hooked up to your televion as follows:
- all three plug into the "video out" column
- all three plug into the VideoXpress tool at the other end.  
3.  The USB plug for the VideoXpress tool plugs into the back of the computer.

Next, open the Instant Video Xpress program and verify the settings are as follows:
- "NTSC M" for the video standard setting
- "640 x 480" and "60 FPS (VGA)" for video format
- "DVD, VCR, TV" for video source
- "Video composite" for video input

Under the program advanced settings:
- Low motion (TV, VCD, DVD)
- CPU support: "SSE3"
- Stereo system: "MTS"
- Video decoder: "video standard: NTSC_M"

Under properties within the program advanced settings:
- Stream format:  Video format: "NTSC_M"
- Frame rate: "59.940"
- Color space/compression: "YUY2"
- Outputs size: "640x480"

Finally, CLOSE the Instant Video Xpress program.  (Windows Movie Maker can't access the video until this program is closed.  And yes, it's silly to have to open it, make those setting changes, then close it, but Video Xpress won't work correctly unless you follow those setting steps.)

In case you need this information for Windows Movie Maker, the steps (in order) are as follows:
Under "File," click on "capture video."

Use the following settings:
- audio device set at: "USB2.0 Analog Audio Device"
- Video input source set at: "Composite"
Under Configure Video Capture Device:
- Video format: Video standard: "NTSC_M"
		   Frame rate: "29.970"
		   Color space/compression: "YUY2"
		   Output size: "640x480"

Under Camera settings:
- Deinterlace method: "Low motion (TV, VCD, DVD)"
- CPU support: "SSE3"
- Stereosystem: "MTS"

Under Video decoder: Video standard: "MTSC_M"
Signal detected: "1"
Lines detected: "525"
Then...

Give the file a name and indicate where to save it

Set it for "best quality" for playback.

Then "Start Capture."

If the Video Xpress is hooked up and running correctly, you should see on your computer monitor the video image of whatever is showing on television, but you will NOT hear the sound.  When you finish capturing and play it back, THEN you'll hear the sound.

I know, I know -- clear as mud.  But hey, it's better than the Xpress instructions!  :-
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000CFY7I:works_fine_for_all_electronics_goods:bibhas_patra
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
467626
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000CFY7I
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex High Performance AA Alkaline Batteries, 50 Pack: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Works fine for all electronics goods
</title>
<date>
August 22, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Bibhas Patra
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Its really works fine for my items as well as my son's toys. We both  are happy with this
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009MZ9UA:not_perfect__but_very_affordable_for_my_needs.:j._bogdon_"music_man"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
468484
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009MZ9UA
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 4.7Gb/16x DVD-R (50-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Not Perfect  but very affordable for my needs.
</title>
<date>
September 11, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Bogdon "music man"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have been using Memorex dvd-r blank media for more than a year and have gotten fine recordings with my new dvd player/recorder.  Not all of my recordings were successful, no product I know is 100% perfect, but the majority have been successful with Memorex dvd blank media.
This 50-pack spindle was purchased from Amazon because I know I can rely on them to give you the best in quality and value plus free shipping.   Moreover, I have never really been disappointed with anything purchased from Amazon.   
After trying many dvd-r blank media, I found Memorex dvd-r spindles to be affordable and reliable for a better than average performance.
 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EH4Y56:light_stereo,_great_for_price:fred
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
476793
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EH4Y56
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony MHCEC70 Mini Shelf System with 3-Disc CD Changer, Cassette Deck, and AM/FM Tuner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Light stereo, great for price
</title>
<date>
November 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Fred
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Cranbrook, BC
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Not quite as powerful as I was hoping for, but the sound is alright and in a small room it'll do fine.

Careful, there is no plug-in at the back, so you can only connect MP3 or auxiliary stuff through the little front jack.

Otherwise it's easy to use and pretty cool-looking... ideal for quiet listening, lame if you host a big party and need loud stuff
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001IXUEY:good_boombox_overall:ketan_shah
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
490922
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001IXUEY
</asin>
<product_name>
Panasonic RX-D29 CD / Radio / Cassette Boombox with MP3 CD Playback: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Good boombox overall
</title>
<date>
March 23, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Ketan Shah
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Raleigh - Durham, NC USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The pro and cons described by other reviews are valid. I was specifically looking for a boombox that has cassette, mp3, cd and radio capability. So didn't have much of an option but to get this one. I am impressed with the sound quality but agree that there could have been improvements related to interface and some of the functionality. Overall I think its a good buy.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000DLB91A:better_then_ipod's_arm_band!:jessica_mcgettigan_"jessica"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
495755
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000DLB91A
</asin>
<product_name>
Belkin F8Z060 iPod Nano Silicon Sleeve (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Better then iPOD's arm band!
</title>
<date>
November 14, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Jessica McGettigan "Jessica"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Living in Germany
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I LOVE this arm band. I have had it for about 6 months now. You dont have to take your iPOD out of the arm band to charge it or to hook it up to your computer. I also only use my iPOD for the gym, so its nice that this arm band provides great protection (better than iPOD's armbands because it fits snugly and wont scratch it when you put it on) as well as not coming off while working out.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00003G1RG:amazing_customer_service_though....:v._patwardhan_"camera_nut"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
499809
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00003G1RG
</asin>
<product_name>
Viking 128 MB CompactFlash Card (CF128M): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Amazing Customer Service though....
</title>
<date>
August 5, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
V. Patwardhan "Camera Nut"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
CA, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought the 128MB card 8-9 mnths ago. At first didnt notice it but the usable memory kept getting smaller! Finally it gave a 'Error Reading Card'  message and stopped working. Customer service at Viking was very very helpful and prompt. They replaced the card is 7 days. They also tried to retrieve some of the images that I had considered 'lost' in the card and sent me a CD with the images on it! I was impressed with the excellent support, but not too impressed that the card died so early in its life. Would I buy it again? Yes but likely go for keeping a backup card on hand at all times as well
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EH4Y3S:great_compact_stereo_system:vicki_sabo
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
501599
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EH4Y3S
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony CMT-NEZ30 Audio Micro System with CD Player, Cassette Deck, and AM/FM Tuner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
9 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great compact stereo system
</title>
<date>
August 11, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
VICKI SABO
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
BUFORD, GA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I'm very happy with this desktop system.  Great sound, great reception, great price
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000068IHH:everything_i_was_looking_for!:s._ingle
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
501687
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000068IHH
</asin>
<product_name>
Case Logic DMB-5 CD Sports Pack: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Everything I was looking for!
</title>
<date>
January 9, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
S. Ingle
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Indiana, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I am very pleased with this item. It is fits comfortably, holds my CD player snugly and has room for my ID, keys, extra batteries and CD's
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00007KDVJ:works_great,_poor/inaccurate_documentation:rcp
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
504185
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00007KDVJ
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys WAP54G Wireless-G Access Point: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Works Great, Poor/Inaccurate Documentation
</title>
<date>
September 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
RCP
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Note to Brian: The WAP54G *can* be configured as a bridge. I have two of them in just such a configuration. Took me about 10 minutes to set them up.
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
(Note to Brian: The WAP54G *can* be configured as a bridge. I have two of them in just such a configuration. Took me about 10 minutes to set them up.)

Major modes of operation are:

1. Wireless Access Point (its default set-up)
2. Wireless Client (connect a wired ethernet device via cable to the WAP54G and you now have a wireless ethernet device)
3. Wireless Repeater (extend range of wireless coverage)
4. Wireless Bridge (connect two ethernet networks without running a cable between them -- acts as one end of a "virtual" cable; you need two to get the job done)

A pair of wireless bridges is just what I needed but hesitated to buy the WAP54G because of Brian's comment that this wouldn't work. Because of my newness to the wireless world it took a bit of investigation to come to the conclusion that Brian was wrong. I bought a pair and they do work.

I rate it 4 instead of 5 stars for a few reasons.

1. I understand that higher-end, more expensive, equipment can be had with more range than this box. Gotta leave some room to rate more powerful equipment!
2. One must dig very deeply into the users guide (a PDF on the CD) to find the default IP address in order to configure this device. Luckily I had read elsewhere what that IP address is (192.168.1.245). Other manufacturers make this info readily available, even going so far as printing it on the device itself. This will be critical info to any Linux user. Also, the users guide says that the default userid for logging in is "admin". Well, it's not. The only allowed userid is an empty field. This had me going for a few minutes.
3. Something that 99% of the world won't care about -- I like to have more access to the firmware. For example other Linksys products allow one to telnet to the box and do low-level analysis of the box and the network it's attached to. I think there are third-party firmware loads that enable this
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00070QI1I:most_reviews_here__are_not_for_this_card:m._mann
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
505409
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00070QI1I
</asin>
<product_name>
Kingston 1GB SecureDigital Flash Card ( SD/1GB ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Most Reviews Here  Are Not for This Card
</title>
<date>
November 21, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
M. Mann
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Intermountain West
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This card is the 2 GB Ultimate 120X  It has a tested write speed 120 times 150kb/sec which exceeds 18 mb per second.  Frequently card manufacturers advertise their read speed, which is always much faster. Analyze your file size for pictures you take and the speed in mb/sec will tell you how many of those pictures you can store in one second.

That impacts time between pictures. For cameras, write speed is the most important, but the speed rating of the card doesn't necessarily tell you its write speed.  For music players and other devices, read speed may be more important.  So you might choose a different card depending on whether you intend to use it to play music or take pictures.  I'm currently shopping for SD cards for a camera with the capability to shoot 3 pictures per second with large file sizes.  In order not to slow the camera down, I need a fast card.  I have done some research and realized that the reviews here aren't necessarily even related to this particular card, but are for all different sizes and speeds of Kingston cards. Kingston has been in the memory business for a long time and they are conservative in their ratings.  This card is #1 on my list right now because of its tested write speed
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00070QI1I:great_product:johnny_chiu
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
505418
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00070QI1I
</asin>
<product_name>
Kingston 1GB SecureDigital Flash Card ( SD/1GB ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great product
</title>
<date>
November 6, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Johnny Chiu
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this memory card for my camera sd500.  At first, I was very dispointed when I only see 1gb on my laptop.  After googled around, I realized I need to update my laptop sd reader driver to recognized sd card that is over 1gb.  I'm able to see full 2gb after driver update.  Just make sure you update your device/laptop firmware/driver first
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000GP8448:what's_up_with_my_wheel:henry_sanchez
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
509781
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000GP8448
</asin>
<product_name>
Logitech G25 Racing Wheel: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 16
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
What's up with my wheel
</title>
<date>
October 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Henry Sanchez
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Santo Domingo, D.R.
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
 Same as everybody else, I ordered mine a couple of days back and it hasn't shipped...I want it!!!!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000658CH:expandable!:agus_suhendar_"goose7108"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
512537
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000658CH
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys USBHUB4C ProConnect Compact USB 4-Port Hub: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Expandable!
</title>
<date>
March 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Agus Suhendar "goose7108"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Cool! I can expand my-single-USB-port-laptop more flexible.
From single peripheral to be quadruplet. I can plug Flashdisk, mouse, external and digital camera in same time. Worth money for usefull gadget
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001DBEM4:these_speakers_are_amazing:m._cody_jones_"book_maven"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
513168
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001DBEM4
</asin>
<product_name>
Harman Kardon Soundsticks II 3-Piece Plug and Play Multimedia Speaker System: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
These speakers are amazing
</title>
<date>
November 8, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
M. Cody Jones "book maven"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
ATX
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I first saw these speakers at the Apple store, and i really liked the sound and the look.  I went on amazon and found a better price and i couldnt be happier with them.  As long as you have a decent soundcard, these speakers really are great.  i have had no problem with them at all, they look really cool, they're loud, they're small, the woofer gives you a lot of bass (which you can turn down), and the sound from the speakers is clear.  buy these
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00003006E:this_switch_works...:uncle-buck
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
516571
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00003006E
</asin>
<product_name>
Linksys EZXS55W EtherFast 10/100 5-Port Workgroup Switch: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
This switch works...
</title>
<date>
April 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
uncle-buck
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Houston, TX USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
What else do you need to know? You plug in your PCs and a cable to your router - and go. I used a Netgear hub for years. Replaced it with this Linksys switch and my network speed improved immediately
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00007LTAU:better_than_my_old_belkin_model:krystal_hillsman_"icekryztol"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
520408
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00007LTAU
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus PA050U USB 2.0 High-Speed Hub (4-port): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Better than my old Belkin model
</title>
<date>
January 30, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Krystal Hillsman "icekryztol"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
TN
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
It's speedy and space saving and inexpensive. I bought this to replace my Belkin because the Belkin needed to be plugged in. This one is powered by your computer so there's no extra power cords, which is a big plus to me. 

The only thing I dislike about this is the fact that the Hub takes up two Usb ports instead of just one like the Belkin. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00007LTAU:pretty_useful_product:bharat_t._madhavan_"maddy"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
520412
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00007LTAU
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus PA050U USB 2.0 High-Speed Hub (4-port): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Pretty useful product
</title>
<date>
October 21, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Bharat T. Madhavan "maddy"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
RI, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
You will appreciate this product only if you don't have enough USB ports. In my case, I had plenty of ports, but needed an extension cable, which would help me in plugging the flash drives, whithout bending down and plunging into the cave of wires(I keep my CPU, under the table).The only complaint I have is the the wire lenght is not long enough.
Overall good value for price
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007Z1M50:great_mouse_for_gamers:enmanuel_zottola
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
521300
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007Z1M50
</asin>
<product_name>
Logitech MX518 Gaming Optical Mouse - Metal: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Great mouse for gamers
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Enmanuel Zottola
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The mouse is perfect for games. I use it to play ET and is great. The software provided by Logitech is configurable in all ways
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00024VTKE:have_really_enjoyed_it.:a._labbe_"tipsyover"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
527996
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00024VTKE
</asin>
<product_name>
iRiver iFP 799T 1 GB Flash MP3 Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Have really enjoyed it.
</title>
<date>
February 28, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
A. Labbe "tipsyover"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Boston, MA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I wanted a non-iPod digital music player, and found this to be a terrific option.  It plays a number of different formats, and includes a lanyard, which is nice when commuting on the train, or for plane travel.  I have only used alkaline batteries so far, and have had excellent battery life.  The menu takes an hour or 2 of playing with to learn, but once you get familiar with the buttons and menu, it's pretty easy.  I have also enjoyed the built in FM tuner, and have not any trouble with reception, even on a moving commuter train.  The sound quality is very good.  I've been using 128 bitrate MP3 songs so far.  The software for transferring music is pretty easy to use, although I did have a little trouble getting the player to be recognized as connected, which seemed to be some kind of order of connections issue.  The included earbuds aren't the most comfortable, especially since I already lost the foam padding, but I will probably get a better pair anyway.  They do sound good though.  Also, the included cases are pretty cheesy and I didn't even bother with them.

A little hint:  One thing I did not like was that because of the location of the on button, the unit can fairly easily be turned on when you have it stored in a bag or pocket.  To combat this, simply turn the Hold on.  The unit won't turn on accidentally when it's on
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000AZ67Z:still_works:j._strauss
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
530316
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000AZ67Z
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDCZ2-256-A10 256 MB Cruzer Mini USB 2.0 Flash Drive (Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Still works
</title>
<date>
April 30, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Strauss
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Worcester
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I've had this device for two years.  Just today I sent it through the wash cycle of my laundry (not on purpose).  The thing still works!! I will not, however, try sending it into the dryer though beause I'm pretty sure that would fry this thing
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001DI6FW:product_desciption_could_be_more_specific:r._david_maurer_"david_maurer"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
530434
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001DI6FW
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus PAUH212U 7 Port USB 2.0 Hub: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Product desciption could be more specific
</title>
<date>
May 28, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
R. David Maurer "David Maurer"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
St. Louis metro area
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I,ve seen complaints about the ac adapter you "must" plug in. Hey guys, try it without an outside energy source, I just hope I,m not gonna fry something but it seems to work fine just plugged into a powered USB port. I have a VERY high end system though with wattage to sprare, but no more PCI slots, Damn 7900 512 gtx graphics cards, why do 2 of em have to take up so much room. Oh well, trade offs are a bi---, but a reality and 7 extra USB slots are awfully nice
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00000JPPI:works_with_dvd_recorders,_too!:larry_j._commons
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
535609
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00000JPPI
</asin>
<product_name>
Maxell DVD-LC DVD Lens Cleaner: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
11 of 13
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Works with DVD Recorders, too!
</title>
<date>
September 6, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Larry J. Commons
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Arlington, TX USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I was about to retire an old standalone DVD recorder, because it would no longer let me create menus or finalize discs.  I bought this lens cleaner and -- voila! -- the recorder is working again.  Super easy to use (it's simply a DVD that you insert into your machine, and the menus tell you what to do).  Highly recommended
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000067VBM:they're_ok:nhopps
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
545137
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000067VBM
</asin>
<product_name>
50-pack Slim CD/DVD Jewel Cases (5mm) Clear: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
They're OK
</title>
<date>
February 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
nhopps
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Hinton, WV United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Just a note to those who've been having trouble opening these cases, without breaking them. If you use an emory board to slightly sand the top knob which is holding the case together, you'll be able to open and close it ok. Don't sand too much, and just do the top knob, or it won't hold together. I like the fact that these cases are clear and fairly inexpensive, so I wanted to make them work. Hope it works for you
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005MIS8:kind_of_slow_,_but_good_over_all:buer_song
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
553098
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005MIS8
</asin>
<product_name>
Viking CF512M 512 MB CompactFlash Card: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Kind of slow , but good over all
</title>
<date>
August 11, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Buer Song
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The CF card works fine but it's response is kind of slow compaired to the 32MB CF card came with my Canon Powershot A95. I got this card 3 weeks ago and so far their hasn't been any problems.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006IW1X:reliable_discs,_great_price:j._merritt
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
554981
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006IW1X
</asin>
<product_name>
Memorex 700MB/80-Minute 52x CD-R Media (100-Pack Spindle): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Reliable Discs, Great Price
</title>
<date>
September 26, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Merritt
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Washington-Baltimore Corridor
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I do all my burning on a standard Windows Media player, and it's almost entirely data and music, no video. For my purposes, these CD's sound great. In some cases, it actually seems like the discs have enhanced the sound spectrum somewhat. That may be a trick my ears are playing on me but, nevertheless, I'm a big fan of the Memorex. And they're a steal if you catch the sale price. Recommended
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0006TI9WG:what_to_consider...:james_cooper_"conspicuous_consumer"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
555926
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0006TI9WG
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk 1 GB Memory Stick Pro Duo (SDMSPD-1024-A10): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
What to Consider...
</title>
<date>
October 18, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
James Cooper "Conspicuous Consumer"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Pennsylvania
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
When I buy flash memory, I consider price, speed, manufacturer and vendor. I got this particular memory stick for a SonyEricsson w810i phone. I paid extra to get it from Amazon (no they don't always have the best price). This way I am confident that I can return it if I got the wrong one or have a problem with it.

The card works fine in my phone, and since I have a USB cable that hooks up to the phone, I don't have to be concerned about removing the card to use a card reader. I have not yet experienced any problems with Sandisk memory products.

I am told that the Sandisk sticks are faster than Sony's, but I have no way to confirm this, nor do I know if my phone (mp3 player, camera) is able to take advantage of faster speeds. The longest process is transferring music to the phone, and I wasn't in a hurry anyway.

This stick comes with an adapter to use with the older memory stick format, so I can use the 128mb stick that I replaced in my Sony Camcorder (which had a 4mb stick in it. No, it's not a typo. It's actually a 4 megabyte memory stick)
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008VF63:amazing!:a._p._singh
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
557402
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008VF63
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony MDR-E828LP Fontopia Earbuds with Winding Case: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Amazing!
</title>
<date>
September 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
A. P. Singh
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Miami, FL
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
These earphones are incredible! They are comprised of excellent bass and treble. You experience everything much nicely. These earphones compared to the iPod headphones are excellent unlike those raggety things. I bought these from ebay for $8 and for that amount of price, you can't regret buying these sensational earphones
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008VF63:owned_these_for_two_years_-_eventually_broke:moflicka
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
557405
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008VF63
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony MDR-E828LP Fontopia Earbuds with Winding Case: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Owned these for two years - eventually broke
</title>
<date>
August 29, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
moflicka
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
California
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Just my two cents, I bought these from the sony store for $15 bucks two years ago, they've lasted me this long for light office use, so at $7/year, this seems to be a good budget earphones.  I'm not an audiophile, so I don't need expensive earphones.  However they did eventually die on me where the cable connects to the jack, the wires got loose and the sound just stopped.  Moral of the story: don't twist or touch the wires/cable.

Pros:  lightweight, budget-oriented, comfortable fit for my ears
Cons:  eventually broke, cheap earphone covers will get lost easil
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002CPBWI:muy_pero_muy_bueno:rodriguez_jose
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
557844
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002CPBWI
</asin>
<product_name>
Microsoft Wireless Notebook Optical Mouse 3000 -Slate: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Muy pero muy bueno
</title>
<date>
November 5, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Rodriguez Jose
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Muy pero muy bueno, es mejor todavia que el primer dvd que salio de esta gira
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000VYJOM:one_of_the_good_high_speed_cf_readers_on_the_market:amazon_fan
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
559742
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000VYJOM
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar Media RW020-001 USB 2.0 CompactFlash Reader: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
26 of 32
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
One of the good high speed CF readers on the market
</title>
<date>
October 16, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Amazon Fan
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
NJ, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Just some specs missing from amazon's description:

USB 2.0 CompactFlash Reader

Small and travels with ease
LED status indicator indicates when files are being transferred 
Data transfer speeds up to 480Mb/s 
Backward compatible with USB 1.1 
Ships with removable USB 2.0 cable 

Features 

Designed for large data transfers, like images, music and video 
Data transfer 5 to 6 times faster than using USB 1.1 
Portable - weighs only 1.5 ounces 
Protective cover case keeps reader pins away from external hazards 
Compatible with Windows 2000/ME/XP and Mac OS X and 9.1 
No drivers required with most current operating systems

2-year Limited Warranty 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00026KJ26:i_like_it:alfy
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
563138
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00026KJ26
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar Media 32X 1 GB Secure Digital Card (SD1GB-32-231): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
25 of 28
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
I like it
</title>
<date>
December 1, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Alfy
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Ohio
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
If you snap shots in burst mode, or if you want to take pictures at sporting events, fast cards like those are the way to go.
Almost no lag, large capacity, lifetime warranty, no complaints
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007G6RZE:great_for_the_nikon_d200_-_sandisk_2_gb_extreme_iii_compactflash:e._shapiro_"gadget_guy"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
569554
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007G6RZE
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk SDCFX3-2048-901 2 GB Extreme III CompactFlash Card (Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great for the Nikon D200 - SanDisk 2 GB Extreme III CompactFlash
</title>
<date>
August 31, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
E. Shapiro "Gadget Guy"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Washington DC
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I purchased several of these cards .... they work great and as advertised. The D200 has a memory buffer ... but these are still FAST cards!  I have used them in the D70 as well. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000B59JJ2:terrific_product.:w._s._quirch
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
570656
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000B59JJ2
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk 512MB TransFlash microSD Card (SDSDQ-512-A10M, Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Terrific product.
</title>
<date>
November 19, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
W. S. Quirch
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Sandisk, leader in this kind of technology products sure do not come short with this one. It works excellent on my phone Samsung t609.I would have bought a 1GB but the phone manufacturer do not recomend it, so bear that in mind. For pictures the resolution at close range and bright light is just excellent. For music as an MP3, lots of memory and room to fill as well as for video. Data and in general is terrific...just like I said Sandisk leads the competition and also seems to be the the standard card for just about any product that requires this kind of card. I will most definitely and undoubtely will not accept substitutions. Only Sandisk is extremely reliable. Personal experiences with these products proof it repeatledly. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000B59JJ2:it's_a_memory_card.:aj
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
570665
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000B59JJ2
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk 512MB TransFlash microSD Card (SDSDQ-512-A10M, Retail Package): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
It's a memory card.
</title>
<date>
August 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
aj
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I use the memory card in my Samsung d807 phone.  Works perfecty
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009XSYZ:a_good_line_doubler_for_the_price:infinite-loop-systems_"buyer_and_seller_of_electronics,_computers,_parts,_overstock."
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
570774
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009XSYZ
</asin>
<product_name>
ADS Technologies HDUP1500 HDTV Upconverter: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
A Good Line Doubler for the Price
</title>
<date>
August 20, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Infinite-Loop-Systems "Buyer and Seller of Electronics, Computers, Parts, Overstock."
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Los Angeles
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
For the Price, I doubt you could do better.  True, there are higer-end devices out there that will improve your picture to the pinnacle of performance, but if all you're after is a significant improvement in the quality of EVERY channel and DVD you watch, you can't beat the ADS for it's price. The biggest flaw is the device's inability to deal with program material that has excessive light or white backgrounds, where the device either creates artifacts or attempts to correct resolution causing my Philips Plasma set to black-out for moments.  This aside, I'm very happy with the ADS, especially it's under $300 price.  One day maybe I'll upgrade to a unit by DVDO, but not until they come don to the sub-$500 range
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006JPV8:watch_out_where_you_plug_in_your_laptop:peterpumpkineater
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
572539
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006JPV8
</asin>
<product_name>
NOVI WI-4C 4-Channel FM Wireless Intercom: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
watch out where you plug in your laptop
</title>
<date>
October 14, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
PeterPumpkinEater
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The one in our bedroom wouldn't always work, couldn't hear the kids calling.  I was unplugging my laptop charger at the same time someone was calling and discovered the charger was filtering the voice.  Both my Dell charger and Thinkpad charger had the same effect, even without the laptop plugged into the charger.  If your having problems, I would start with unplugging other things first.

Overall, these have been a Godsend, wife no longer has to scream at the kids across the entire house.  Used to drive me crazy
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000A0AJH:it_reads_em_all:nikolay_a._vazonov
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
584745
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000A0AJH
</asin>
<product_name>
CyberHome CH-DVD 300S Progressive-Scan DVD Player (Silver): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
It reads em all
</title>
<date>
July 19, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Nikolay A. Vazonov
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is a nice product,i buught it beacause i needed to play DVDs from foreign country and my fancy "sony" dvd vcr player can't read them but this little thing can,it reads all the standards i'm glad i've got it. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000CO77EQ:money_well_spent:j._c._bennett
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
591726
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000CO77EQ
</asin>
<product_name>
1-Year Replacement Plan for Electronics Products $100 to $124.99: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
money well spent
</title>
<date>
August 31, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
J. C. Bennett
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Washington, DC United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I was burned by another company with I bought their product and they didn't offer a replacement plan.  The item died and no one can repair it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006I5FQ:works_great,_good_price:auction_queen_"love_them_bargains!!!!"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
595490
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006I5FQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Lexar PD-128-231 128 MB JumpDrive Portable USB Flash Drive: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
works great, good price
</title>
<date>
March 18, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Auction Queen "Love them bargains!!!!"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Gardena, CA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Great price for a 128MB jump drive, works perfectt for my daughters college work, such a good price I bought 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00003IE4J:i_always_wanted_to_write_a_battery_review:recovering_remote_programmer_"charlie2620"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
599865
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00003IE4J
</asin>
<product_name>
Energizer E91BP-4 AA Batteries (4-Pack): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 11
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
I Always Wanted To Write a Battery Review
</title>
<date>
December 14, 2000
</date>
<reviewer>
Recovering Remote Programmer "charlie2620"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Santa Cruz, CA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I used to buy Energizers and Duracells at $3-4 a pop for four batteries.  Now I buy generic Alkalines at Costco.  Cost: $8 for 10 four packs.  It's like having a battery store in the kitchen drawer.  According to a recent coprehensive story in Consumer Reports, there is only a little difference between name brand and generic alkaline batteries
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006B91Z:pretty_useful_product:bharat_t._madhavan_"maddy"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
603937
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006B91Z
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus PA055U 4 Port USB 1.1 Ultra Mini Hub: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Pretty useful product
</title>
<date>
October 21, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Bharat T. Madhavan "maddy"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
RI, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
You will appreciate this product only if you don't have enough USB ports. In my case, I had plenty of ports, but needed an extension cable, which would help me in plugging the flash drives, whithout bending down and plunging into the cave of wires(I keep my CPU, under the table).The only complaint I have is the the wire lenght is not long enough.
Overall good value for price
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000F38IQK:flawless_budget_mini-stereo:dabigpaybackski
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
604505
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000F38IQK
</asin>
<product_name>
Panasonic SC-PM53 180-Watt 5-CD Executive Micro System: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
24 of 24
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Flawless budget mini-stereo
</title>
<date>
October 11, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
dabigpaybackski
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
OR
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this model in order to be rid of my almost-new Sony MHCEC70 with its faulty ergonomics and detestable tuner.  Having once owned an earlier PM-series model, this new Panasonic was the obvious choice and it does not disappoint.  Like its predecessor, the PM53 is a nice, powerful compact stereo with (for the money) ridiculously nice audio quality and a good tuner, especially on the FM band.  It can easily be turned up load enough to cause hearing damage and annoy neighbors in adjacent houses.  The remote covers every function and is easy enough to figure out without consulting the manual.  

Right now, this is the budget stereo of choice for the discerning.  Sony's competing models are cheesy-looking (hog attention on store shelves,) bigger (i.e., take more materials/cost more to ship,) and consequently suffer certain cost-cutting measures like the aforementioned crappy tuner and simplified (and of course, proprietary) antenna connector.  It's like choosing between the Pontiac and the Toyota.  The Sony is for the unwashed rubes who want 300 watts of mylar-coated bling.  The Panasonic is for people who want something that makes pleasant sounds and looks like the rest of the furniture. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00024ENVG:computer_to_go:janice_reynolds
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00024ENVG
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus TCG650 15.4 CityGear Chicago Notebook Backpack: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Computer to go
</title>
<date>
March 29, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Janice Reynolds
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Brunswick, ME USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Bag is attractive and very sturdy.  The computer fits securely and is well padded.  I recently used it on a trip and was able to place other carry on items in it and it traveled well
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006HQ3B:western_digital_wd800bb_80gb_7,200rpm_ultra_ata/100:robert_l._aydelott_"robert"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006HQ3B
</asin>
<product_name>
Western Digital WD800BB 80GB  7,200RPM Ultra ATA/100: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Western Digital WD800BB 80GB 7,200RPM Ultra ATA/100
</title>
<date>
November 29, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Robert L. Aydelott "Robert"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Randle, WA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Drive got to me timly, installed per instructions, and works wel
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000F4CTUK:must_have_professional:stuart_plotkin_"splotki"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000F4CTUK
</asin>
<product_name>
Panasonic TH-50PX60U 50" Plasma HDTV: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
must have professional
</title>
<date>
April 10, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Stuart Plotkin "splotki"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
paramus, new jersey
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
picture sound all great. the only problem is that you must have an advanced degree in english,engineering,and computer science to set the television up.  without my cable company making a house call setup is impossibl
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006I5KQ:almost_excellent:a._welles
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006I5KQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Omnimount 75/100 CL Cantilever Mount: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Almost excellent
</title>
<date>
March 21, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
A. Welles
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Santa Cruz, CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This mount is nicely designed and well-made; it fit the TV perfectly. Our only criticism is that the screws provided for attaching it to the wall were of poor quality. The heads stripped out right away and it took a trip to the hardware store to get replacements
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000CODQD2:deskjet_6980dt-great_product:sandra_b._rohrbacher_"rysanwelsh"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000CODQD2
</asin>
<product_name>
HP Deskjet 6980DT Color Printer: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Deskjet 6980dt-great product
</title>
<date>
February 21, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Sandra B. Rohrbacher "rysanwelsh"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Sparta, NJ
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I read some of the reviews about installation issues and they concerned me initially. But, when it came time to get the printer up and running on my wireless network, there really weren't any issues. Just following the directions (and avoiding the EasySecure option) worked fine. I would highly recommend this printer-the quality of the printing is excellent, the feature/function set is quite high for a moderate price, and it's a great home/office printer that has lots to offer.

</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000FPLTRI:no_problems_here:marisa_nitsch_"theauctionstall"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000FPLTRI
</asin>
<product_name>
Belkin N1 Wireless Desktop Card ( F5D8001 ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
No problems here
</title>
<date>
December 14, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Marisa Nitsch "theauctionstall"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Yonkers, NY United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Maybe beginning ones were a bad batch? Had mine months now and it works great. Everything it says, it does. No problems  keeping it in the system and did not cause any errors.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000FPKOV0:superior_quality_and_performance:wireless_headset_user
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000FPKOV0
</asin>
<product_name>
CS70 Wireless Headset System Lightweight Over Ear 300FT Range: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Superior quality and performance
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Wireless Headset User
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
NY, NY
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The CS70 is an excellent product, easy to setup and use and good battery life
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000FCFYT0:1_ghz_memory_card:timothy_m._linscott_"red_sox_timmy"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000FCFYT0
</asin>
<product_name>
1GB Xd Picture Card Type H: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
1 GHz memory card
</title>
<date>
April 4, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Timothy M. Linscott "Red Sox Timmy"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Grand Rapids MI
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Great memory card for the price.  I would highly recommen
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000FCFYT0:very_good_buy:a._michael
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000FCFYT0
</asin>
<product_name>
1GB Xd Picture Card Type H: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Very good buy
</title>
<date>
March 21, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
A. Michael
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Englishtown, NJ
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This xD memory card works perfectly with my camera Fujifilm Finepix F650. Good buy for the price
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000LRMS66:great_product:lawman
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000LRMS66
</asin>
<product_name>
Garmin Portable Friction Mount for Nuvi and StreetPilot C Series (010-10908-00): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
GREAT PRODUCT
</title>
<date>
March 18, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Lawman
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this because I did not want to mount my Garmin 350 Nuvi to the windshield. This device makes is much easier to switch the unit to different cars. I drove normally and the unit did not slide around on my dashboard. I can also mount the unit on a center console and it works there too. Please note that this is a complete unit for portable mounting and it is much cheaper than buying the sandbag and mounting arm separately
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00004TDN0:in_its_day...it_was_on_top.:s._horrocks
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00004TDN0
</asin>
<product_name>
Handspring Visor Deluxe (Blue): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
In its day...it was on top.
</title>
<date>
August 11, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
S. Horrocks
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Washington, DC
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have had my Handspring Visor Deluxe for 5...yes, FIVE years (actually longer).  While I take decent care of it, it has taken care of me.  My doctor has one too...exactly like mine and we often talk about how perhaps they should be replaced, but the darn thing is still working great and does everything we need it to.  I finally ordered a new PDA with all the capabilities of my laptop and am passing this one on to someone else who needs it. (I'm not selling it...good karma)  

Down to business - the Handspring Visor Deluxe is not the creme de la creme anymore.  But in its day it was.  Great product and if you don't need the bells and whistles (or color display)...go for this.  Totally flawless.  People often complain about the styli of other PDAs.  No complaints here.  Not only is it relatively comfortable, it is stainless tipped with plastic on both ends (doesn't break) and it stays securely in place when you store it in the device.  I literally lost my ORIGINAL stylus just a few days ago.  

The display is not as easy to read as the new super crisp glossy screens that are out now, but if you need a basic device with a few bells and whistles that are thrown in for fun (heck, a good deal of the new ones don't have IR)... go for it.  And for the price I just saw it listed for on Amazon ($85) it's a total steal.  Great product
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009W39R:storm_alert_radio_(jensen_mr-600):l._holladay
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009W39R
</asin>
<product_name>
JENSEN MR-600 AM/FM Weather Band Radio with Storm Alert: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Storm Alert Radio (Jensen MR-600)
</title>
<date>
February 16, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
L. Holladay
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Columbia, SC USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The item works perfectly if you do not place it near other mechanical devices, i.e. TV, air purifier, elec. clock, etc.  Fortunately it hasn't alerted us yet so that will remain to be experienced.  You have to turn it a
number of directions until you get the best reception, then leave it in that  position
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000F6SR0O:awesome_tv_for_the_best_price:van_e._hodges
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000F6SR0O
</asin>
<product_name>
Panasonic TH-42PX60U 42" Plasma HDTV: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Awesome TV for the best Price
</title>
<date>
April 11, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Van E. Hodges
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is the best value you can get. Awesome picture with 10,000:1 Contrast Ratio. My XBOX 360 looks amazing with 1080i resolution. Definitely worth the money. You would not be disappointed with this TV.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009ORXE8:i_love_this_thing:urbanite4ever
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009ORXE8
</asin>
<product_name>
iRiver T10 1 GB MP3 Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
I Love this thing
</title>
<date>
December 31, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
urbanite4ever
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I got this on sale for $80 and i love it. It holds about 300 songs, gets plenty loud, has amazingly good battery life, and takes all my abuse. I play it at least 2 hours a night, if not all night, its my alarm in the morning, i listen to it in the car, on the bus, before school, during lunch, ok how bout his i use it a ton. I never leave home without it its small, easy and comfortable to hold, and it wont die if you drop it. Wiht my previous player I had an issue with it erasing all the songs and i know other people who have had that issue with other players but this one hasn't let me down yet. O and one big plus the battery back is attached so it will never dissapear
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009XTDHO:great_recorder:xlamp_"xlamp"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009XTDHO
</asin>
<product_name>
Olympus DS-2300 Digital Voice Recorder: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great recorder
</title>
<date>
January 17, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
xlamp "xlamp"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New YOrk, NY
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this to record interviews done primarily on the phone and it's worked beautifully. Clear and easy to use. Once downloaded onto my computer I used the Olympus transcription package to transcribe the interviews. This allowed me to listen on headphones, control the progression (and backtracking)of the interview with a foot pedal and keep both hands on the keyboard to type quickly. This voice recorder plus the transcription package dramatically cut the amount of time I had to take trascribing the interviews. Well worth the price. I'd recommend this combo highly, especially to other journalists.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000G2BGFK:wd_mybook-the_answer_to_all_of_your_digital_storage_needs:kirk_j._blankenship_"www.academycurve.com"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000G2BGFK
</asin>
<product_name>
Western Digital My Book Pro Edition 500 GB External Hard Drive with Triple Interface: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
WD MyBook-The answer to all of your digital storage needs
</title>
<date>
April 1, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Kirk J. Blankenship "www.academycurve.com"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
LA, CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I've been very pleased with this external drive-500GB. My only comments would be that at first the drive was a little 'hit or miss' with mounting on the desktop but a restart would always fix it. Now it seems to always mount. Its all automatic so no need to ever touch the drive. The other thing would be that it could use one more FireWire 400 port (there is only one). I don't use 800 yet so I need to daisy it off of my SmartDisk FireLite that happens to have 2. All in All-Get this drive
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002ICGDY:good_fix_for_laptop_audio:jersey_sam
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002ICGDY
</asin>
<product_name>
TURTLE BEACH Audio Advantage Micro: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Good Fix for Laptop Audio
</title>
<date>
August 19, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Jersey Sam
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Solid product.  Headphone/speaker jack on my laptop died and manufacturer wanted $40 just to cover shipping fees to have it fixed!  I bought this great little unit instead for under $30.  Good audio.  Actually, it saved my laptop once too, laptop fell from 2-3 feet but landed right on the rubberized Turtle Beach Micro, which took most of the force.  It was bent 90 degrees at the USB connector but it still worked!  Proof of solid construction..
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000KZBAP4:happy_w/purchase:m._chung
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000KZBAP4
</asin>
<product_name>
Sharp AQUOS LC37D42U 37" LCD HDTV: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Happy w/purchase
</title>
<date>
March 17, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
M. Chung
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
NY, NY USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is our first LCD TV.  Our tube TV finally died.  My wife actually picked out this unit and Consumer Reports also recommended this unit.  We purchased it directly from AMAZON on January 23, 2007.  I wanted to wait a couple of months before I write my review to see if anything happens. But to my surprise the TV is still running and there have been no problems.  We have digital HD and the pictures are great.  It took me a couple of weeks to get use to watching tv with such sharp color and contrast.  However, if you are watching normal digital programming you may not be too happy as it is flat.  But overall its a good buy for us
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000KZBAP4:excellent_tv!:mlb_fan
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000KZBAP4
</asin>
<product_name>
Sharp AQUOS LC37D42U 37" LCD HDTV: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Excellent TV!
</title>
<date>
March 10, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
MLB Fan
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Tucson, AZ
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I researched TVs for a long time before I ended up buying this set.  It helped that Costco offered a coupon for $300 off the price ($1000 final price).   I thought I may not like the TV, so I decided to buy in person as opposed to online to help with a potential return.  However, there is no way I am returning this TV; it's awesome.  The picture is great, and that is just with SD.  The Strech feature makes the regular 4:3 picture fit the screen and not look distored.  I was worried about buying the 37" TV and then having to watch with the black bars on the sides to avoid distortion.  But there is no need with this TV since Sharp has figured out how to strech the picture without distortion.  DVDs look incredible on this TV as well.   What is even better is the built-in HD tuner.  I was debating upgrading my cable to the HD package, but I decide to spend $13 on "rabbit ears" from Target.  Oh my, once I plugged in the indoor antenna and let the TV track for digital stations I was amazed.  The analog station popped up like a fierce snowstorm in winter, but when I went up to the HD digital companion station, I couldn't believe my eyes.  An incredible HD picture with the rabbit ears set on my desk...indoors no less!   Why would I upgrade my cable TV to the HD package when they can't offer the local stations in HD?  Especially when they are FREE with a simple antenna!  I was told this was possible, but quite frankly I was skeptical.  Not anymore, I am so glad I got the Sharp that has the built-in tuner.  I seriously considered just buying the HD ready TV monitor and upgrade through my cable provider.  Boy am I glad that I didn't do that.  If you are in the market for a very nice TV that is easy to use and provides a great picture, I would highly recommend this set. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000A2AGZC:classy_wall_mount:ryan_mccullough
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000A2AGZC
</asin>
<product_name>
Articulating LCD Wall Arm for 22IN-37IN LCD Screens - Silver: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Classy Wall Mount
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Ryan Mccullough
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Wichita, Kansas
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is a great product. It was easy to mount and looks great. The only thing that could make it better is if it let the tv rest closer to the wall, but from what I have seen they all sit out from the wall about two inches. I have a 32" LCD mounted on it and it seems pretty heavy for the mount so I always try to keep it closer to the wall, but every time I come home my wife has it extended all the way and swung over 45 degrees. This hasn't caused any problems and I'm sure this is well within its design strength. 

Highly Reccommended
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000A2AGZC:quality_construction,_easy_installation:demanding_buyer
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000A2AGZC
</asin>
<product_name>
Articulating LCD Wall Arm for 22IN-37IN LCD Screens - Silver: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Quality Construction, Easy Installation
</title>
<date>
October 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Demanding Buyer
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Southern California
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is a high quality, precision made piece. I'm very particular about the construction of things that I buy and this Peerless arm more than met my expectations. It was easy to attach to the back of my 32" LCD television and equally easy to mount to the wall. I read a review of another arm where the buyer complained that there were many pieces to assemble. Not so here. Everything is assembled except for the mounting plates that attach to the back of the screen. All hardware is included along with clear, complete instructions. I'd be surprised if you could find something better
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000A6NUVU:quality_keyboard_and_mouse:yare_marketing
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000A6NUVU
</asin>
<product_name>
Microsoft Wireless Laser Desktop 6000 v1 ( B7T-00001 ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Quality Keyboard and Mouse
</title>
<date>
November 28, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Yare Marketing
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Boston, MA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Pros:
Like a quality piano, the keys give a sense of weight, the bend in the keyboard tool some getting used too but now am typing a full speed.  The mouse offers great control, though I haven't much used all the buttons that are one the form.

Cons:
The only gotcha is if the computer freezes, there is no way to control-alt-delete.  Also, Setting the favorite keys to non microsoft items tends to reset after updates and restarts
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000A6NUVU:watch_out_for_key_reflections:john_clavadetscher
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000A6NUVU
</asin>
<product_name>
Microsoft Wireless Laser Desktop 6000 v1 ( B7T-00001 ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Watch out for key reflections
</title>
<date>
August 29, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
John Clavadetscher
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Seattle
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
One warning for users with over head lights.  The 6000 keyboard that has tranparent (light gray) keys is very hard to read if the lighting is not quite right.  I have a light directly above my desk  and the reflected glare off the keys makes all the letters and numbers disappear.  Go for a black key or similar model
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00025O7LQ:excellent_down-to-basic_mouse_and_it_looks_good:d._tsai_"hardware_guy"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00025O7LQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Kensington 72213 Mouse-In-A-Box Optical USB/PS2 Mouse (PC/Mac): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Excellent down-to-basic Mouse and it looks good
</title>
<date>
November 5, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
D. Tsai "Hardware Guy"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Sunnyvale, CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
After going through nearly 6 mouses (including several of the Microsoft mouses), I settled on this because its round contuour shape and large effective button area that extend very far back. It also works with my KVM switch, which is a key consideration. The buttons are a bit stiff but I expect them to "loosen" up a bit after some use. I highly recommend this mouse
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007M0VWS:can't_wait_for_the_color_version:judith_b._kenyon
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007M0VWS
</asin>
<product_name>
Verbatim CD-R 80MIN 700MB 52X LightScribe (30pk Spindle Box): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Can't wait for the color version
</title>
<date>
March 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Judith B. Kenyon
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Burbank, CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
They are everything the other reviewers said they were, and I, too, can't wait until the printing is darker and in color!  Wish it didn't take so long to print and hope the darker images and color only require an upgrade
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002MQGOU:great_cable,_great_price,_low_loss,_excellent_sound.:john_p._rhodes_"john_paul"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002MQGOU
</asin>
<product_name>
Optical Cable 12 ft.: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great cable, great price, low loss, excellent sound.
</title>
<date>
June 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
John P. Rhodes "John Paul"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Birmingham, Alabama
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I used two 12 foot cables with a coupler for a 24 foot PCM connection between my satellite receiver and my home theater system.  The Dolby 5.1 is excellent
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BFNT2A:bang_for_its_buck:n._passero
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BFNT2A
</asin>
<product_name>
Logitech LX7 Cordless Optical Mouse - Dark Blue ( 931395-0403 ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Bang for its buck
</title>
<date>
March 10, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
N. Passero
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Verona, NJ
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
this is one of the best in its class for the low price. quick, and responsive, and very convenient for a frequent web browser. the back and forward buttons on it work like a charm and are perfect for the web
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002ILKNQ:excellent_apple_screen:tin_tin_"journalist"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002ILKNQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Apple Cinema 23" HD Flat-Panel Display: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Excellent Apple Screen
</title>
<date>
February 3, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Tin Tin "journalist"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Chicago, IL
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Replaced my old 22" Cinema Display that was 5 years old. What a difference. Clear screen, flawless finish, solid and adjustable stand. Easy hook-up, it took longer to clean the dust off my computer than hook this up!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002ILKNQ:big_and_beautiful_laptop_accesory:tharv_"harvey809"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002ILKNQ
</asin>
<product_name>
Apple Cinema 23" HD Flat-Panel Display: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
big and beautiful laptop accesory
</title>
<date>
January 8, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Tharv "harvey809"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
PA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I got this monitor along with a keyboard. When I get home I plug my laptop into both and I have a huge screen to do my work on. The colors are terrific, the mouse works seamlessly across the laptop screen and the big auxilliary screen. Wish I had done this a long time ago
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002A9RFM:works_like_a_champ,_24/7:alejandro_au_ma
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002A9RFM
</asin>
<product_name>
Netgear GS608 8-port Gigabit Ethernet Switch (10/100/1000 Mbps): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Works like a champ, 24/7
</title>
<date>
January 4, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Alejandro Au Ma
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Just remember to use the proper cable, Cat 5e or Cat 6
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002A9RFM:gige_switch_that_is_both_fast_and_quiet:franticinfresno_"fresno14"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002A9RFM
</asin>
<product_name>
Netgear GS608 8-port Gigabit Ethernet Switch (10/100/1000 Mbps): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
14 of 15
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
GigE switch that is both FAST and QUIET
</title>
<date>
August 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
FranticInFresno "Fresno14"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Fresno, CA  USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Like so many other small home office users, I have recently upgraded my network to 1000mpbs to help increase productivity.  Unfortunately, I originally purchased a GigE 8 port switch from another mfg. that used a fan on their switch, a VERY noisy fan.  After a month of listening to what sounded like an airplane engine, I tossed that unit and purchased this 8port Netgear GigE unit.  It is SILENT.  Basically a plug and play item due to its unmanaged nature, I have had good data thru put and no problem.  It comes with a small clip on stand for vertical storage if desired.  The unit is finished in an attractive gray and chrome exterior.  It is also small enough to live on a desktop with sucking up valuable real estate.

So, if you are looking for a switch that will not be stored remotely in some closet, this is the one that will keep the peace in your office. A+ ****
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000FA9F74:great_looks_and_sound:j._seidel
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000FA9F74
</asin>
<product_name>
Eton S350 Deluxe DLB AM/FM Shortwave Radio (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Great looks and sound
</title>
<date>
March 27, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Seidel
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have this radio for two weeks now.  I am very satisfied with the reception of AM, FM and Short Wave -- very sensitive.  Has great sound.  The only negative is the lack of being able to preset the stations.  Would buy the radio again - worth the money
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009GWX46:great_price:jennifer_anthony
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009GWX46
</asin>
<product_name>
Motorola Talkabout FV200AA GMRS / FRS Two-way Radio (Pair): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
18 of 19
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great price
</title>
<date>
December 9, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Jennifer Anthony
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Chicago,Illinois
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
How can  you go wrong with a price so low. They're good for both parents and kids to use. Not to mention they're easy for young kids to operate! Keep in touch
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008DD20:can't_say_enough_good_things:petros_"loving_life"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008DD20
</asin>
<product_name>
M-Audio Revolution 7.1 Surround Sound PCI Card ( PC / Mac ): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Can't say enough good things
</title>
<date>
May 2, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Petros "loving life"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Pacific Northwest, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
     This card, using VIA's superb Envy24 HT chipset, is a huge improvement over my Realtek and VIA Envy24HT-S based cards.  Everything sounds better.  

     My old Audigy 2 platinum (which I think I shall melt) did better in 3D games, but only slightly. Since this card doesn't snap, crackle, and pop like the Creative cards do, I'll venture to say that it actually DOES make games better, since there are no weird noises distracting from the feel of the game.

     PROS:
* Very high audio sampling rates, allowing for incredibly good audio production; warm, rich, warm bass all the way up to crystal clear highs.
* No crackling, popping, or hissing!  A real joy after pulling my hair out for years trying to figure out why Creative Labs cards keep doing this.
* Well-maintained, solid drivers.
* Supports EAX 2.0
* Excellent ASIO support.

     CONS:
* No hardware support for DirectSound; however, if your machine is faster than about 1GHz, you probably won't notice the difference.  Benchmark your results on a machine made in the last three years and you'll find that no hardware DirectSound acceleration amounts to *less* than a 1% difference in speed.
* Only supports up to EAX 2.0, due to Creative Labs refusing to license the technology.  Sound difference is minimal, though
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006YZ3Y:great_deal!:christopher_deweese
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006YZ3Y
</asin>
<product_name>
Monster Cable THX Mini-to-RCA Audio Cable (8 Feet): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great Deal!
</title>
<date>
April 19, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Christopher Deweese
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Kansas City
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I'm using this Monster cable to connect my iPod to my receiver via an iPod dock and it works flawlessly.  Sound is crisp and clear.  Plus, it's a lot cheaper than getting the actual Monster iPod AV cable.  The length of the cable makes it convenient but not too cumbersome.  It's a great way to increase the functionality of your iPod
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006YZ3Y:easy:bruce_c._erb
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006YZ3Y
</asin>
<product_name>
Monster Cable THX Mini-to-RCA Audio Cable (8 Feet): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Easy
</title>
<date>
January 26, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Bruce C. Erb
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
White Plains, NY
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Within about 12 seconds of opening the box I was listening to my IPOD on my home stereo.  Wires are well made.

There may be cheaper options that work as well but these will last forever
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00005RE7T:great_speaker_for_its_class!:t._fischer
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00005RE7T
</asin>
<product_name>
JBL HTI6C 2-Way 6.5-Inch In-Ceiling Loudspeaker, Pair (White): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
13 of 13
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great speaker for its class!
</title>
<date>
January 27, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
T. Fischer
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Minneapolis, MN
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I ordered a pair of these online, a bit nervous as I wasn't ever able to hear them (I heard a pair of JBL SP6C's, the cheaper version, at Best Buy, and wasn't all that impressed, although it might have been the poor listening environment).  

Anyway, the speakers arrived, we installed them (they look great and inconspicuous in our living room ceiling) and I'm quite impressed.  Note that we're using these for "whole-house" background music, not home theater, so my standards aren't as high as they would be in the HT case.  But for a 6.5" speaker, these put out a surprising amount of bass, and clear highs.  Right now we just have a cheap amplifier hooked up while we're shopping for a better one, and they still sound great.  These probably would be just fine for HT rear-speaker use (I wouldn't want any in-ceiling speaker for front or center HT use).

Our home theater downstairs already has JBL speakers (studio series for the fronts and center, northridge for the rears) and I've been very happy with them.  

I recommend these for those who need a great looking and decent sounding in-ceiling speaker without breaking the bank. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002GS4Z0:great_camera:robert_c._ward_"rob"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002GS4Z0
</asin>
<product_name>
Panasonic Remote Video Monitoring Webcam (BL-C10A): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great Camera
</title>
<date>
March 29, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Robert C. Ward "Rob"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Kansas City, MO
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Bought 2 of these to watch over my house while I am at work.  Setup is pretty easy, but be prepared to wait a minute after changed settings, many changes when you initial setup the camera require it to restart.  Camera's work great together and the free use of [...] to access the cameras is nice.  Setting up timers and sensor emails/ftp is pretty straight forward but will require a user to test and retest to get the settings just right.

Pros: Price is good for a ip camera with tilt/pan.  viewnetcam.com feature is a great addition to the camera package.  Works great with similar model panasonic cameras.

Cons: Multiple restarts while setting up or making changes(minor issue), limited online support/how-to's
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002GS4Z0:cabin_watcher:bog_rat
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002GS4Z0
</asin>
<product_name>
Panasonic Remote Video Monitoring Webcam (BL-C10A): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
cabin watcher
</title>
<date>
February 1, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
bog rat
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Chicago
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
After reading all the connection problems with wireless IP cameras , I decided to purchase the wired ver. (BL-C10A panasonic). I was very pleased with the easy setup and dns service included for the camera . I currently use this camera in a cabin , so I can look in and see the temp. inside and look around. This is simpe remote monitoring , as hookup took less than 1.hr to get up and running. I do not use the emailing feature presently .
Pros : simple to setup and get running over internet
       price is reasonable
       images are the best for a camera this cheap
       using viewnet  (dns service) very easy  
Cons : wired to the router 
       no included light leds (but at this price)
       must use timer to reset ip camera (cheap house timer every 24hrs
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000FH658O:good_product,_horrible_handling_in_shipping:bob_smith
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000FH658O
</asin>
<product_name>
Samsung HT-TQ85 XM-Ready Five-Disc DVD Changer Home Theater System (5.1 Channel): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Good product, horrible handling in shipping
</title>
<date>
April 10, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Bob Smith
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The product works well for my space and needs. One note to Amaazon. When you ship a $400 item, thats semi fragile, and the box shows up looking like it was used as a make shift soccer ball, how does the consumer deal with physical damage? The item is so massive to ship back, and most likey costly.
I experimented with buying an expensive electronic online because the price was right. I was worried how the shipping would be handled, and sure enough, I was worried rightfully. The DVD tray catches everytime the tray comes in and goes out. The top of the receiver/dvd player had been slightly caved in. Even with all the packing Samsung supplied, it could not protect the product from the shipping company. It will be such a hassle to try and exchange this, that I am not sure if I will be purchasing something this expensive and fragile online again. Other than that, I have purchased smaller items, and less fragile from Amazon with no issues. I realize that the shipping damage canot be held on Amazon, as it is out of their control. I just don't think I will roll the dice on something like this in the future. Too bad, it would have been nice to say good buy to brick and mortar pressure salesmen
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009H50OA:excellent_flashlight:obibo_"obibo"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009H50OA
</asin>
<product_name>
Dynamo Illuminator Wind-up LED Flashlight: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Excellent flashlight
</title>
<date>
December 31, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
obibo "obibo"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Baltimore, MD
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Not quite as bright a conventional flashlight, but certainly bright enough. No battery feature can't be beat. Manufacturer claims it will stay on for a hour with a one minute wind. I've never left mine on that long, but I've only needed to wind it once in over a year. This is an excellent flashlight. I've bought several
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007UVRVO:it_connects_to_more_than_advertised!:e._mcauliffe
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007UVRVO
</asin>
<product_name>
Wyse USB to Parallel Converter Cable - Parallel adapter - USB - parallel: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
It connects to more than advertised!
</title>
<date>
March 17, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
E. McAuliffe
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Easton, MA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I was unsure of whether to purchase this product when I saw that my printer (HP Deskjet 712C) was not on the list put out by the manufacturer but after reading some others' reviews, I tried it anyway because the price was right.  It may look a little cheesy but it works.  I didn't even need the CD that comes with it in order to use the product.  I just plugged it in to my printer and then into my new Dell laptop and it worked.  I think I may have had to restart and add my printer but that was it.  Very good product
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007UVRVO:usb_to_parallel_cable:l._q._johnson
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007UVRVO
</asin>
<product_name>
Wyse USB to Parallel Converter Cable - Parallel adapter - USB - parallel: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
USB to Parallel cable
</title>
<date>
March 1, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
L. Q. Johnson
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
CT USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Do you have an OLD printer you would like to tie to that NEW lap top?  I did and at first I didn't think it could be done but a little quick research on Amazon and I found this beauty.  The Sabrent cable is very well made and has the look of quality and ruggedness.  I just plugged it in and everything took off without a hitch.  (PC w/Windows XP
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EIW3E4:samsung_hp-s5053_50"_plasma_hdtv:peter_j._grzybowski_"pete_grizz"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EIW3E4
</asin>
<product_name>
Samsung HP-S5053 50" Plasma HDTV: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Samsung HP-S5053 50" Plasma HDTV
</title>
<date>
April 11, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Peter J. Grzybowski "Pete Grizz"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Long Island, NY
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Great picture, great price, superb and fast delivery by Amazon (via EGL trucking).
No complaints except for a faint buzzing sound on the plasma TV. I have heard that all plasma's "buzz" a bit. This would not stop me from purchasing this TV again
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EIW3E4:the_wife_is_finally_sold:d._young_"happytvowner"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EIW3E4
</asin>
<product_name>
Samsung HP-S5053 50" Plasma HDTV: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
The wife is finally sold
</title>
<date>
March 31, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
D. Young "HappyTvowner"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Francisco, ca
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I was looking for a tv that offered bang for buck.  So I knew Samsung is the way to go.  Except my wife was not eager as I was, but soon after buying it The Planet Earth HD Discovery channel show was on.  Now I can not get my wife to stop talking about HD.  We love the TV not the best tv, but best for the price.  Nice design and easy to use
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EIW3E4:great_tv,_service_and_delivery:k._feltner
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EIW3E4
</asin>
<product_name>
Samsung HP-S5053 50" Plasma HDTV: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great TV, Service and Delivery
</title>
<date>
March 26, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
K. Feltner
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Washington, D.C.
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have had my Samsung for about three weeks now; no problems.  I am extremely hapy with the picture quality and the number of inputs.  We also bought the 42" plasma for my parents; we've been extremely happy with it as well.  In addition to the television, I am extrmemly happy with Amazon and the delivery process.  Everythin was handled very professionally.  The tv arrived within the timeframe and undamaged.  I will buy next tv through Amazon as well
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000632G5:great_speakers_at_a_great_price:andrea
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000632G5
</asin>
<product_name>
JBL Northridge N24AWII 2-Way Weather-Resistant Bookshelf Speakers, Pair: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
14 of 16
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great speakers at a great price
</title>
<date>
February 17, 2003
</date>
<reviewer>
Andrea
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Seattle, WA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
These speakers deliver a clear, crisp, and vibrant sound, with a richness expected of a higher-end speaker.  I would recommend these to anyone interested in a good-quality sound but keeping an eye on price
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0002CWPW2:great_price,_great_product:r._lewis
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0002CWPW2
</asin>
<product_name>
Netgear JGS524 24-Port Gigabit Ethernet Switch: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great price, great product
</title>
<date>
March 8, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
R. Lewis
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Kemah, TX United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
After reading several reviews on this unit, we purchased it.  The majority of our equipment supported gigabit and so we decided it was time to "get in the game".  It took less then 15 minutes to install in our rack and change over to it.  All I can say is "wow"!  The performance is phenomenal.  We have had no issue with it since switching over and it just plain works.  I cannot believe that we can obtain that level of speed in network applications for the price we paid.  Highly recommended
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0000AOWWY:nice_product!!!:brian_m._eichorn_"utley's_fan"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0000AOWWY
</asin>
<product_name>
Microsoft Wireless Optical Desktop Elite: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Nice Product!!!
</title>
<date>
March 3, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Brian M. Eichorn "Utley's fan"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Philadelphia, Pa
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this product mainly for my girlfriend to use on my computer. I find myself using it most of the time, now!  The mouse is great, lost of extra buttons on it (not that I need them, but it makes it a little more convenient in case I do.)  The Keyboard is great...lots of shortcut buttons right on the keyboard, making navigation VERY easy.  A couple of features on the keyboard I really like are the scroll whell on the left, the favorites buttons (all customizable, as are all the shortcut buttons on this keyboard) and the very comfortable hand rest.  I got this refurbished and it works like new!  I HIGHLY suggest this.  The only drawback is that it is a little bigger than I would have liked, but I don't mind it nearly as much as my girlfriend.  If that's not a problem, I highly suggest this product!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006I62X:works.:a._laundrie
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006I62X
</asin>
<product_name>
Fellowes Standard Foot Rest: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Works.
</title>
<date>
March 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
A. Laundrie
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Not much to say here.  It works.  Easily adjustable with just your feet.  Feels good wearing socks
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009ZAA4M:nifty_table_radio_sounds_great_-_works_great:mark_s._deneen_"juicymusic"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009ZAA4M
</asin>
<product_name>
Sangean WR-2 Digital AM/FM Tabletop Radio, Walnut: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Nifty Table Radio Sounds Great - Works Great
</title>
<date>
February 1, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Mark S. Deneen "juicymusic"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Ferndale, Ca
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is a surprisingly good radio at this price. It is small, compact and yet very robust and quite heavy. It is nothing like the cheapie plastic radios one sees in the drug store. Here are three things I really liked about this product: 1) The AM/FM reception is outstanding. I am in a bad area with few stations and this model gets them in clean and clear. Listening to FM on my stereo headphones was a real pleasure. 2) The buttons and controls are easy to use and sensible in function. This is something Sangean seems to get very well. 3) The multi-level display lighting can be turned OFF, or up in 3 steps from dull to very bright. 

A few things I didn't like. The pilot light for "ON" is a like an intense blue laser and lights up the entire room at night. I had to put black electrical tape over it. The AUX input is a mini-jack instead of RCA connector. Minor inconvenience here. And finally, the cabinet is nice wood, but the finish is not as good as I think it could be. 

This radio is a pleasure to use and it sounds better than I expected for this price. It's a keeper
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009YJXMI:archival_quality_for_a_good_price:amyprime
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009YJXMI
</asin>
<product_name>
Verbatim 16x Single-sided DVD-R Spindle, 100 Discs: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Archival quality for a good price
</title>
<date>
January 15, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
AmyPrime
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I want the DVDs I'm making to last to as close to forever as possible, so I did a lot of research before deciding what DVDs to buy.  Verbatim came out as #1 for durability.  I chose the DVD-R format for maximum compatibility with various devices.  And I've only had a few errors after burning about 75 DVDs.

Amazon's sale price for these was great.  If you're just looking for short-term backup media, I'm sure you can find cheaper, but these are a different class of DVDs
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000653GY6:hdmi_difference:mark_keuls_"postman"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000653GY6
</asin>
<product_name>
Belkin HDMI to HDMI Cable 8ft Cord: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
HDMI Difference
</title>
<date>
February 11, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Mark Keuls "Postman"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
With my new LCD television, the hook-up was a snap and what a difference with the new HDMI compatible up-scale DVD I installed.  The audio and visual difference for DVD and HD television programing is amazing with the cost at half the price at retail stores.  Very happy and highly recommended
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000653GY6:don't_spend_extra_for_monster_cable!:5_of_5
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000653GY6
</asin>
<product_name>
Belkin HDMI to HDMI Cable 8ft Cord: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Don't Spend Extra For Monster Cable!
</title>
<date>
November 8, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
5 of 5
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Great Falls, VA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This works perfectly, and it is built very well.  My picture looks great and sound is also great
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00004Z5RA:two_wrists_way_up!!__:-):peabody88
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00004Z5RA
</asin>
<product_name>
Belkin F8E263-BLK Wave Rest Gel-Filled Cushion Wrist Rest Pad (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Two Wrists WAY Up!!  :-)
</title>
<date>
April 13, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Peabody88
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
IL USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Wonderful for those who type and work with computers alot--soft and comfortable!  I haven't had any problems with carpal tunnel since!  It didn't have a nasty smell as other reviewers stated.  A great buy; saves me a lot of pain
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006LLHX:great_product:kraig_r._benson
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006LLHX
</asin>
<product_name>
ATandT 5800 Accessory Handset for 5800 Series Phones: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
great product
</title>
<date>
March 21, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Kraig R. Benson
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This phone is clear and easy to use ...have had a couple and have not been disapointe
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000E3DRZS:ipod_charger:jerry_d._withers
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000E3DRZS
</asin>
<product_name>
USB Wall Charger for Ipod with USB-to-Dock Cable (White): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
11 of 11
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
IPOD charger
</title>
<date>
July 5, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Jerry D. Withers
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Washington D.C.
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This performs better than the unit offered at the Apple store at about 20% of the cost! Plus it has an indicator light and the folding plug is handy for travel. Good deal
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0001KWGOW:works_pretty_well_for_what_i_need_it_for:rentagoodbook
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0001KWGOW
</asin>
<product_name>
PalmOne Zire 31 Handheld: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
works pretty well for what I need it for
</title>
<date>
February 18, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
rentagoodbook
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Chicago Suburbs, IL USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I had an old Palm m100 for the longest time and used it as an electronic replacement for a paper organizer. But it ate batteries and wasn't rechargeable, so when I got a newer computer without a serial port (and discovered it would cost a fairly decent sum for a serial-USB connector), I decided to upgrade. Thought it'd be cool to have something with mp3 playing capabilities as well, (I don't own an iPod or other small mp3 player) but I didn't need many features beyond an organizer (didn't need for e-mail, etc) and didn't want to spend much over $75. 

Pros: 
I like the Palm interface, very intuitive.
Calendar and contacts work well
Plays mp3's
Syncs well with Outlook/computer
Plugs in to recharge; all cords came with it.
Easy to download new software (I recommend Blocks, it's similar to Tetris)

Cons or caveats:
Display: when viewing calendar in "full month" mode, I have trouble seeing any entries unless I view the screen at an angle. Not a deal-breaker, but a little odd. They probably improved this with newer (pricier) models, but you get what you pay for. I can read all other screens just fine.
Haven't used it to display photos; I don't think I'd use this to do that--resolution isn't worth the effort.
Expansion card: WARNING: WILL NOT READ ANY CARD OVER 1GB size! (I had purchased a 2GB card with the intent of putting mp3's on it and listening to them on the Zire. Wouldn't read it. Didn't realize this till I read the fine print. Fortunately, I have a camera which takes SD cards so I can use in the camera).
Listening to mp3's: This really isn't gonna replace an iPod for features. They do say that listening to mp3's uses more battery than other functions. I would agree but then I've not used this for long periods of time as an mp3 player, so I can't really say. Functionally, mp3's play just fine with RealOne player. Sound quality is pretty good BUT I have noticed a "hiss" background noise when using earbud-style headphones; it's a lot less noticeable with "outside-the-ear" style headphones. Recommendation: outside-the-ear style headphones with an in-line (cord) volume control. If you're in a quiet environment, the lowest volume level on the RealOne player isn't all that soft. With non-volume-adjustment headphones, the lowest volume level (there's a slider bar on screen) was the loudest I wanted to hear. Headphones with a volume adjustment fixes that problem.

Overall, it's been worth the $$ for me as a replacement for my former m100, and it works ok as an mp3 player, as long as you can recharge it on a regular basis
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000FDXWQ6:good_deal:d._mroz
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000FDXWQ6
</asin>
<product_name>
iRiver Armband for T10 MP3 Player: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Good deal
</title>
<date>
January 3, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
D. Mroz
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This arm-band is surprisingly good.  I initially got it for my boyfriend for his iRiver, but I was afraid it wouldn't fit his arms since he's very muscular.  Surprisingly - it stretched enough and wasn't tight!  He loves it.  I thought there might be too much motion on mine when I run or use the eliptical, but no, it's fine
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00011KM3I:great_product:julia_m._covey_"romance_novelist"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00011KM3I
</asin>
<product_name>
Case Logic CDE-48 48 Heavy Duty Wallet CD Organizer (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great product
</title>
<date>
August 14, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Julia M. Covey "romance novelist"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Hillsboro, OR USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This product is exactly as described and arrived very quickly... A+++++ seller!  Will definately buy from again
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000ETYO7C:nice_brand-name_receiver_with_6.1:donald_j._larson_iii
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000ETYO7C
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony STR-DG500 6.1 Channel Home Theater Receiver: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Nice brand-name receiver with 6.1
</title>
<date>
March 20, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Donald J. Larson III
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
FL USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This receiver puts out a lot of power. It also has a bit of weight to it. It comes with a microphone to automatically adjust it for optimal surround sound. The remote take some getting used to but it is great how you can hook up a DVD player, CD player, radio and many other devices. The display is nice. You really have to read the manual before you start plugging away. If you're a surround sound fan on a budget pick this up
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000ETYO7C:quite_pleased:robert_jpnes
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000ETYO7C
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony STR-DG500 6.1 Channel Home Theater Receiver: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 11
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Quite pleased
</title>
<date>
December 3, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Robert Jpnes
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
A couple years ago I got a projector for the "big screen effect", and decided to finally get my mini Advents out of storage for the surround sound. My OLD Pioneer receiver worked ok, but I decided it was time to upgrade. I have 30 year old Speaker Lab (build 'em yourself) speakers up front with the Advents in back.
The only complaint I have with this unit is there is no way to connect a turn table (yes, I'm old). So I kept the Pioneer for dedicated service to the record player.
I have my son hook everything up as he is taking networking in school. For him it's a breeze. I don't even look at the directions. I just say "here".
Having said that; I think this thing is great! If you are my age and can go back 30 years to your first sound system, you paid a lot more to get a simple 200 watt system (WOW) for your records and cassettes. Ahh.... technology.
I love this thing! I can understand that some folks want something better, but for 95% of us, this will be the last one you will ever need.
Highly recommended.
4 stars for the lack of LP connection. Otherwise.... 5 all the way
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00083XXY4:works_great_with_the_psp!:s._rahman
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00083XXY4
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk 1 GB Ultra II Memory Stick PRO Duo: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 10
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Works Great with the PSP!
</title>
<date>
September 15, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
S. Rahman
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I just got mine from Amazon (after a lengthly delay).  It is an awesome memory card.  It comes with the adapter so that you can use it in digital cameras.  I tested it on the camera and it worked great.  The real test was the compatibility with the SONY PSP.  No issues there.   The card worked flawlessly.  I've already used up 600 MB.....its a must buy!

Plus, at $99.99, its much less than other retailers.   btw, i ordered it at $104.99, then contacted amazon about the price drop.  They credited the difference to me without any hassle and gave me the one-day shipping at no charge because of the delay.  Overall great service too.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00083XXY4:perfect_for_psp:andrew_perluss
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00083XXY4
</asin>
<product_name>
SanDisk 1 GB Ultra II Memory Stick PRO Duo: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Perfect for PSP
</title>
<date>
August 29, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Andrew Perluss
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Portland, OR
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I use this 1GB card in my Sony Playstation Portable, and it is awesome!  The tranfer rate using the USB 2.0 cable to the PSP is very good, and I love having all that storage space for movies, music, and images.  I got the Ultra II because I had read that Sandisk outperformed Sony in speed tests, and I have to agree.  The tranfer rate seems much faster than with the 32MB Sony card that came with the PSP.  For an extra $5-$10 I got the Ultra II that has a warranty and better performance.  I think it is well worth it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0009XDKNW:great_product_at_a_great_price.:p._pirolla
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0009XDKNW
</asin>
<product_name>
IPOD Shuffle Armband Carrier: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great product at a great price.
</title>
<date>
January 25, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
P. Pirolla
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
When compared to other 1st generation iPod Shuffle armbands, this one is just as good, if not better, and you can't beat the price.  Definitely worth every penny
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00004U8RE:good_quality_ink_for_an_inkjet_printer:"dargo2001"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00004U8RE
</asin>
<product_name>
Canon Ink Cartridge Ink I550,I850,S520,MP750,MP780 (4479A003): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 11
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Good Quality Ink for an Inkjet Printer
</title>
<date>
July 29, 2003
</date>
<reviewer>
"dargo2001"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Southern CA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The BCI-3eBk is good quality black ink for an inkjet printer.  I have used this ink for a couple of years now and don't recall it smudging on the pages I print.  The price on this product (compared to HP products) is fair, but I am able to print a 100 to 200 pages before running out of ink.  Of course, you will get more pages out of this cartridge if you print more color graphics than text
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00006343N:good_price.__just_not_sure_it_is_needed.:nirav_k._mulani
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00006343N
</asin>
<product_name>
Monster Cable MP SW 200 Subwoofer PowerCenter SW 200 with Clean Power Stage 1 v2.0: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
good price.  Just not sure it is needed.
</title>
<date>
April 10, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Nirav K. Mulani
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
good price.  Just not sure it is needed
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00008NRR2:good_deal:c._towles
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00008NRR2
</asin>
<product_name>
6PT USB 2.0 ADPT CARD-PCI: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Good deal
</title>
<date>
January 9, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
C. Towles
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Winston-Salem, NC United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The first one I ordered worked for about four days and then stopped recognizing the USB devices I was plugging into it.  Although I had considered just getting a refund, Amazon was quick to replace the card with no hassles.  The replacement card has been working fine for a couple of months now.  The USB 2 is much faster than the original USB ports that were a part of my original computer and this particular card was a reasonable price
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00030DEUA:tight_fit_for_the_475:robert_frank
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00030DEUA
</asin>
<product_name>
HP Q3424A#B1H Photosmart Carrying Case: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Tight fit for the 475
</title>
<date>
May 11, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Robert Frank
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Jacksonville, FL United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I own the HP 475 and since it's slightly larger then the rest, the printer barely fits in the case. It does fit but it is very tight. I would not recommend this for the 475. Probably I shouldn't have bought this but I really liked the case
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000068NUW:works_fine:d
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000068NUW
</asin>
<product_name>
HOSA DUAL MIDI CABLE, 3m (9.9 ft.): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
works fine
</title>
<date>
January 11, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
D
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Minnesota
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This cable has worked fine for me with no problems.  I'm using it to connect an inexpensive keyboard to a laptop
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009AKLJ:just_what_the_doctor_ordered:r._dewitt_"cowboy"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009AKLJ
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus DVD401 9 Vehicle Portable DVD Travel Case: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Just what the doctor ordered
</title>
<date>
November 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
R. DeWitt "Cowboy"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Cuero, Tx USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Outstanding item. Plenty of room to carry dvds. Enough padding to protect the player, but not too bulky
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009AKLJ:compact_and_convenient:l._recker_"lisarex"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009AKLJ
</asin>
<product_name>
Targus DVD401 9 Vehicle Portable DVD Travel Case: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
15 of 16
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Compact and convenient
</title>
<date>
May 10, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
L. Recker "LisaRex"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Cincinnati, OH
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I wish Targus made the same bag just a few inches wider.  My Toshiba 2600 barely squeezes in the bag.  However, it does fit and I was able to mount it between the two seats of our 2004 Toyota Sienna with no problems.  There's also ample room for cords and DVDs. 

I like how this bag doubles as a storage case and a way to mount it in the car for viewing.  

All in all, a very nice product. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BM946S:likes/dislikes:_a_list:j._reuland_"jodemonster"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BM946S
</asin>
<product_name>
Creative Zen Micro Photo 8 GB MP3 Player, Green: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Likes/Dislikes: A List
</title>
<date>
April 11, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Reuland "jodemonster"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Laramie, WY USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
There are some things I like about this, others I don't. Some people have written similar reviews, but I want to add my 2 cents. Hope this helps potential buyers.

Likes:
1. Small, easy to use
2. Good sound quality
3. Good storage capacity for those of us who don't have 10 million songs hanging out on our computers.
4. Some people have complained that the Creative Media software is hard to understand. I disagree, I found it straightforward. You can even change the titles, artists, and genres of the songs on the software before it gets transferred to the player. Yes, I realize this can also be done in WMP, but sometimes you want to edit later, or you missed something earlier.
5. Replaceable battery. If it dies, you can get another one, you don't have to send it in to the company.

Dislikes:
1. The shuffle mode is annoying. It doesn't go through the entire playlist on shuffle. Once a song is over, it goes right back onto the potential playlist, and can sometimes get played again fairly soon after it was first played, to the exclusion of the other items on the list. I want to hear all my songs at least once before I hear repeats.
2. The Creative Media Center software doesn't install on Windows Vista.
3. This is a hard drive player, so no running with it. That's okay though for people like me: I don't run. It also makes it cheaper than the IPod Nano, which is a flash player.
4. The cable to recharge the battery is a usb cable that hooks directly into your computer. I don't like this because I'm not always around my computer, I don't lug it with me everywhere I go. However, there are ports you can buy (here on Amazon, even) that plug into the wall and have little usb ports, so that's handy.
5. Not as many accessories as the IPod, but not that important.
6. You can't view your photos while you are listening to music. Sometimes this sucks, but if you have a camera phone, or are in an actual conversation with someone, you probably won't be listening to your music anyway.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BM946S:scott_in_maine:s._snedden_"principal_in_maine"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BM946S
</asin>
<product_name>
Creative Zen Micro Photo 8 GB MP3 Player, Green: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Scott in Maine
</title>
<date>
March 9, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
S. Snedden "Principal in Maine"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The Creative Zen is outstanding. Took a little while to get use to the controls but the sound is incredible. I bought one for my wife as well and see loves it.  I did spend a little extra money for better earbuds. For the price that I paid -[...] for 8GB you can't go wrong
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EGC9B8:great_size:girleen_"girleengirl"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EGC9B8
</asin>
<product_name>
Red Classic CD WALLET-128: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
22 of 22
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Great Size
</title>
<date>
September 1, 2003
</date>
<reviewer>
Girleen "girleengirl"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
CT USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I totally love this Cd Wallet- it is not too big and not too small. The construction of this piece is very sturdy. I've owned this for a while now and it still looks new. The color is a classic, the only problem I have with it is that the CD pockets are very flimsy other than that the exterior of this piece is unbelievable. I love it!!! I actually bought another one, oh another note do be careful because the if you don't handle the zipper with care it tends to get caught. But nothing major :
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EDI406:this_is_my_fourth_sony_dvd_player,_and_easily_the_best:sabalom_glitz
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EDI406
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony DVP-NC85H/S HDMI/SACD/CD Progressive Scan 5-Disc DVD Changer Silver: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
This is my fourth Sony DVD player, and easily the best
</title>
<date>
February 10, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Sabalom Glitz
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Miami, FL USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The very first DVD player I bought was Sony's very first 5 Disc DVD changer back in 1998. It was an excellent player, but as the technology improved, it could no longer keep up. I upgraded to a single disc Sony which could handle DTS, and later to another single disc player which could handle progressive video. But I always missed the convenience of a 5 disc changer after having been spoiled by one at the start. At about one-third the price of that original DVD changer, this player has all the features of those previous upgrades and more while retaining the familiar functionality of my first player. It produces an excellent picture, has lots of tweakable settings, has more outputs, and is also very stylish looking.

I do have a couple of nits, though. My original DVD changer had buttons on the remote which allowed me to jump directly to whichever disc I wanted. With this one, I have to press a Disc Skip button to cycle through all the discs until I reach the one I want. The front of the player does have direct access buttons, though. I wish I still had my old remote control as I'm sure it would work with this unit to restore that remote functionality.

Second, the upscaling through HDMI produces a great image, but not really any better than leaving the image at 720x480p. In fact, upscaling will sometimes magnify some interlacing artifacts visible in the picture. It's also unfortunate that while connected through HDMI, progressive scan cannot be turned off. This shouldn't be an issue most of the time, but there are some video sources that might look better with it turned off. Progressive settings can only be changed on the unit itself and not through the remote, but they cannot be turned off when connected through HDMI. 

One last thing about the HDMI connection. There can sometimes be a noticeable audio sync issue when using HDMI connections and digital TVs. This is not a problem with the player, but with the way HDMI is currently implemented. This player has an audio-sync adjustment feature which should compensate for the problem. However, the audio-sync adjustment doesn't work if the player is connected to a receiver via its optical digital outputs. Since I need to have mine connected this way in order to enjoy 5.1 sound, the audio-sync adjustment feature is useless here. And that's a shame. By the way, there should be no audio-sync issues if the player is connected via component, s-video, or composite outputs.

There's also a minor thing I've found about all my Sony DVD players that I haven't liked. They are unable to correctly display Time Remaining on certain discs, or more commonly on the special features (documentaries, etc.) on certain discs. I also have a cheapo Philips player which has no problems displaying Time Remaining on those things (even on the menu). It's an improvement I'd really like to see implemented on future players.

Now, despite the complaints I've listed above, don't get me wrong. This is still an excellent player and I really love it. I happily recommend it to anyone considering purchasing it. It really is a great value and it performs very well in most instances, and I feel it's the best DVD player I've ever owned. It's just not quite perfect. In all likelihood, it's also the last DVD player I'll ever own as I'll probably be buying a BluRay or other HD player in a couple of years when that format war is over. But this is a great player to hold me over until then
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000FJEYYY:sennheiser_mx55v_stereo_headphones:michael_j._smith
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000FJEYYY
</asin>
<product_name>
Sennheiser MX55V Stereo Headphones w/ Twist-to-fit System and Volume Control: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Sennheiser MX55V Stereo Headphones
</title>
<date>
March 13, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Michael J. Smith
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
These headphones sound pretty good, but they aren't the best.  When running, the volume controller gets in the way and bounces.  It is also easy to change the volume which is annoying.  I also find the fact that the cord for the right side is longer than the other a little bit strange.  I realize it is done intentionally, but it does nothing for me.  Overall, for just listening at your desk or in your room, these are great headphones.  For running, I would recommend something else
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BTL0OU:worked_well.:ira_c._kleinberg
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BTL0OU
</asin>
<product_name>
Kensington Travel Plug Adapter with USB Charger 33346: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Worked well.
</title>
<date>
January 9, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Ira C. Kleinberg
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Toms River, NJ
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I needed a way to power my laptop, and my batteries for my camcorder, as well as my digital camera. This was done without a problem when my wife and I visited Slovakia.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009UHYQ:best_antenna_on_the_market:joel_barron
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009UHYQ
</asin>
<product_name>
TERK FM-50 Indoor/Outdoor Dual-Drive Amplified FM Antenna (TERK FM50): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Best Antenna On The Market
</title>
<date>
February 13, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Joel Barron
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Southaven, MS USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I installed this antenna in my Pawn Shop where we keep most of our electronics running all day. I could never get good reception with standard antennas and now this single antenna does the job better than any I have ever seen. Keep in mind that I have a full surveillance systen, alarm syster, phone system, 20 home stereos, a dozen or more computers and on and on. The Terk FM-50 has exceeded my expectations.  Thanks, Joel DBA Pawn-Plus
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00009UHYQ:finally,_an_fm_antenna_that_works_for_me!:clinton
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00009UHYQ
</asin>
<product_name>
TERK FM-50 Indoor/Outdoor Dual-Drive Amplified FM Antenna (TERK FM50): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Finally, an FM antenna that works for me!
</title>
<date>
January 27, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Clinton
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Thousand Oaks, CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Radio reception in my apartment is terrible.  I have purchased a few indoor antennas, even a different Terk model, but none of them helped very much. I had to move the antenna around to different areas for different stations, and my digital FM radio only received one digital channel.

This unit, however, works great.  I get every station I want, and the digital FM works great.  The only thing I would mention is that the antenna casing is bulky, so if you're concerned about asthetics you'll have to figure out where you can conceal it.  Also, I didn't get any additional benefit from the amplifier, but the antenna worked so well that I didn't need it
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000J2Q9HW:a_quality_product!!:tonio
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000J2Q9HW
</asin>
<product_name>
Sonic Impact i-F2 Portable Speakers for iPod: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
A quality product!!
</title>
<date>
April 2, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
ToniO
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
After reading several reviews on portable speakers, I decided to purchase the Sonic Impact i-F2 for my iPod.  It has great sound quality, the case is durable, it packs away easily and you can take it anywhere.  You can listen to music while its charging and the sounds system is quite attractive.  This is by far the best accessory I've purchased for my iPod.  Did I mention that it has a remote control!!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000117DGW:no_regrets:jc
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000117DGW
</asin>
<product_name>
Netgear WGB511 802.11g Wireless Networking Kit: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
No regrets
</title>
<date>
March 19, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
JC
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Contrary to popular belief, I even had a good experience the one time I needed technical support. A few random disconnects, but overall a great product
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000090W8J:believe_the_hype!:techguru
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000090W8J
</asin>
<product_name>
Motorized SkipDoctor by Digital Innovations (Model 1013000): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
16 of 23
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Believe The Hype!
</title>
<date>
April 18, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
TechGuru
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
London - England
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Remember back in the day when CDs first came out? I do: hi-fi shops and all my male relatives proudly did these demonstrations of scatching a cd, putting it into a player, PLAY and  *presto* the disc played.

Well, either they were making bomb-proof players back thens or the laser never got to the scratched bit of the disc because I used to have piles of discs were handled carelessly and didn't play. Yes, you read correctly: I USED to have stacks of unplayable discs.

If you don't read any further, you can stop at the end of this sentence: SKIP DR WORKS!

Here's the short of it

1. I have my own multination consulting firm
2. I have worked with computer in the media and creative industries for over 20 years
3. I dislike misleading reviews
4. I dislike wasting my time looking for products that work
5. I dislike being lied to and wasting my money and 
6. I dislike people aggressively selling me stuff that they have little knowledge about and frankly doesn't work 

On top of that, I am impressed NEITHER by people that trash products that do work NOR people that work for certain manufacturers, create ghost profiles and trump up their employer's products.

SKIP DOCTORS works. 

I own over 3,500 discs. Out of that number, I had countless discs -- from my beloved Trance Planet disc, a Jessye Norman classical and spirituals collection, stuff by Miles Davis, reams of and Nina Simone compilations to computer program discs, backups of various creative projects, rare SACDs (SuperAudio CDs) and stuff that got mangled at parties or  being dragged around the world before CreativeLabs and Ipod came on the scene -- that were ALL unreadable. 

I have seen the sprays, I have seen the wipes, I have seen the low grade sandpaper product, I have tried using BRASSO metal polish (a remedy recommended by a friend of mine from Venezuela -- and for little scratches actually works) and low-grade industrial solvent. HANDS DOWN, short of the industrial strength polishing machines (that handle 500 plus discs at a time and go from $1500 to over $5000), SKIP DR (and all its incarnations GAME DR / DVD DR / PHOTO DR) WORKS. Period.


Why did I only rate the product '4 stars'?

Simple: this review is about the mechanical version of the product. And I am lazy: mechanised means EFFORT. 


Will I buy the mechanised version?

Definitely! The product is in my shopping basket will be ordered (when I finish writing this review to set the record straight!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000FS4OCW:warranty_of_merchantability:william_e._ehardt_"cpa"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000FS4OCW
</asin>
<product_name>
Western Digital WDXE5000KSN 500GB NetCenter External Network Hard Drive: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Warranty of merchantability
</title>
<date>
January 17, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
William E. Ehardt "CPA"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Francisco
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
They say it's quiet, and it holds tons of data.  They were correct.  Fast access speed, easy installation, an overall fine product.  Have not used the feature that let's you back-up your entire drive, but we use it in our LAN for shared files, and it's comforting to know that we've got these files stored redundantly.  This box does just what it claims to do, the warranty of merchantability (from my old law class!).
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B00004U8A0:easy_to_assemble,_classic_look:bradly_baxter
</unique_id>
<asin>
B00004U8A0
</asin>
<product_name>
Sanus Systems AFA Accurate Furniture Audio Stand (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Easy to assemble, classic look
</title>
<date>
February 26, 2003
</date>
<reviewer>
Bradly Baxter
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Everett, WA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Very easy to assemble, has very classic lines, lets stereo equipment have plenty of ventilation, hard to find add-on shelf in maple. Holds a lot of equipment
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000BS4PZW:awesome_cycling_tool:steven_p._myers_"shocked_reader"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000BS4PZW
</asin>
<product_name>
Garmin Edge 305HR+ Bicycle Monitor and GPS (Heart Rate Monitor and Cadence): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Awesome Cycling Tool
</title>
<date>
January 9, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
Steven P. Myers "Shocked reader"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The Edge 305 provides a wealth of knowledge, is easy to install, as well as use. I would love to have given it 5 stars (it deserves them), but one thing that does not work correctly, and really bugs me is the calories expended. It couldn't be more inaccurate if they tried to make it that way. The first day that I installed it, I took it for a quick 1 mile test ride. IT indicated that in that mile I burned 100+ calories. Wish it were true, but it is not. Unfortunetly the next day I was going to take it out on a 100 mile ride, but crashed as I started out and have not riden since (3 days). I wore the chest strap in the office today to test the calories burned further. After 2 hours it read 0 were burned. I just took it for a car ride of 7 miles. In those 7 miles DRIVEN IN A CAR, it indicates I burned nearly 600 calories, again I wish, but no way.

Other than that flaw, whioh I hope they fix with a software update, I highly recommend this product, it all other ways it is great
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B0007Y6AN0:bargain_buy:bob-bo
</unique_id>
<asin>
B0007Y6AN0
</asin>
<product_name>
Sony STR-DE598 6.1 Channel Surround Sound AM/FM Audio/Video Receiver: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
Bargain Buy
</title>
<date>
March 14, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Bob-bo
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Michigan
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Buying from Amazon was cheapest price especially with free shipping.  Stepped up for more power per channel.  Stayed in the Sony family. (Previous Sony surround, output to center speaker quit)  Dislike the speaker hook ups in back, difficult to attach speaker wires and screw down connections.  Overall happy with purchase
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000E5DLIE:v_good_product:k._smith
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000E5DLIE
</asin>
<product_name>
Shure E3c-n Sound Isolating Earphones (Black): Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
4.0
</rating>
<title>
v good product
</title>
<date>
April 2, 2007
</date>
<reviewer>
K. Smith
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Very satisfied with sound quality and ease of use.  Before purchasing, I did believe that these were noise canceling.  However, that is not the case.  The foam inserts do reduce background noise enough that I am very satisfied with the result.  Replacement foam inserts must be purchased online
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000EINRA8:good_hand_heeld_ssb_radio:alfred_lococo_"wd2adl"
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000EINRA8
</asin>
<product_name>
Eton E5 AM/FM Shortwave Radio: Electronics
</product_name>
<product_type>
electronics
</product_type>
<helpful>
9 of 9
</helpful>
<rating>
5.0
</rating>
<title>
Good hand heeld SSB radio
</title>
<date>
June 29, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Alfred Lococo "WD2ADL"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Florida
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
According to other reviews, this radio compares favorably with others in its price class.

As a ham radio operator I can say I am very happy with the E5.  It is the best portable Broadcast band radio I have ever had.

It is the best portable Shortwave radio I have ever had.

I was particularly interested in SSB capability.  It works well.


I called about the noisy power supply and they are sending me the improved replacement.  I use 2100 mah Nimh batteries which I charge externally.  I have two sets.  The radio works well with these.

I found that the internal antenna by itself, indoors, is not enough.  I used the included wire antenna with moderately good results.  But more convient is using the telescoping antenna.  This antenna works, according to the manual, for FM and SW only, but I found that extending it fully, is effective in all cases.  Ressults using this method were similar to the wire.

Holding the radio and using the headset may also improve reception.

Hams know that the antenna is a critical part of any receiver.  There are limits to what is possible in a package this size.  I have not tested it with a tuned outdoor antenna.

For what it is, this is a great tool.  It is a convient size and easy to program and use.  It more than meets my expectations.

[...
</review_text>
</review>
</reviews>